-Eyes over here, Spike!
-Uh, sorry.
For this to work, it's crucial we keep
our concentration totally on the...
Ooh!
Spike! This magic needs
our full attention to make it happen!
There's no other way.
I can't help it.
Look!
Never mind her. She's just being Pinkie Pie.
Super extra Pinkie Pie today.
Twitchy-twitcha-twitcha-twitch.
Pinkie Pie. What in the wide, wide
world of Equestria are you up to?
Oh! It's my tail! It's my tail!
It's a-twitchy-twitching!
And you know what that means.
Actually, Pinkie, I haven't the slightest idea.
The twitching means my Pinkie Sense is telling me
that stuff's gonna start falling!
You should better duck for cover.
Oh, Pinkie. It's not gonna rain.
Weather's barely even a cloud in the...
He just said "Nice catch" in Frog.
Oh. I'm so, so sorry.
You okay, Twilight Sparkle?
I just couldn't stand to see
the pond getting so overpopulated...
...what with the frogs all
hopping into each other and all...
...so I decided to fly as many as I can
on over to Froggy Bottom Bog.
Of course you did.
Bye bye.
Um, Twilight? You've got a little
something on your face there.
Oh, really? Did your Pinkie Sense
tell you that too?
Nah, I could just see it.
Come on, Spike. Let's continue our practice
session where there's a little less commotion.
Wow! That was amazing!
Pinkie Pie predicted something
would fall and it did!
Oh, come on. She said something would fall...
...and a frog just happened to fall
right around the same time.
A coincidence. Nothing else to it.
My tail! My tail! Twitcha-twitch! Twitcha-twitch!
Something else is gonna fall!
Oh, Pinkie, please.
Nothing else is gonna faaaAAAH... Ugh!
Oh no! Twilight fell!
Is it... safe to go help her?
It's okay. My tail stopped twitching.
That was amazing!
Oh, please.
Uh, Twilight? Why are you hangin' out in a ditch?
Because Pinkie Pie predicted it.
Honestly, Spike, she did not.
Two coincidences in a row
like this may be unlikely...
...but it's still easier to believe than
twitchy tails that predict the future.
Twitchy tail? Pinkie Sense?
Don't worry. It's safe.
Prediction already came true.
Oh, wait. Don't tell me
you believe in this stuff too.
I know it doesn't make much sense,
but those of us, who've been Ponyville a while...
...have learned over time that
if Pinkie's a-twitchin', you better listen.
My ears are flopping! My ears are flopping!
What does that mean?!
I'll start a bath for you.
HUH?!
A bath? This thing keeps on
getting more ridiculous by the minute.
So basically it works like this:
I get different little niggly feelings
and they mean different things.
Like when my back is itchy,
it means it's my lucky day!
And when my knee gets pinchy, that means
something scary is about to happen.
Is your knee pinchy now?
No. But my shoulder's achy.
That means there's an alligator in the tub.
How come your knee didn't get pinchy?!
That isn't just scary. It downright dangerous!
No, it's not, silly.
This is my pet alligator, Gummy.
He's got no teeth. See?
Okay, okay. I get it.
Well, I still don't believe
all this "special power" stuff.
It's just a bunch of mumbo-jumbo.
What's not to believe? You do magic.
What's the difference?
Huge!
For one thing...
Magic is something you study and practice.
It only happens when you decide to do it.
And it's meant to make something specific,
that you choose to happen, happen.
With you... it makes no sense at all!
That so not true, Twilight.
Sometimes it's a *bunch* of random things
happening to my body...
...at random times that
supposedly predict the future.
I call them combos.
Combos?
Sure! You know, like ear flop,
then knee twitch, then eye flutter?
That means the sky is about to
be graced with a beautiful rainbow!
Yeah. Sure.
Uh-oh. I feel a combo coming on.
Ear flop... Eye flutter... Knee twitch...
You said that combo meant beautiful rainbow.
Oh, nonononono. You're thinking of an ear flop,
then knee twitch, then eye flutter.
This was an ear flop,
then eye flutter, then knee twitch.
That usually means "Look out for opening doors."
You okay?
I don't believe this.
You don't believe, because you don't understand.
Okay. Now when you get another twitch...
...we'll have all kinds of scientific information.
Okie dokie lokie!
Any twitches yet?
Nopie dopie!
Now? Anything?
Wait! Hold on...
Uh, no.
Are you kidding me?
After a whole day of nonstop twitching...
...now that I've got you all hooked up,
you're not getting a single one?
I don't control it. They just come and go.
That makes no sense!
Sometimes you just have to believe in things.
Even when you can't figure 'em out.
I will not believe in anything I cannot explain.
Wait! Hold on... I'm feeling something.
Omygosh! What? What is it?
It's my tummy!
That usually means I'm hungry. Let's eat!
You know what?
Just forget it.
I don't need to know if this is real or not.
I don't need to understand it. I don't even care!
Okie dokie lokie!
Uh-oh!
Pinkie, have you seen Twili...?
Uh-huh.
Twilight? What are you doing back there?
Did you two plan this?
Plan what?
This is ridiculous! This can't be happening!
This makes no sense!
I have to figure this out.
Twilight?
Honestly, Spike, don't you know better
than to sneak up on ponies?
Oh! Sorry, but...
Um... Well... Isn't that what you're doing?
No.
I'm doing scientific research.
I'm observing Pinkie Pie (scientific name:
Pinkius Piecus) in its natural habitat.
Pinkius Whoecus?
There's something fishy going on
with the whole twitchy prediction thing.
And I'm getting to the bottom of it.
So shhh!
Come on! Pinkius Piecus is on the move.
Itchy nose.
Aha! That makes no sense.
See? She's hiding like something's
about to fall from the sky...
...but a twitchy *tail* means something's
gonna fall from the sky. Not an itchy nose.
This proves, perhaps conclusively, that...
Spike! Where are you going?
I'm trying to teach you
the value of scientific obse...
What's she doing now?
Smelling a flower.
Holy guacamole! I don't know what that means.
Probably that the flower smells good.
Wait! I'm getting something.
Ear flop... eye flutter... knee twitch.
Hold on...
You told me that's the combo
that says "Watch out for opening doors."
You really, really believe this stuff, don't you?
Here. Let me show you
there's nothing to be afraid of.
You see?
I promise you there's nothing
to fear from that... whoaaa...!
Twilight! You came to visit
my new apple cellar. How nice.
Twi? You okay? Uh, Twi?
Here. Let me help ya.
Okay.
Take this down.
Twitchy... tail.
Twitchy tail?
TWITCHY TAIL!!!
Hush, Spike! We can't let Pinkie
know we're here, remember?
Something's gonna fall! Something's gonna fall!
Run for your lives!
Ugh... Spike, honestly, you're overreact...
Hey, Applejack! Whatchu doin'?
Takin' more apples to my new apple cellar.
How about you, Pinkie? Whatchu doin'?
Oh. Letting Twilight secretly follow me
all day without me knowing.
You mean you knew all along?!
Why didn't you tell me?
Silly. That would have spoiled the secret.
Tail... still twitching?
All done. Clear skies from here on in,
as far as I can tell.
Oh no! What does that one mean?!
Dunno. Never gotten any like it before.
But whatever that shudder's about, it's a doozy!
Something you never expect
to happen is gonna happen!
And it's gonna happen... at Froggy Bottom Bog!
That's where Fluttershy's headed!
Oh no! Is it about her?
I... I'm not sure.
We better go and make sure she's okay.
Calm down, everypony. All we know right now...
...is that Pinkie Pie just got
a case of the shivers. That's all.
Hey! I thought you didn't believe in this stuff.
I don't.
I just want to be there to see the look on
Pinkie's face when we find out nothing's wrong.
Okie dokie!
Cold?
Need a jacket or something?
No, thanks. I'm fine.
So... what do you think happened to Fluttershy?
I hope nothin'.
I know, but... what do you *think* happened?
I'm tryin' not to think about it.
Me too.
But... I'm thinking about it anyway.
Like... what if... she exploded?!
Just exploded? For no reason?
Yeah! Like, boom!
-Whoa!
-I know!
What if... What if she exploded...
and then... and then exploded again?!
Can you do that? Can you explode twice?
Of course not.
But what if... she exploded...
and exploded again... and then...
Will you two stop?
She's fine. I'm sure of it.
I hope you're right, for Fluttershy's sake.
Look! There's Froggy Bottom Bog!
Fluttershy!
Fluttershy! You're okay!
Of course.
What a relief.
I'm so glad everything's all right.
Sorry. I know it's not nice to gloat, but...
AHA! I told you there was nothing
to worry about and I was right.
Pinkie Pie said whatever she was shuddering
about was a *cough* doozy. And... *cough*
And the only *cough* doozy here is how right I am.
Um... Twilight?
Pinkie's made a lot of predictions
today, but... *cough*
What is that smell?!
But what we've shown here is that
there's no point in believing... *cough*
...anything you can't see for yourself.
W-Well then, see what's b-behind you, Twilight.
I see it... but I don't believe it!
Is that a hydra?
Who cares? RUUUN!!!
Pinkie! Come on!
Oh! I'm so sorry.
Everypony up that hill!
HEEELP!!!
Coming, Spike! Hang on!
I think we're gonna make it!
But Pinkie's still shuddering!
Oh, lookie there. It stopped.
Ohhh, therrre ittt isss agggainnn!
He'll be up here in no time!
Quick! One at a time! Cross!
Uh, do you know any spell
for turning a hydra into a mouse?
-No.
-How about a squirrel?
-No!
-How about...
No small rodents of any kind!
That's too bad.
A hop, skip and a...
JUMP!
Wwwhoooa!
He's too close!
I'll distract him. You two go! Now!
Oh... What would a brave pony
like Rainbow Dash do?
CHAAARGE!!!
Tttwilight!
You have to jump!
I'll never make it!
You'll be fine!
I will not!
It's your only hooope!
You have to take a leap of faith!
No!
Oh no!
NOOO!!!
I knew you could do it, Twilight!
I don't know how it happened.
Coincidence, dumb luck or what.
But you said there'd be a doozy
here at Froggy Bottom Bog...
...and I'd say we just had
ourselves one heck of a doozy.
I mean, that hydra...
Pinkie?
That wasn't it.
Huh?
What wasn't what?
What are you talkin' about, Pink?
The hydra wasn't the doozy.
I'm still getting the shudders.
You see? There it is again.
Whatever the doozy was at Froggy Bottom Bog,
my Pinkie Sense says it still hasn't happened.
Huh... But I... WHAT?!
The hydra... wasn't the doozy?
How could it not be... the doozy?
What could be doozier than that?!
Dunno. But it just wasn't it.
I give up.
Give what up, Twi?
The fight. I can't fight it anymore.
I don't understand how, why or what...
...but Pinkie Sense somehow... makes sense.
I don't see how it does, but it just does.
Just because I don't understand
doesn't mean it's not true.
Yyyouuu mean yyyou bbbelllieve?
Yep. I guess I do.
Oh.
That was it! That's the doozy!
What?
What is?
You believing!
I never expected *that* to happen.
That was the doozy! Oh, and oh,
what a doozy of a doozy it was!
Oh, good, Spike. You're here.
Take a letter.
With pleasure, Twilight.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"I'm happy to report, that..."
Spike. What have I been saying about focus?
I know, but I... well...
What's wrong, Spike? Never thought
you'd see me with an umbrella hat on?
Not really. No.
Pinkie's tail's a-twitching. What else can I do?
"I am happy to report that I now realize..."
"...there are wonderful things
in this world you just can't explain."
"But that doesn't necessarily
make them any less true."
"It just means you have to
choose to believe in them."
"And sometimes it takes a friend
to show you the way."
HONK!
"Honk."
"Always your faithful student, Twilight Sparkle."
There it goes again.
I wonder what's gonna drop out
of the sky this time.
You never know.
Twitchy tail?
Holy guacamole!