♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(everyone snoring)
Wow!
(laughing outside)
Look at me!
Come on sleepies, wake up.
Look, pretty!
Oh boy!
(giggling)
Whoopee!
(loud giggling)
Hey there, you two.
You wanna help me build
a little ol' snow pony?
(All)
For sure! Yeah!
Uh, Truly...
U-uh, watch yourself, Galaxy.
Truly, I don't think
you understand.
North Star, honey,
you gonna play
by yourself all day
or do you wanna help us here?
(Baby Pony)
Yay! All done! It looks pretty.
North Star,
I'm worried about the snow.
It's not natural
this time of year.
I don't wanna spoil
anyone's fun but--
Well, you are spoilin' my fun,
and the babies' too!
Now if ya have ta worry,
why don't you just go
worry by yourself, hear?
C'mon ya all, let's build forts
and have a snowball fight.
(sighs)
(Sonny)
Whew! W-well
I hope your d-d-dad knows
why it's so c-c-cold
where I live, Edgar!
(Edgar)
Don't worry, Sonny.
We'll find out what's going on.
We wanna see my dad.
Why has Sonny's home
become so cold, father?
Yeah.
M-my wh-whole family is packing
to g-g-go south for the w-winter
and it's s-still s-s-summer.
Don't bother packing.
Soon, there will be no south
for your family to go to.
Soon there will be no place
for anyone, but us penguins!
The power of my icy cold stare
may be small,
but when magnified
by this machine
it creates a wind so cold
that soon the whole world
will be frozen over,
all who are unworthy of living
in such a lovely climate
will be frozen.
And I shall rule
the whole world.
As will you, Edgar,
when you become king.
No, father!
What?
I don't wanna rule the world,
And even if I did,
it wouldn't be right.
When you are king,
you may decide
what is and is not right.
But I am king now,
and what I say is law.
Is that clear?
But why should only
penguins survive?
Yeah. What's wrong
with bein' a duck?
They're weak.
(Sonny)
How?
Can they withstand the cold?
Why should w-w-we have to?
Sonny!
(sobs)
He is but
a bad influence on you.
You won't be listening
to his nonsense anymore.
Guards!
(sobbing)
How could you?
When you are king,
you'll understand these things.
(giddy laughter)
Is that the best ya all can do,
North Star, honey?
All right, baby.
Give it a good swat.
(Galaxy)
Stop this all of you.
Haven't any of you noticed
how could it's gotten?
(yawns)
All of our beautiful trees are
barren and covered with frost.
And when was the last time
anyone saw
a bird or a butterfly.
(Sea Shimmer)
Galaxy, Truly,
all of Ponyland...
(Surf Rider)
...is like freezing over.
Goodness me!
Look at the rainbow.
I dare say it is freezing too.
Looks like I was wrong.
This is a worry.
We need help.
North Star,
you better go fetch Megan,
if you can still
get over the rainbow.
I cold now, Truly.
We'll be okay real soon.
Don't you worry.
(teeth chatter)
♪ We're not gonna
freeze, no sir ♪
end up frozen ♪
♪ We're gonna hang
in there together ♪
♪ We're gonna rise
above the weather ♪
♪ We're not gonna
freeze, nuh-uh ♪
♪ That isn't the path
we've chosen ♪
♪ We're gonna leave
the cold behind us ♪
♪ No more waiting
till they find us ♪
♪ Frozen solid
like a block of ice ♪
♪ If you think
we're giving up... ♪
No dice! ♪
♪ We're not gonna
freeze, my friends ♪
♪ That won't be the way
it ends ♪
♪ We may be on the spot ♪
♪ We may shiver
quite a lot ♪
♪ But no matter what ♪
♪ We're not gonna freeze ♪
(giggling)
Heya, Megan! Boy, oh boy,
I bet you're
surprised to see me.
(laughs)
Relieved is more like it.
I've been terribly worried ever
since the rainbow froze over.
What's happened in Ponyland?
We don't know.
We hoped you could help.
Can ya make it back?
(shivering)
I-I don't know...
My wings are awfully cold.
I thought that might happen.
Wait right here.
For once,
I've got a surprise for you.
Wing warmers, huh?
Ohh! Neat!
I knitted them myself.
Great idea!
(giggles)
(shivers)
(Galaxy)
Look! Surprise made it.
Megan, thank goodness
you're here.
(Truly)
Are we glad to see you!
Surprise explained the situation
to me on the way here.
But it's more serious here
than I thought.
I don't know what we should do.
I know... We'll go North!
That's where
it's always coldest
(Truly)
Oh, yeah, right.
Just what we need...
To get colder...
Good thinking.
Don't you see?
North is where
we'll probably
find the source
of this cold wave.
She's right.
The cold has to come
from somewhere
and it normally
comes from North.
(North Star)
Come, this way is north.
Tally-ho!
(Surprise)
Okay. So we went North.
Now, anybody got a clue
as to what we're looking for?
We just have to be patient.
Keep at it, Surprise.
(shivers)
But I'm so cold.
Galaxy, get a load of this!
It's Surf Rider and Sea Shimmer.
(Galaxy)
Yes!
And I think they're trying
to lead us somewhere.
Follow me everybody.
This way.
(North Star)
Thank you, Sea Shimmer.
You too, Surf Rider.
We'll have to go the rest
of the way on our own.
The ice is too thick
for you to swim under.
Surprise and I
shall fly overhead
and guide the rest of you
through these maze, agreed?
(all gasp)
So sorry, Megan.
I suppose it's just
a bit too cold.
Nice try you two.
But I think we'll have to
rely on Galaxy's intuition.
Come on.
(Galaxy)
Another dead end.
I am sorry, Megan.
I feel so lost.
(Megan)
Welcome to the club.
We'll never get outta here.
(Surprise)
I don't believe this.
Megan, Galaxy, giving up?!
Well, not me.
This way.
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
I suppose we've really nothing
to lose by following her, what?
(gasps)
(Galaxy)
Oh, my stars! Look!
An abominable snowman!
(growls)
This is a surprise I don't like.