♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Nearly all the little ponies
and their friends
have been captured, master.
Nearly all
is not good enough, Bray.
I want
every inhabitant of Ponyland
in the dungeons by nightfall.
I am especially interested
in the humans,
since they,
like the Troggles, have hands.
We need more slaves
with hands, Bray.
(gulps)
Hands that can serve us.
NOW GO!
The baby ponies
are safe with the Moochick.
His magic will protect them.
The bad news, Megan,
is all the Seaponies
except Surf Rider and Water Lily
have been captured.
As far as I can ascertain,
Forget-Me-Not and I,
are the only two Flutter Ponies
that escaped.
Lots of Bushwoolies
captured too.
(All)
Yeah, yeah, lots, yeah.
(tremor)
Here you are!
Grundles looked all over,
I mean all under for you.
Are you all the
Grundles that are left?
'fraid so.
All others captured.
What are we gonna do?
How are we gonna stop Grogar?
Oh, cheer up everybody.
As long as we're free,
there's still a chance.
It may look
pretty dark right now,
but believe me,
the morning is gonna come.
Tell us what to do first, Megan.
Well, the first thing to do
is figure out a way
to break into the city
and rescue everyone.
Any ideas?
Grundles can dig the way in.
Yeah, great idea!
Let's do it!
(All)
Yeah. Yeah. Great idea.
Are we there yet?
Uh-oh!
(panting)
Took wrong turn.
Bushwoolies have plan too.
(All)
Yeah. Yeah. We have a plan.
Bushwoolies sneaking
out tumbleweeds.
(All)
Tumbleweeds, tumbleweeds,
yeah, yeah, great idea.
Charge!
(All)
Yeah, yeah, charge. Yeah.
Yeah, charge, charge,
yeah, charge.
Look! Tumbleweeds!
They are great
for target practice.
Retreat!
Troggles don't like tumbleweeds.
We need a plan.
I've got an idea.
Maybe one of us can sneak in
where a lot of us can't.
Good idea.
Lofty and I will try it
before it gets light.
Be careful, Megan.
Don't worry, we will.
Over there, Lofty.
Well, we're inside.
Now all we have to do
is find them.
That's it.
Now let's push it
out of the wall.
Looks spooky.
I just know it leads to freedom.
Galaxy, Heart Throb,
and I will explore it.
The rest of you, stay here.
Oh, this is so exciting!
Oh!
What a marvelous old antique!
I think it's more than
just an antique, Heart Throb.
I sense power in it.
Umm--do you suppose
it's the way out?
Only one way to learn, come on.
Look, there they are.
(Heart Throb)
Megan!
Oh, I must look a fright.
Do you have any idea
what a dungeon
can do to your hair?
Not now, Heart Throb.
Get the others
and we'll lead you to the gates.
Gee, I hope
Megan and Lofty are all right.
Say no more.
I'll reconnoiter and ascertain
what's transpiring.
Huh?
I meant I will perform
a covert surveillance
and report back posthaste.
Megan's come to show us
the way out.
Hurry!
The gate is not far from here.
If we time it right,
we can get out
when they change guards.
There they are.
Oh! No!
(Heart Throb)
I think we're really
going to make it,
I really do--
then again I could be wrong.
Capture them now!
You better make some bubbles,
quick, quick, quick.
Gusty, you blow them
on the Troggles.
Come on right now.
Okay. But I didn't
know this was a party.
I must get Grogar.
Only he can stop them.
Master, they're escaping.
The ponies and their friends
are escaping.
We have to stop those sentries
or we'll be back
in the dungeon.
Of course, we'll stop them.
Draw near!
I'll take that.
Come on, everybody, push!
It's working.
Give it all you've got.
(All scream)
(cackles)
I've got to return
and alert the others.
Have the Troggles return
them to the dungeon.
Yes, master.
And Bray, if it happens again,
you shall join them!
And then Grogar immobilized
them all with his magic.
That means Megan
is a prisoner now too.
What are we gonna do, Danny?
I don't know.
But we got to do something soon
or Grogar will rule Ponyland.