♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Yay...I'm first...I win!
You always win.
What we play now?
Not play.
Time for practice to be
the famousest famous Ballerina.
(singing)
Ra...ra...ra...ra
Whoa! Ow!
Okay, maybe play now.
Okay, what game?
Aa...ba...
Checkers!
Baby Lofty, go get
checkers, okay?
Me try.
Whoa!
(gasps)
I'm never gonna fly good.
Didn't wanna play
checkers anyway.
Yes, checkers!
Aaa...
Baby Ribbon, get up, okay?
Wink up there.
Hmmm...okay.
Get checkers!
No! I'm not all here.
Checkers is all there.
I'm not all here.
We thought we heard a crash.
Is everybody okay?
What's going on?
Mama!
Where are you?
Some of me up here.
Help!
Thanks, Mommy.
Now hold still.
Some little ponies look
a little bored to me.
Buttons, would you play
a game with us?
Please!
(All) Play with us, please!
Why don't you play
by yourselves today?
How does a game of
make-believe sound?
(All) Ugh!
Make-believe is a great game.
You don't need anyone
else to play with you.
All you need is
your imagination.
I-Imagination?
(giggles)
Sure.
Buttons and I will
get you started.
But then the rest is up to you.
Let's go!
All right everyone.
Look at the hill.
Something special will be
coming over at any second.
Just grass there.
Ribbon and I'll send our very
favorite old toy over the hill.
Oh, it's a wonderful red ball
that can be anything
you want it to be.
(both gasp)
Anything? In the whole world?
Anything.
It's all up to you.
This gonna be fun.
What ball can it be?
Maybe...maybe...
(ball bouncing)
Who are you?
Your very own special
playmate, Baby Tiddlywinks.
And I know a place filled with
the best toys and games
in the whole world.
Oh! Boy!
Just close your eyes, we'll
be there in a flash.
Wow! Look at all the toys.
In this place, there's nothing
to do but play all day.
What's this?
It's a ping-pong table,
made especially for you.
Get ready.
(Baby Tiddlywinks)
Wanna play more.
Okay, come on.
This is the best game ever.
Look!
(Baby Tiddlywinks)
Wow!
Looks hard.
Every room has a
different surprise.
And you have to find
your way through.
- Try it.
- Okay
I'll see you at the other end.
Oh-oho!
(merriment)
Weeee!
(gasps)
(balloons burst)
Which way I go?
Go...this way.
(merriment)
This is fun!
he-he-hey!
I told you, you could do it.
Baby Tiddlywinks likes ball.
Ha ha, shucks.
I'm turning red.
(laughs)
It will be just like that.
Will be just like what?
I was just thinking what red
ball would be like to play with.
Oh, boy!
Red ball is gonna
play with me too.
Yes.
What we do?
I'm gonna teach you how to be
a great flier, Baby Lofty.
Follow me.
Wow. Flying!
Don't be afraid, Baby Lofty.
The sky is yours.
(laughter and merriment)
Come on, let's take a trip.
(sneezes)
There's more.
Pretty!
So pretty!
I couldn't have
brought you here,
if you weren't such a
good flier already.
Really?
Sure.
And I'm not the only one.
All of Ponyland is
waiting to honor you.
(laughter and merriment)
And this is that.
Go ahead.
They're all waiting for you.
(cheer and applause)
On behalf of all the little
ponies in Ponyland,
I'd like to honor you
with this medal
for being the greatest
flying pony of all time.
(cheering)
Aw, gee.
Ball helped.
(cheering)
Thank you ball.
Flying is good for you,
but guess what I'm gonna do?
♪
(cheer and applause)
(cheer and applause continue)
Oh...
Oh, what are you gonna
do, Baby Ribbon?
I'm not sure.
Wow.
Wow!
What are you?
I'm your good luck charm.
Try winking out now.
Okay, here goes.
Wow! I did it.
Better try again.
You see, Baby Ribbon, you
can wink in and out.
Yeah!
Now, give it a real test.
Watch this.
(chuckles)
Yay!
Did it!
Welcome to Baby Ribbon
School of Winking.
(cheering)
It's good. Bye.
What Baby Ribbon means is that
you're now all expert winkers.
And now that you've graduated,
she's going to wink herself
to a tropical vacation.
Have a good time, Baby Ribbon.
Thanks ball.
So long!
(cheer and applauds)
That was fun.
Where ball?
Maybe, it wasn't any ball.
Maybe, it was imagination.
Imagination?
Yeah.
Baby imagine anything.
♪ Imagining is fun ♪
♪ A lovely way to
pass the time ♪
♪ Imagining is fun ♪
♪ I love it so pretending ♪
♪ I'm a beautiful ballerina ♪
♪ Or a nifty flying ace ♪
♪ I'd live in a
fantasy toyland ♪
♪ I would wink through
time and space ♪
♪ Imagining is fun ♪
♪ The nicest work
we've ever done ♪
♪ We know it's only
make-believe ♪
♪ As real as it may seem ♪
♪ But imagining
is so much fun ♪
♪ It makes your
life a dream ♪
♪ Yes imagining,
is so much fun ♪
♪ It makes your
life a dream ♪
(Ribbon)
Naptime everyone, naptime.
So, did you have fun
playing by yourselves?
(All chuckle)
Yeah.
(chuckles)
I guess you did.
Now, it's time for your nap.
- Okay.
- See you later. Bye, bye. Bye.
They really enjoyed themselves.
What...what happened
to the red ball?
I didn't see it
with the baby ponies,
and I know
we sent it over the hill.
Ribbon, look!
(laughter)