♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Gee Sweet Stuff,
I saw Mimic going this way.
She should be...
(gasps)
There she is!
Mimic! Mimic!
Where'd she go?
Mimic, What's the matter?
I...I don't know...
Sweet Stuff,
what are we going to do?
Mimic's so weak, it's scary!
When North Star brings Megan,
she'll help Mimic get well.
There they are.
Sweet Stuff, Surprise,
How's Mimic?
Let's hurry inside.
Aww, is that
more comfortable Mimic?
Thank you, Cupcake.
Hello, Mimic
how are you feeling?
(Spike)
The twinkle is gone
from her eys.
She's lost her appetite.
She hasn't eaten
anything in three days.
No cough, no fever,
her tongue isn't coated,
and her throat isn't red,
she's awfully pale.
But I don't know what's wrong?
Neither do we.
It's not like any illness
we've ever had.
Could...could it be magic?
Magic, that's it!
When magic's involved,
the Moochick is the one to see.
I'll take you to him, Megan.
Let's go.
Just a minute, Megan,
I'm coming with you.
- Me too.
- We'll all go with you, Megan.
I'm coming too.
Hop on Spike.
We'll be back soon Mimic.
Hold on!
Hurry back!
And good luck.
(wolves howling)
(howling continues)
There, all safe and sound.
Gee Thanks.
(wolves howling and barking)
Wolves!
Run for the Moochick's cottage.
I've done it, Habbit.
Help! Open up!
Whoever you are,
go away, go away.
I'm busy.
(wolves howling and barking)
(gasps)
Nduh! No.
I'm sorry.
But this is an emergency.
Wolves were after us.
(giggles)
Oh! Ha, ha, hah.
No, no, no, no, no!
That was my wolf box.
(barking sound from the box)
Oh! But it was supposed
to scare you away, oh!
Ummm...Mr. Moochick,
Mimic is sick
and we think it's due to magic.
Uh-ah, what?
She's lost her twinkle.
Can ya help her?
Hmmm...
Well, I'm sure I have something
about sick unicorns
in a book somewhere.
(snaps)
Aha! Yes this book
is the very one.
"Pony Legends and History."
(clear throat)
"The Legend of
the Four Golden Horseshoes."
Yes, of course!
Ah! Mimic is descended
from this unicorn.
"Long ago, in the land of
Argyte,
four horseshoes were made
of mystical starlight."
Yes, oh.
"They were placed on the
hooves of this special unicorn.
Now, each shoe gave her
a magical power."
My, my, my!
"The first showed the future,
"the second had
the power of blazing light,
"the third made
another's thoughts
"sound clear and loud,
and the fourth let its wearer
float like a cloud."
(neighs)
"Deep in dream valley,
the wind left her at dawn
And there she did stay,
for her horseshoes were gone."
That's all fascinating,
Mr. Moochick.
But what does it have to do
with Mimic's illness?
Well, my, my.
Mimic is a direct descendent
of that unicorn.
And the magic of the shoes
still flows in her veins.
Over the years,
the Golden Horseshoes
have been carried
farther and farther apart.
And because of that,
their magic is weakening.
That's why Mimic
is getting weaker.
Where do we find the Horseshoes?
In the Land of Screera.
It's said that the Scree gaze
upon one to see what will be.
Okay, we're going to Screera.
Now, while you hunt for
the Horseshoes,
Habbit and I will
look after poor Mimic.
Won't we Habbit?
Here child.
This might prove
of better use to you than me.
Oh now! Dear, dear, dear...
Well, let's see.
I was about to turn
yellow into blue, uh, I think.
Oh! Of course, poor Mimic!
Come along, Habbit!
What are you wasting time for?
♪ All through the night,
although it's frightening ♪
♪ Even though
there's lightning ♪
♪ We'll keep pressing forward ♪
♪ All through the night,
although it's scary ♪
♪ Though it may get hairy ♪
♪ We'll keep moving toward
our final destination ♪
(Spike)
♪ And furthermore, me ♪
♪ And all the rest of us ♪
♪ We'll never let out fears
get the best of us ♪
♪ We'll save the day
by conquering our fright ♪
♪ We'll keep on being brave ♪
♪ All through the night ♪
(Spike)
(North star)
It's over there! That's Screera.
If this is Screera, North Star,
where are the Scree?
They're all around us.
(cackles)
I'd bet five-to-one
you'd come back, North Star.
I want you all
to meet Fleetfoot,
leader of the Scree.
And watcher
of the Crescent of Visions.
That was how I could
predict North Star's return.
Isn't that cheating?
Screes only bet on sure things.
But the Crescent of Visions did
not show why you returned.
It's like this...
You see, Mimic,
one of the ponies...
The Crescent fell from the sky,
it was a gift to the Scree.
We cannot part with it.
That's the horseshoe,
but what can we do?
Shhh...I have an idea.
Fleetfoot, I challenge
you to a race.
The winner gets the Crescent.
On one condition!
If you lose, you become
my servant forever!
Done.
Oh, poor Wind Whistler,
she looks so embarrassed.
- Come on! Wind Whistler!
- You can do it!
(All cheer)
Oh, no!
Oh! Wind Whistler.
(laughs)
The Crescent never lies.
It foretold
that Fleetfoot would win.
(cackles)
Of course, we Scree,
only bet on sure things.
Silly ponies!
(both laugh)
So that's what's going on.
But they won't get
away with it.
(wolves howling)
Wolves scream...
My head's goin' in!
(howling continues)
Megan,
what are you doing?
They cheated.
They knew Fleetfoot would win.
And we need it for Mimic's sake.
I say...
These ninnies don't play fair.
It's worth a try.
Horseshoe of Visions,
where is the Horseshoe of Light?
That's Blarkland!
I've been there.
Great! Show us the way.
So you want the Horseshoe
to save your friend, correct?
We Blarks collect, keep,
and trade junk and riddles.
You have no junk.
So, tell me a riddle
I don't know,
and the Horseshoe is yours.
Thank you.
That's very generous.
Uh...why did the boy threw
the alarm clock out the window?
Because he wanted
to see time fly.
Tell me one I don't know!
I have a riddle.
What walks on four legs
in the morning,
two at mid day,
and three at sunset?
Uh...a three-toed bullfrog?
No...uh,
a dragon with gooseflesh?
Um-uh, a gyrating galumpadillo?
I guess not...
I give up!
What?!
Humans, like Megan.
They crawl as babies,
they walk as adults,
and they use a cane
for a third foot
when they grow very old.
(laughs)
Very good!
Cracker, take them
to the Horseshoe.
It's here, umm...
somewhere.
We'll never find it in all this.
Everyone listen!
This horseshoe
has the power of light,
so that's what we look for.
You mean like
the one by Cracker's foot?
I'll get it out!
Uh-oh!
Look out!
You saved Cracker.
So I order a hole to be dug
to the Goblin tunnels.
There you will find
another Horseshoe,
stolen a long time ago
from the Blarks.
Thank you for your help.
No problem.
You are all the Blarks' friends.
Megan, look!
The Horseshoe is growing
brighter.
We must be nearing
the third one.
Now, what have we here?
Won't Ma be surprised?
(murmuring)