♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(laugh)
Everyone run for it!
(grunt and groan)
You pushed me bagger.
No, you pushed me smacker.
You both pushed me,
and now you're stinking mean.
Oh! Dear, Ma...
(All panting)
Everyone hide.
Quickly!
Paradise! The Horseshoe's
illumination will reveal
our place of concealment
to the goblins.
Perhaps you can wish it off?
All Little Ponies,
we know you're here.
Yeah. We can read your minds.
You don't like us,
you think we're ugly and mean.
They're right.
(All laugh)
Oh My!
The goblins just caught
North Star and Spike,
They seem to intuit their
precise locations.
- What?
- They know where they were.
I'm reading two more minds
right over here.
Ahhhh!
Ma is gonna be
so proud of me.
I got two and you guys
only got one.
And that's all there is.
(laughs)
I thought there was more?
Dummy, we'd read their minds
if there was.
Let's go show Ma...
If the goblins found everyone
by reading their minds,
why didn't they know
we were here?
Perhaps it's the Horseshoes,
they might cancel out
the telepathic power
of the Goblin's Horseshoe.
Then we can follow them
secretly.
Come on!
(struggling)
That's the 306th time
I won today.
(laughs)
Look what we got Ma...
I got two
and they only got one.
So? Wanna make something of it?
Both of you is thinkin' worser.
Alright, you two's been
asking for it.
Boys!
I like all your presents.
They'll make good little slaves,
and we need slaves.
But what would please
me and your Pa most
would be if you would
STOP FIGHTING!
- Yes Ma.
- Sorry Ma.
It won't happen again Ma.
We'll be good.
Why can't the three of you
learn to get along?
(Crying)
♪ We're friendly
with the beasts... ♪
with the snakes... ♪
♪ So can't you three be
friendly too? ♪
♪ For heaven's sakes ♪
♪ We're chummy
with the wolves... ♪
♪ We're cordial
to the bees... ♪
♪ Why can't you three play
nicely too? ♪
♪ For Mama please? ♪
It's not my fault.
Don't look at me.
They're the ones who start.
(both)
Nuh-uh!
♪ Enough. Enough. ♪
♪ No more rough stuff. ♪
♪ You'll break
your old Ma's heart ♪
♪ We're friendly
with the beasts... ♪
♪ So someone tell me why? ♪
♪ You little beasts
must fight and scream ♪
♪ And make your
old Ma cry? ♪
(Crying)
I'm Sorry.
I'm Sorrier.
I'm sorriest of all.
No you're not.
Excuse me!
Your sons fight because
the magic Horseshoe you wear
lets them read
each others minds.
If you free us, we will take the
Horseshoe far away from here.
Nonsense!
Goblins don't give things away.
Boys, Pa and I are going in
the back to count our treasures.
We don't want any more arguing,
you hear?
Yes Ma.
I wonder how Mimic is?
It doesn't look like
we could help her much now.
I've done all that
I can for her.
I'm afraid it's not much,
the only thing that can help
her now is the Horseshoes magic.
Well why can't you make
horseshoes for her?
I just might be able to,
but it would take too long
to return to my workshop.
I'll take you, I'll take you!
That's not problem.
It's no problem at all.
If any of us can get you there
in time, it's me.
I can get ya home in a wink.
I'm the fastest flyer here.
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
Then, what are we waiting for?
(snoring)
It's Paradise and Wind Whistler.
Hey, whatÂ's the big Idea?
Who do you think
you're hitting?
Oh boy, are we glad to see you.
The Slaves are escaping!
(fighting loudly)
See what your fighting has done?
Keep going, Lofty.
I'll catch up.
I've been robbed!
Ma we're sorry.
We'll get it back.
(All)
Oh yeah, Ma, sure we will!
I promise, I promise!
And I am sorry.
I was hittin' you guys.
Yeah, I'm sorry,
I punched you in the face.
Well, I'm sorry I was, you know,
jumping up and down
on your legs.
Oh!
Forget the Horseshoe boys.
We've got something better.
We got our family spirit back.
Bat's Wings... Tail of Newt...
(loud explosion)
Oh! Oh!
The magic involved is just
too strong for me to control.
(Spike sighs)
Now where do we go?
According to the power
of this Horseshoe,
the last one is near
but up high.
Look up there
on that high peek.
I've been there,
it's the home of
the green mountain elves.
It's awfully high up.
Do you think we can make it?
The air's thin up there,
but breathable.
Let's go!
I-I hope the others can make it,
it's a long way down.
(gasping for air)
Northstar. Wind whistler.
Help!
Air is too thin...
I can't breathe...
Come on, we'll make it together.
It doesn't look friendly.
It was built to be deceiving.
Warm welcome Lofty to you
and your friends.
I am Cara, keeper of the gate
to the Mountain Elf Kingdom.
What quest brings you here?
We're looking for
a magic Horseshoe,
that can take you
wherever you wish.
We need it to save
our friend's life!
I'm sorry.
It is not within my power
to give it to you.
It belongs to the child,
Princess Mave.
And according to Elven Laws,
no one may take anything
from a child,
unless the child
surrenders it willingly.
May we ask Mave
for the Horseshoe?
Yes. I'll take you to her.
(giggling)
Oh!
Come to play with Mave?
No, Mave.
This is Megan,
she has a favor to ask of you.
Ask.
A unicorn is very sick,
your magic Horseshoe
is needed to cure her.
Will you give it to us?
No.
Horseshoe Mave's!
Fun to play with.
Watch!
Hey, wait...help!
(All gasp)
See?
Horseshoe make fun for Mave
all day.
Now we go under the ocean
for more fun.
Uhh...let's not.
We've seen why you
want the Horseshoe.
Now let's go to Dream Valley
so you can see
why we need the Horseshoe.
Okay! Dream Valley.
(starts sobbing)
Here. Pony needs Horseshoe
more than Mave.
Thank you! Thank You!
Megan? Megan!
We have all the Horseshoes.
Give them to me, quickly.
(gasps)
Mimic, are you better?
All better. Thank you all.
(cheers)
(Mave sighs with relief)
We did it!