♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
I say it's a lovely day
for exploring, eh, Lofty?
If you happen to
like exploring solid rock.
Oh, don't be so dreary!
No one's ever been here before.
We are sure to find something
terribly exciting.
Like that!
(mysterious music)
It says, "keep out."
Well, they couldn't mean us,
Paradise.
Where could it lead, I wonder?
Wait!
What if there's something
dangerous behind that door?
Think, North Star,
before you do anything rash.
Very well, very well!
Oh, drat! Let's have a
go at it, shall we?
North Star, please!
This could be the Golden Door!
A long long time ago,
the most fearsome creature
ever known terrorized Ponyland.
So, a sorcerer forged
the Golden Door.
A gateway to
the Land of Legends.
A mysterious door of realm.
And it was
through that golden door
that the beast was pushed
into the land of legends.
As long as no one passes
through the door,
the beast will remain there.
So reign in that curiosity
of yours North Star.
And stay away from that door!
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I've had enough
exploring for one day.
A brightfully silly story.
I fancy she simply made it up.
North Star!
How could anything dangerous
be behind such a lovely door?
In any event, Paradise
didn't say not to open it.
She merely said not to pass
through it.
North Star, don't!
Oh, how dreary!
Well, that certainly
was a disappointment.
Ohh!
Stand and deliver!
Oh, no!
Hold steeds.
What manner of pony are these?
Aye, who'd be your master?
Does he have any money?
We...we have
no master or money.
No money?
(All cry)
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Hood, Robin Hood.
And these are my..eh..huh,
merry men.
Merry men?
We are North Star and Lofty.
Welcome to Ponyland!
Ponyland, eh?
Jolly good!
They have a holiday here,
it would make my Merry Men,
a bit more merry.
I say everyone-
come out
and have a look.
Ahhh!
This is nice.
There's quite a few of you.
You are not all Merry Men.
(Laughs)
No, no.
We're legends and myths.
There's Paul Bunyan
and Big, his ox.
And Aladdin and his lamp.
And Chaharazad.
And there's Hercules.
Uh..Haa! Uhh!
It's coming!
(aligatorsaur roar)
(All gasp)
It's coming after us!
Close it!
Hurry!
Shut the door!
(All sigh)
I say,
what was all that about?
No...no, it's too horrible.
That creature
Paradise mentioned.
Could that be
what they're so afraid of,
that they all have
come to Ponyland?
Quite.
Hmm, I guess
we should let everyone know.
(tremoring)
Ohhh...
Oh darling, Paradise!
Such a lovely bouquet.
I would give
it to my true love,
but, where is he?
Will he never come
into my life?
Oh, Heart Throb, don't be
discouraged.
Your true love will show up.
He's out there,
I'm sure of it.
♪ There's a prince
in your future somewhere ♪
♪ Your Sir Lancelot
is waiting 'round the bend ♪
♪ Now you may be minus ♪
♪ A royal highness ♪
♪ But your Romeo will
show up in the end ♪
♪ But when will he arrive? ♪
♪ How long must I wait? ♪
♪ I know it will be soon ♪
♪ But let's leave the date
to fate ♪
♪ There's a prince in your
future Heart Throb ♪
♪ And he'll be exactly who
you're dreaming of ♪
♪ Handsome and disarming ♪
♪ A regular prince
charming ♪
♪ When he comes you'll know
at once it's love ♪
♪ Yes, when he comes ♪
♪ you'll know
at once it's love ♪
You called?
My darling! Where have
you been all my life?
(Shy)
Oh! Nowhere special, heh.
Ah, who...who are you?
Well, Prince Charming of course.
And I've been searching
my whole life through
for you, my sweet.
You have?
Promise me
we'll be together always?
Darling, you needn't even ask.
Huh?
Dearest!
Oh, how I've longed
to find one so fair as you.
But, but what about Heart Throb?
Forget the past!
Think only of the present.
Us, together.
Now and always.
Ohh, my one true love.
Oh, my sweet!
How can you pass me by?
True Heart, it's you I love!
Darling, Don't go.
I've got a funny
feeling about this.
(groaning)
Rrrraaaahhh!
There! I just love a
tidy place, don't you?
Oh, yes, Hercules,
so do we!
I haven't had so much fun
since I cleaned
the Agean's stables
Filthy dirt. filthy,
filthy, filthy...
Just like
a willow in the breeze.
(All giggle)
That's it my little ones.
And that's how we do the dance
of the seven waves.
Gee-Wiz!
It's a wonderful day
for a picnic, Lickety-Split.
It truly is.
Those clouds have me worried
Buttons--
'Cause it looks like
it's gonna rain, and I might
What's that?
It's a lamp that
Aladdin fellow traded to me.
It should clean right up.
I think he tricked you,
Buttons,
there's no place
to put a light bulb.
(both gasp in amazement)
I am the Genie of the Lamp
and I'm obliged to grant
you three wishes.
May I take your order, please?
You go first, Lickety-Split.
I wish the weather was perfect.
Perfect! Hmm..
Could you be more specific?
Temperature?
Well...
Eighty two, sixty four,
a hundred and seventy nine?
Uh, eighty two?
Relative humidity?
C'mon c'mon! What'll it be?
Five percent, ten, ninety?
Whub-ah,
I haven't thought of it.
And I'll also need to know
the prevailing wind speed
and the percentage of
the color orange in the sunset.
Look all I want
is a perfect day,
So what's so difficult
about that?
And what about the sky?
You have your cerulean blue,
your robin's egg blue,
your royal blue or
blueberry blue, cobalt blue?
(Lofty)
Well, North Star,
I hope you're satisfied
opening that door.
We're practically being crowded
out of the estate
by uninvited guests.
Shame on you!
Come, come, Lofty!
'Tisn't that bad.
No?
What about the legend?
If anyone passes
through that door?
Everyone came through the
door already.
And we shut it behind us,
there was no monster.
Monster?
(panicked shouts)
We don't
have to worry.
Oh?
Then why are they so nervous?
(Heart Throb)
Prince Charming, darling?
How romantic?
(roars)