( theme music playing )
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will today's
adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander,
hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide? ♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there ♪
♪ Right by your side. ♪
( giggling )
Where's Surprise?
We don't want to lose her.
( giggling )
Boo!
- ( Baby Cuddles squealing )
- I got ya! Ooh!
Surprise
frightened me!
Sorry, Baby Cuddles.
Knock off
the surprises,
Surprise.
We have to get
to Flutter Valley.
And we're already late
for the celebration...
I think.
Aren't we?
It's Cupcake's fault.
Took her forever to bake
that cake.
Perfection is not something
to be rushed, Gusty.
Me never been
to Flutter Valley.
You'll love it,
Baby Cuddles.
It's the most beautiful place
in all of Ponyland.
( gurgling )
Hydia:
The most beautiful
place, indeed!
I hate Flutter Valley!
( squeaking )
We hate it too, Mama--
I mean, Hydia.
And we hate
the Flutter Ponies too,
don't we, Hydia?
I want to ruin
the Flutter Ponies'
big deal celebration.
I want to make them pay
for stopping the Smooze.
( slurps )
Can't we get even
with the little ponies too?
They helped.
I have an idea,
Hydia--
whoa, oh-hh!
Let's ruin
the Flutter Ponies'
celebration.
I just said that,
you numbskull!
Now listen,
girls.
We're gonna
start by stopping
those little ponies
from getting
to that celebration.
- Got it?
- Got it.
- Then do it!
- Reeka: How?
- Draggle: Yeah, how?
- Ow!
Hydia:
You ask me how?
You're witches,
that's how!
We're going, Hydia.
We're leaving right now.
We're gone.
Bye!
( creaking )
Oh-hh, kids!
What is it with
them today?
They don't listen,
they don't think,
they have no idea
what they're doing.
Whoa!
( grunting )
See you later,
Hydia. Bye.
We'll get those ponies.
Don't worry.
Oh, what am I gonna do
with them?
- There they are.
- Yeah, let's get 'em.
And how, sister dear,
do you plan to do that?
Go down there
and grab them,
that's how.
Boy, you really
are dumb, Draggle.
There are too many
just to grab.
We've gotta be clever.
We've got to outsmart 'em.
You mean
we have to get help?
Follow me.
I have an idea.
Ugh!
( laughs )
Sorry, Reeka, dear.
( Draggle laughing )
It's gotta be
in here somewhere.
( muttering )
Here it is-- lasso.
I knew it.
Hold this.
( chanting )
"Cluerman, norkferm,
dand-evil, ferderkel"!
- You did it!
- Well, of course I did.
Get ready.
Here they come.
We should be getting close
to Flutter Valley.
Oh, I hope we don't
miss the celebration.
You're gonna miss
more than that!
Oh! Help!
It's the witches
from the Volcano of Gloom!
( cackles )
Run, Spike!
Get help!
Not so fast,
"dragon breath."
( gurgling )
Oh, my little girls!
Look what they've done.
It's wonderful!
I'm so proud of them!
I'm so proud!
I wonder where
the little ponies are.
They're never late.
Oh, I hope
nothing bad happened.
What could happen?
It's a beautiful day,
the sun is shining,
life is wonderful!
Down there!
The witches have
the little ponies.
Switch to utter flutter.
Come on, little ponies.
Move it.
( gasps )
It's the Flutter Ponies!
Draggle:
I think we're in
big trouble.
( sneezes )
This way.
( sneezing )
Wha-what are we
going to tell Hydia?
Nothing.
She'll never know.
What if she's watching us
in the viewing pool?
Draggle,
get down here.
What if
she finds out
we failed?
We haven't failed.
Not yet.
We're going
to Flutter Valley.
Follow me!
Agh! Ow!
What are you
tryin' to do?
Hey, watch it!
- Ow!
- Ooh!
( grunting )
The sun is the lamp
that lights our valley.
It gives color to our
fields and flowers,
and spreads
beauty and love
with its warmth.
Ugh! That's
the worst thing
I ever heard, Ugh!
Yeah, who'd
want to live
where it's always
warm and beautiful?
Well, it won't be warm
and beautiful for long.
Let's see what we
can do about it.
Can I do it
this time, Reeka?
You always do it. Please?
Well, all right.
But you
better come up
with something good!
- Here!
- Uh-- ooh! Oh!
( whines )
Thank you.
As Rosedust,
Queen of the Flutter Ponies,
I proclaim this day,
Sun Tuesday.
Let the celebration
begin!
♪ From the sun
comes light ♪
comes power ♪
♪ It's the sun
up high in the sky, ♪
♪ That makes
the flowers flower ♪
♪ From the sun
comes warmth, ♪
comes daytime ♪
♪ It's the sun
and it's light,
gleaming bright ♪
♪ That brings the fruit
at May time ♪
♪ Winter, summer ♪
♪ Spring and fall ♪
♪ The sun shines
through it all ♪
♪ From the sun
comes warmth ♪
comes daytime ♪
♪ Here's to the sun
up above! ♪
♪ From the sun... ♪
♪ From
the sun... ♪
♪ From the sun... ♪
♪ Comes love. ♪
Reeka:
Will you hurry up?
I can't find
anything.
Do something simple,
like a landslide.
We'll bury 'em.
Good idea!
"Land, Land grant...
Landlord... Land mine..."
I found it!
Then make it!
We made some woolie pies
for you, Rosedust.
We hope you like 'em.
Yeah, we really do.
Yeah,
please like 'em.
And we brought you
some bush melons too.
- Yeah, bush melons.
- Ooh, they're good.
I'm sure
we'll like them,
Bushwoolies.
Thank you very much.
And here's
a chocolate cake,
Rosedust.
Well, it was
a chocolate cake...
- ( rumbling )
- What is it?
Thunder? Drums?
Heavy dancing?
Spike:
It's a landslide!
( all yelling )
Landslide, landslide!
Run, my little ponies!
Fly away,
my little flutter ponies!
Hide, Bushwoolies,
hide!
The sun stone's
going to fall!
Oh, there must be
something we can do.
Better hurry!
( theme music playing )