♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Don't hold me so tight,
you're choking me.
Sorry. Bushwoolie
not want to fall.
Just tell me which way to go.
That way. Uh-oh!
Oh!
Oh no!
You will tell me
how to drain the magic
in the wands for my own use.
Don't be ridiculous.
That could destroy
all of Ponyland.
So be it. Take them
to the lava pits.
(all gasp)
(both gasp)
Who are you?
I am Princess Tiffany,
a keeper of the magic wands.
At least, I was.
You're one of the legendary
Princess Ponies?
Yes. And we need your help.
Our magic wands were stolen.
Wait. You'd better tell this
to Megan. Come on.
(lava bubbling)
They can't throw us
into a lava pit.
It would ruin my complexion.
Let's play bounce, now.
Oh, boy, play bounce!
-Yeah, bounce. -Play now.
-Okay, bounce!
(bouncing)
(grunting)
Now's our chance. Let's go!
No you don't!
-That was fun. -Do it again.
-Yeah. Yeah. -Yeah!
Quiet!
Huh...we've got to rescue
the Princess Ponies.
-Yeah.
-Rescue ponies.
-Yeah, sounds like fun.
- Yeah, fun.
Uh-oh!
Looks like we're the ones
who need rescuing.
You have a choice ponies--
jump, or be pushed.
(evil laugh)
(loud shaking)
(grunting)
(grunting continues)
All right. Everyone, run.
Don't mess with me.
I...I'm warning you.
Okay.
You asked for it.
Oh! He breathes flame.
He must be
one of the Lava Demons,
our hereditary enemies.
Uh-oh! I think
I just made a tactical error.
Hey! Wait a minute.
I'm a dragon, not a demon.
There's a big difference.
Would you be willing
to undergo a test to prove
you're not a Lava Demon?
Sure. You bet.
Uh, it won't hurt, will it?
Hey!
(teeth chatter)
It's true, you are not a demon.
They can't stand our touch
anymore than we can stand
theirs.
Listen, we need your help.
We've got to rescue the
Princess Ponies from...Lavan.
Lavan has captured
the Princess Pony?
This is bad, very bad.
I will help you.
Come, there is no time to waste.
Oh, boy, are we lucky.
Paradise! You're back.
But who is this?
Megan, may I present
Princess Tiffany,
one of the keepers
of the magic wands.
Greetings your
majesty, I'm Megan.
Do you know what's causing
all these strange happenings?
It's a long terrible story.
And I'm so glad you asked.
It all started
when we lost the magic wands.
This is just awful,
all this mud.
Oh, it's not so bad.
♪ Keep on slogging
through the muck ♪
♪ Even though
it's dark and yucky ♪
♪ Keep on dragging
through the mud ♪
♪ Even though it's
dank and cruddy ♪
♪ Maybe at the tunnel's end
there will be a light ♪
♪ We might even find
our magic wands ♪
♪ That's right, we might ♪
♪ Keep on slogging
through the muck ♪
♪ Even though it's
dark and yucky ♪
♪ Keep on marching
to the fray ♪
♪ Maybe we can
save the day ♪
♪ Though it's hard on us, ♪
♪ we won't raise a fuss ♪
♪ We'll keep on slogging,
keep on slogging ♪
♪ Keep on slogging,
come what may ♪
We've got to keep searching.
There's more important
things to worry about now.
Look, everyone.
It's Spike!
Spike. Over here.
(Bushwoolies)
Hey! Princesses found us.
-No, found them. -Found us?
-Yeah. -Yeah -Yeah.
I'm so glad to see you.
You are?
Yes, indeed.
Now if only we can
find the magic wands.
Uhh, this is Gnash.
He...he says he can help us.
There are tunnels in here that
even Lavan doesn't know about.
We'll get the magic wands back.
It's worth a try.
Yeah, worth a try.
-What's worth a try?
-Yeah.
And so we need your help to
get the magic wands back.
This is serious, Megan.
The Jewel Desert is spreading.
Everything is
turning to crystal.
It'll reach Dream Valley soon.
Tiffany, I'll go with you
back to Royal Paradise.
The Rainbow of Light
is the only thing
that can restore
the magical balance.
There must be a way to release
the magic in the wands.
Maybe my own powers
are strong enough.
(screams)
It's working!
(evil laugh)
Master, what's happened to you?
I told you I was
not to be disturbed, Sludge.
What do you want?
Your pardon, master.
But the Princess Ponies
have escaped.
WHAT?!
This is silly. We're
going around in circles.
Hush! We're inside the
walls of Lavan's chambers.
He may hear us.
(evil laugh)
I can feel the power within me.
All my senses
have been sharpened.
(sneezes)
What's that?
(sneezing continues)
I thought so.
Guards.
(guards growl)
Seize them!
(groans)
-Our magic wands,
-there they are!
Not so fast.
We're trapped.
An Ice Org, eh?
I should melt you into a puddle
right here.
Wait, master.
There's no need for that.
Quiet, Sludge,
or do you want another dose
of what I gave you before?
Then throw them all
into dungeons.
I'll deal with them later.
I'm tired.
I don't know if I can make
it back to Royal Paradise.
You've got to, Princess Tiffany.
The Rainbow of Light may
be Ponyland's only hope.
Whoa! What's going on?
The magic's going crazy again.
Hang on!
Oh! No! The Rainbow of Light.