♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Nursery pretty, Megan.
Sure is, Baby Heartthrob.
Watch out, Baby Lofty.
Whooooooooaaaaaaaaaah!
(giggles)
I crashed, Megan.
You're not hurt, are you?
Not hurt, uh-uh.
Not good flyer either...
All done, Megan.
Let's get cleaned up then.
Come on, you can all sleep
with us in the Estate.
(snores)
Ooh, cold.
(howls)
Scared too.
(gasp)
Baby Sundance,
Baby Lickety Split, wake up!
(snores)
Oh, what?
Ghost in the room.
Ghost?
No, not ghost.
Bad dream, Baby Heartthrob.
That's all.
Yeah.
Go back to sleep.
(snores)
Is too ghost.
I get Megan.
(ghost howls)
Aaaah!
It is a ghost.
(howls)
I knew
I didn't want to sleep here.
Wake up, wake up!
- Ghost!
- Ghost?
Go away, ghost.
Leave us alone.
Get out of here.
We didn't do anything.
(screams)
(howls)
Help!
Let me out of here.
Megan.
(All scream)
(ghost howls)
Eek!
Yikes!
(ghost howls)
(bat screeching)
(gasps)
(screams)
Can't scare us, ghost.
(screeches)
(gulp)
Yes you can.
No, it can't.
(bat screeching)
Get out, ghost.
(howls)
Go away.
Hurry, Megan.
So what's so important
that you have to come
and get me
in the middle of the night?
What's going on here?
Ghost here.
A ghost?
Looks more like
a pillow fight to me.
We didn't do nothing.
Ghost did it.
All right, the fun is over.
So let's all settle down
and go back to bed.
There, now there's nobody
here but you.
No ghosts,
just baby ponies.
But there really was a ghost.
- Yeah.
Now let's get some sleep.
Don't wanna be alone, Megan.
I guess you could
stay with them.
Yeah, stay Molly.
Please.
Well, okay.
But no more fooling around.
We be good.
Promise.
We go right to sleep.
The ghost still here,
I think.
Now, Baby Cuddles,
you just close your eyes
and stop worrying.
Believe me, there are no
such things as ghosts.
♪ Go to bed,
have no fear ♪
♪ You won't find any
ghosts in here ♪
♪ It's all
in your imagination ♪
♪ Close your eyes,
shut the light ♪
♪ Goblins won't be
about tonight ♪
♪ It's all
in your imagination ♪
♪ If some scary monster
picks on you ♪
♪ The odds are it's your mind
playing tricks on you ♪
♪ So if a ghost appears
in this location ♪
♪ Don't get in a state
of agitation ♪
♪ It's all
in your imagination... ♪
in your imagination. ♪
(howls)
The ghost!
Megan!
Molly, what is it?
The ghost.
I saw it for sure.
Oh, Molly.
Not again!
It wasn't my imagination
or a dream.
It was a real ghost.
Yeah, just like that giant bear
in your closet
when you were three.
That was different.
Sure it was.
It was stuffed.
Tell you what,
we'll search the entire Estate,
and see if we find any ghost.
Okay?
We won't.
Will too.
Will not!
Will too!
I'm telling you,
there is no ghost.
Boo!
(gasps)
(laughs)
Spike, that was not funny.
It...
It wasn't?
Let's keep looking.
It's got to be
around here somewhere.
And when we find it,
we ask it to go away, right?
That's the dumbest thing
I ever heard.
That's not the way
you deal with ghosts.
You have a better idea?
Yeah.
If there's anything here,
I'm gonna catch it.
This ought to do it.
Okay, Cupcake.
Bring me the cake.
Ooh, looks yummy.
There.
All set.
I still don't get it.
It's actually
pretty simple, Spike.
The trapdoor is triggered
by this pulley mechanism.
And the cake is the bait.
Now I get it.
The ghost gets hungry,
sees the cake,
picks it up to eat it...
(thump)
Drat!
Er, would somebody
open the box please?
Huh, please? Could you, huh?
Would you?
(laughs)
Here,
ghosty-whosty!
Come out, come out.
Wherever you are.
Eek!
Oh, it's a mirror.
Oh, youch!
Eek!
Hang it on that nail,
Masquerade.
I wonder what happens
if a ghost gets wet.
Done.
Well, if it a ghost,
it won't get wet.
Come on,
let's put one over the door!
Spike!
What?
I already
put one over the door.
Oh!
(birds chirping)
(gasp)
Yikes.
Eek.
Whoaaahhhh!
It's the ghost.
No, no, no, it's not.
Take it easy, baby ponies.
Oh, Megan, we're never gonna
find that mean old ghost.
Molly, behind you.
I don't believe it.
It really is...a ghost!
(howls)