♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
We got them, Draggle.
(laughs)
They'll never survive this.
What is this?
It's a land pie.
Wh-What?
What's a land pie?
It's was...it's a...
Well...oh,
you told me to make it.
I told you to make a landslide,
not a land-pie.
Ugh!
(laughs)
Ew...
You've ruined everything.
Let's get out of here.
(cheers)
The landslide has stopped.
The witches are leaving.
It's safe now.
- Yeah, it's safe.
- No more landslide.
Yeah, nothing to worry about.
Phew.
That was a close call, Rosedust.
Too close if you ask me.
I think we ought to do something
about those witches.
- Yeah.
- Do something.
Get those witches.
No, they didn't really
mean to harm us.
- Correct.
- No revenge.
Revenge stinks.
Morning Glory,
Honeysuckle, please don't argue.
The important thing is that
we're all safe now.
But Morning Glory is wrong.
We can't let others
just run over us.
No, Honeysuckle.
It's better to
just turn the other wing.
Fighting isn't necessary.
But one thing is necessary,
Flutter Ponies.
We have to be getting back to
Paradise Estate now.
I wish we could go with you
because we don't want
to go home alone.
- No, no. Not alone.
- Oh, no way, no way.
Of Bushwoolies.an,
Thank you for coming,
little ponies.
Goodbye, Spike.
Goodbye, Bushwoolies.
Goodbye! So long!
See you soon.
Bye!
Be careful.
Watch out for the witches.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
It wasn't my fault.
Draggle did the magic.
It was Reeka's idea.
I just did
what she told me to do.
I don't understand it.
I've done everything
a mother could do
to make you low
and miserable and wretched.
Forget evil and mean,
give me something.
Could we please stop eating
these doughnuts, Mama?
No you can't,
and don't call me Mama.
Ouch! Agh!
Now come with me.
We'll have a family meeting.
I'll get even with
those Flutter Ponies
if it's the last thing I do.
♪ Oh family, family ♪
♪ Come to my aid ♪
♪ I need your help ♪
♪ I am afraid ♪
♪ Family, family ♪
♪ I turn to you ♪
♪ I helped you once ♪
♪ Now you come through ♪
♪ Tell me what to do ♪
♪ Oh, tell me what to do ♪
Help me, please!
(witches whispers)
(whispers)
Get Bumble and her bees
to steal the Sunstone
from the Flutter Ponies.
But what good would that do?
What do you mean,
"What good would that do?"
It would... It would...
What good would it do?
(whispers)
Oh!
The Flutter Ponies would chase
after their precious Sunstone,
and the bees would capture them.
See?
But Bumble and the bees
would get the Sunstone
and the Flutter Ponies.
What would we get,
Mama?
Oh, Hydia...I mean Hydia!
What would we get?
What would we get? We'd get...
(whispers)
We'll get Flutter Valley.
But there's all those flowers
and sweetness.
Yeah, yuck!
(whispers)
Flutter Valley will become dark,
dank and dreary
without the Sunstone.
Really disgusting!
(All)
Yay! Hooray! Whoo! Wow!
♪ Oh family, family ♪
♪ What a good plan ♪
♪ I'll make it work ♪
♪ I know I can ♪
♪ Family, family ♪
♪ Thank you so much ♪
♪ You did your all ♪
♪ You came through
in the clutch ♪
♪ Goodbye...Goodbye...
Goodbye...♪
♪ Keep in touch ♪
I forgot Bumbleland was so
co-cold.
That's why Bumble and
her bees are so mean and tough.
They're-
They're probably freezing.
They were mean and tough before.
That's why they got
kicked out of Flutter Valley.
Oh, look.
Red clover -
Bumble's favorite plant.
Maybe we should bring her
a present.
Good idea, Draggle.
Go get it.
What if I slip off the tree?
Stop being so afraid.
I'll be down here waiting.
Go on!
All right...
Whoaaaaaaah!
(laughs)
Ouch!
You were wrong, sister dear.
Now you get it.
Aww...aww! Uuh!
Aww...aww!
See how easy that was?
It's Bumble's swarm.
Agh!
Not so fast.
- Where are our seatbelts?
- I am not used to it.
(slurps)
One step closer and
I'll stick you.
Wait.
We come as friends.
We ain't got no friends.
We brought a present for Bumble.
(slurps)
What's going on here?
Can't you see I'm eating?
(slurps)
We're Reeka and Draggle.
The witches from
the Volcano of Gloom.
We have a proposition for you.
What is this
about a proposition?
Well, we thought
you might be interested
in a little plan
that would turn Bumbleland
into a warm place
filled with lots of flowers.
But nothing grows here.
I have to import everything.
But that's the whole idea.
With our help
you can get the Sunstone
from Flutter Valley,
and grow
all the flowers you need.
The Sunstone?
Flutter Valley?
The Flutter Ponies?
I hate Flutter Ponies!
So you like the idea?
I think it's simply marvelous.
But what do you get out of it?
We get Flutter Valley.
(laughs)
But it will become so ugly
without the Sunstone.
That's exactly how we like it.
Do we have a deal?
I'll do it.
Spike, what are you doing?
I'm on a witch watch.
What's a witch watch?
I'm watching for witches.
You never know
when they might attack.
But Morning Glory said
there's nothing to worry about.
Better safe than sorry.
Beware, little ponies.
Strange looking creatures
up ahead.
Follow me,
and be quiet.
Shh!
What are they?
I've never seen
anything like them before.
(arguing voices)
They're Furbobs.
Our first cousins.
Furbobs.
It's us, the Bushwoolies.
Yeah, Bushwoolies.
Your first cousins, Bushwoolies.
Relatives.
Cousin Bushwoolies, hi!
I'm Hugster.
I'm Charmster.
Charmed, I'm sure.
I'm Wishful.
I wish you remember us.
And we're little ponies.
Except me.
I'm Spike, a baby dragon.
Where are you going,
cousin Furbobs?
We're going home.
No we aren't.
We're picking berries.
The Furbobs never agree
on anything.
No, never. Nothing.
I wish they would.
Where do you live, Furbobs?
- Up there.
- Down that way.
- Across that way.
- Over there.
In the woods.
Actually we've moved
so many times in the last year
we don't remember.
Why? What's the problem?
The Stonebacks!
- They agreed.
- They said the same thing.
They didn't argue.
Who are the Stonebacks?
Our mortal enemies.
They chase us
from every place we live.
What do these Stonebacks
look like?
Like that!
(snorting)
We're trapped.
Help! Save us! Please help!