♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(growls)
Four-feet invade
kingdom of Charlatan.
Is forbidden!
(all gasps)
Ah!
No escape. No escape!
(thud)
Ooh!
(growls)
(Surprise)
Look!
(All scream)
(evil laugh)
(grunts)
(pants)
Galaxy, North Star, over here.
No, Megan. Stop!
(roars)
(All gasp)
It's a dead end!
(groans with exhaustion)
Come on.
Maybe now we can get it--
Halt! We take you prisoner
in the name of his majesty,
King Charlatan The Great.
Move!
Sonny, Sonny, are you in here?
Oh, Sonny, where can I take you
so you can thaw out?
All right, through here,
right in this cell.
That's it. That's it.
Trod in there.
I say, you must
let us out of here right now!
Oh, it's no use.
I fear we shan't be able to
tunnel through the floor.
We can't squeeze through
the bars either, Megan.
We've tried everything
and I can't wink
through the wall, so--
I know, Galaxy, I know.
Wait a minute!
My horn!
When I make it light up,
it gets warmer.
Maybe I can make it hot enough
to melt those bars of ice.
(zapping sound)
I think you've got
something there.
Good work, Galaxy.
Keep it up!
You're almost through.
Yikes, it's moving.
Sshhh,
don't make so much noise
or the guard will come
and catch us.
What are you doing here?
I'm trying to help
my friend thaw out.
This is your friend?
This sculpture?
That's my friend, Sonny.
He's frozen solid
inside the ice.
I thought maybe her horn
could help him thaw out.
Maybe. We're trying
to thaw things out too.
Everything.
(footsteps)
Quick! The guard is coming.
Pretend to be my prisoners
and do what I tell you.
Prince Edgar!
I didn't expect to see you here.
Umm--His Royal Majesty,
my father,
wishes to have these creatures
transferred to my custody.
You two, bring along the duck.
If we wanna thaw things out,
we've gotta get
to father's magnifier
and get him to
reverse its power.
Father's built a lot of
booby traps into this castle.
So watch your step.
Huh?
Oof!
I said, "be careful."
(siren sounds)
(gasps)
(Surprise)
Help!
(Edgar)
Follow me!
This way.
(All pant)
Don't relax yet.
We've got a long way to go.
(loud tumbling)
It's gaining on us.
It's dry ice!
Jump!
Put your friend on my back.
(All gasp)
We made it.
(All cheer)
Yay! Oh, yeah!
Don't congratulate
yourselves yet.
We haven't passed
the worst of it.
My father's throne room
is right in here.
(bangs the door)
Locked?
Then let's break it down!
Edgar, my son,
you disappoint me.
No more than you have
disappointed me, father.
It's my duty.
Stand aside, Edgar.
No, father!
No!
Oh, my!
(Both gasp)
(clears throat)
Well, what are you waiting for?
Arrest them.
Well?
But sire, what of the prince?
I--I don't know.
He shouldn't have
tried to interfere.
He--He knew the risks.
♪ How can you be
so cold? ♪
♪ So rigid
and controlled? ♪
♪ How can your heart
be so small? ♪
♪ Haven't you any feelings
at all? ♪
♪ How can you be
so hard? ♪
♪ Why don't you
drop your guard? ♪
♪ You have some warmth
deep inside ♪
♪ Why should that be
the feeling you hide? ♪
♪ There's room enough
for everyone ♪
♪ In this world
in which we live ♪
♪ Can't you find it
in your heart to forgive? ♪
♪ Why don't you show
some love? ♪
♪ Some warm and
tender love ♪
♪ It'll come back
a thousand fold ♪
♪ And you'll wonder ♪
♪ How you could have been,
so cold ♪
(ice melts)
Nothing is worth
the loss of my son.
Perhaps if you undo
your machine's effects?
Hmm, it's not reversible.
What's done is done.
I...blame myself and my folly...
It was my cold heart which--
(Edgar)
Don't be sad.
No.
I must face facts.
But father--
Edgar, how many times have I--
Edgar?
Yes, father, and you did it.
Only you could break
your own cold spell.
But how?
Because you love him,
and you proved it
with the tear that melted
the coldness of your icy stare.
It can't hurt to try anyway.
(machine rumbles)
Sonny!
(animals chatter)
(chatter continue)
(singing in harmony)
Shoobee Doo, Shoop
Shoop Bee Doo!
You did it, Galaxy
Ah! That's nice.
Achoo.
Well, goodbye,
Good King Charlatan.
It makes me so proud
to hear you call my father,
Good King Charlatan.
And I plan to live up to it
too...with Edgar's help.
I'm sure you will.
Goodbye!
(Surprise)
Take care!
(giggles)