♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Ponies
(Laugh)
We've gotta get these banners
and bows
and balloons
and things up.
You're certainly
on cloud nine today, Truly.
But of course, Paradise.
The Big Brother Ponies
are comin' home!
♪ In a short time from now
the Big Brother Ponies ♪
♪ The Big Brother Ponies
will arrive ♪
♪ Everyone will cheer 'cause
they've been away for a year ♪
♪ They'll be making a bow
the Big Brother Ponies ♪
♪ The Big Brother Ponies
look alive ♪
♪ They've been racin' 'round
the world ♪
♪ but the finish is very near ♪
♪ This time tomorrow ♪
♪ The Big Brother Ponies
will be here ♪
♪ Bold and brave
and strong ♪
♪ They've been away
so long ♪
♪ We have missed
them very much ♪
♪ But very soon
we'll be in touch ♪
♪ They've been racing
around the world ♪
♪ But the finish is very near ♪
♪ This time tomorrow ♪
♪ the Big Brother Ponies
the Big Brother Ponies ♪
♪ Will be here ♪
(All)
Yay!
Gee, what if the Big Brothers
don't make it on time?
Who knows what might
have happened to them?
And a year's an
awfully long time.
You're speaking of
the Big Brothers.
They'll be here alright.
And they'll be on time.
(giggling)
Surprise!
(balloons burst)
Hiya Buttons!
Wasn't that a good surprise?
Uh, sure!
Now help me replace
all these surprised balloons.
(distant music)
Do you hear something?
(circus music playing far)
A bit louder, perhaps?
It sounds like a circus.
Now, Kyrie sing.
No, Somnambula,
please, don't make me.
Sing!
(singing)
(singing continues)
Let's see... What it is...
Paradise!
(singing continues)
What are you doing?
You- aaoh!
(singing continues)
But the party.
Oh well, It doesn't matter.
(singing continues)
Lofty,
You can't! The Party!
(singing continues)
Everybody, please don't do this!
(band plays)
(Kyrie sings)
We're gonna play this
(singing continues)
when the big brothers cross
the finish line
(singing continues)
So get it right!
You hear somethin'?
(singing continues)
I surely do.
I hear the sound of
ya all not playin'!
(band plays)
(Kyrie continues to sing)
That's enough, Kyrie.
Aaahhh...
I feel better already.
Welcome.
We thought
we heard...a circus.
And so you did.
We can go there if you like.
All you have to do is follow me.
(All laugh)
(laugh Continues)
Fourth down and five yards
to go, Steamer.
We're almost home.
Yeah! And I'm gonna ride
all over your rails
at the finish line, Score!
Ah, just think, Salty.
In a few moments,
we'll see Paradise Estate again.
Ah, after all this time..
(laughs)
Aye, matey.
We'll hoist our jib
and lay ha-hard into port.
Uh... right.
Reckon you're lookin' forward to
seein' them
(laughs)
little fillies when we get home,
eh Slugger?
Yep.
'Specially that there Buttons,
huh?
Yep...
Hm.. sure hope she can improve
your talkin' abilities some.
Yee-haw!
Gonna bust
your chops, Score.
It ain't a touchdown
till you pass the goalpost, Tex.
Uh...
Ho-ho-ho! Blow me down.
Where is everybody?
Maybe they forgot
we was comin'?
Ah, not the Little Ponies.
N-not Buttons!
They'd never forget.
I've got it!
This is all a gag.
All we gotta do is walk
through that door,
and they'll all
jump out yelling "Surprise!"
It's the big brothers ya all.
Uhh... You could jump out
and surprise us now.
Anybody home?
Ahoy?
There is something
seriously wrong here.
Who could imagine
we'd return
after all this time to find
Paradise Estate abandoned?
Devoid of life?
Silent.
(Truly)
You're here!
You're here.
- Hooray!
- Me happy.
What happened to everybody?
They heard
the sound of a circus.
And they all
just up and left.
Like they were in some kind
of trance or something.
I hear it,
but it didn't bother me.
Me heard it too,
but no make me go.
Hm...it sounds like it affects
just the Little Ponies,
and not the babies.
And not baby dragons.
What d'you think
we should do?
I think Truly and the others
should wait here.
While we go find 'em!
They're just so dashing.
And brave.
Oh, I do hope
they can rescue the others..
(evil laugh)
Ah...I can feel
my powers increasing already.
Now I can make all this real.
(gasps)
Oh yes, oh yes, oh yes,
here it is!
The wonder kitchen
bake to your heart's content.
Step right up, folks.
The gardener's delight!
Oh boy, seeds!
(seeds scattering)
Ice cream, ladies and gents.
All you can eat.
I'll have one of each.
We've been following
the Ponies' tracks all day
without a sign of 'em!
And it's getting dark.
We're gonna
have to bed down soon.
N-no! We keep searching.
No way, Slugger!
Why, in five minutes,
you won't be able to see
your own nose.
(laughs)
Now, Kyrie.
Sing for me.
No, Somnambula.
It's not right.
I have the power to make
my illusions real now.
Uh- ah- all right, all right.
(sings)
(singing continues)
Truly!
Come on! We've gotta stop her!
Hurry!
Oh, Truly, wake up!
(singing continues)
Oh no!
Not big brothers, too?!
(singing continues)
We gotta break their trance,
somehow.
Oh, I hate to do this,
but...let'em have it!
(Kyrie continues singing)
What in the Sam Hill?
What're we doing here?
Somebody knocked us
off the tracks.
(Kyrie continues singing)
It was us.
Oh! Wha-what's that singin'?
It's funny singing.
It makes all the grown-up ponies
act strange.
Even Big Brothers,
like they walking in sleep.
(Kyrie continues singing)
But where is it coming from?
Right there!
Slugger!
What're you doing?
Truly!
(Kyrie continues singing)
Ahh...oh, no!
Come back!
Hey, you okay good buddy?
(Kyrie continues singing)
Yup, I-I think so...
That's where we've gotta go.