♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
There...
That oughta hold this little...
whatever they're called.
Ponies.
Who cares?
This one's no threat to us now!
But we'd better
take her with us.
So she can't tell her
friends what she's seen.
Right. We can't let them keep us
from devouring their land,
can we?
(all chuckle)
This garden was
only an appetizer.
Yeah! Haven't you seen all the
green hills around here?
What a main course.
Oh, no!
So the Crab Nasties
were right after all.
Ohh! It's been so long
since we've chowed down
the way we did back there.
Yeah. I'd almost forgotten
how sleepy it makes us.
What about her?
She won't go anywhere,
now that she's put down
some roots.
(All chuckle)
(All snore)
(struggling)
Psst!
Don't worry, Masquerade.
Whizzer!
I'll have you outta there
in a flash.
(snoring)
Shhhhh!
(grunts and groans)
Whew.
(snores)
Those rotten Flories,
they lied to us.
Wait till I get my hooves
on those...
Whoa, there!
They're too big for us.
We need help.
Only the Crab Nasties
know how to handle them.
Oh, no!
We locked the good guys in jail!
Hello?
I knew it.
I just knew this would happen.
I just knew they'd
escape some way.
Look at that!
We still gotta find them.
And for that, we need help.
(sobbing)
Oh, my poor, poor darlings...
and the Flories...
gone.
Maybe the Crab Nasties got free.
Oh, of course.
That m-must be it.
No, Posey.
It was the Flories.
Then what the Crab
Nasties said...
about being police.
They were telling the truth!
We don't know where they are.
Okay, you two keep
looking from the air.
(Posey continues to sob)
But Megan, the Flories
were so pretty
and the Crab Nasties
so horrible looking.
I guess it's like...
when you see a seed,
it's hard to believe
there's a flower inside it.
Well, creatures can
be like that too.
They aren't always
what they seem.
Now take this little
fella for example.
♪ When you look
at a caterpillar, ♪
♪ it's ugly to the eye ♪
♪ But remember, a caterpillar ♪
♪ becomes a butterfly ♪
♪ Ugly isn't always nasty ♪
♪ Pretty isn't always nice ♪
♪ Looks can be deceiving ♪
♪ Remember, always look twice ♪
♪ Be careful how you
reach conclusions ♪
♪ Appearances are often
just illusions ♪
♪ So remember that
with some creatures ♪
♪ A frown can mean a grin ♪
♪ Don't be fooled by
their outward features ♪
♪ The goodness lies within ♪
♪ Ugly isn't always nasty ♪
♪ Pretty isn't always nice ♪
♪ Looks can be deceiving ♪
♪ Remember, always look twice ♪
I just can't believe
flowers could be
capable of such things.
We found 'em, Megan.
The lake, the lake.
We tried to warn you.
We tried to protect you,
but you wouldn't listen.
Now, they're your problem.
We just wanna wash our claws
of this whole rotten business.
Please?
I said we're sorry.
We know we were wrong.
But instead of arguing now,
let's work to beat those
creepy plant things, together!
(boulder crashes)
Captain, up there.
The Flories.
(boulder crashes)
(All laugh)
We can't leave the Ponies now.
No one should have to
face the Flories alone.
Crab Nasties...
Let's go get 'em.
Come on!
Let's fix these crabies
once and for all.
(Flories growl)
(All roar)
Oh, my!
Wizard, no!
(growls)
(grunts and groans)
- Posey!
- Megan!
(growls)
Coming, Posey.
No! Go back, Jubilee.
(roars)
Charge!
(evil laugh)
That's enough.
(loud tremoring)
(fearful cry)
Don't move.
Release the Ponies.
Release the girl.
Or it's snip-snip for you.
Flories!
Surrender...
(Flories growling)
Time to shove off.
Gotta file our
report on this case.
And your names will be
mentioned, prominently.
I'm so sorry.
She certainly paid a
big enough price.
Her garden's a mess.
Oh, that's okay, Megan.
It can be fixed.
There you go, Ma'am.
Ready for replanting.
Oh, thank you, thank you,
thank you!
Ya know... Ya know what?
I think...I-I think
you're all beautiful.
Anything you say, Ma'am.
And uh... ah...
Gee wiz...thanks.