♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
♪ Shoop be doo,
shoop shoop be doo ♪
♪ Call upon the sea ponies
when you're in distress ♪
♪ Helpful as can be ponies
simply signal S.O.S. ♪
♪ If you find
you're cast adrift ♪
♪ And haven't got an oar, ♪
♪ Count upon the sea ponies
they'll see you to shore ♪
♪ Shoop be doo
shoop shoop be doo ♪
♪ Are you sinking fast ♪
♪ Had some nasty shocks ♪
♪ Feeling like
all hope is gone ♪
♪ and washed up on the rocks ♪
♪ Washed up on the rocks ♪
♪ Shoop be doo
shoop shoop be doo ♪
♪ Call upon the sea ponies
when you're in distress ♪
♪ Helpful as can be ponies
simply signal S.O.S. ♪
♪ If your rudder runs aground or
seaweed holds ya down - Kelp! ♪
♪ Count upon the sea ponies ♪
♪ They'll see you get help ♪
♪ Sea Ponies, Sea Ponies ♪
♪ Simply signal S.O.S!
simply signal S.O.S! ♪
♪ Sea Ponies, Sea Ponies ♪
♪ Simply signal S.O.S.
Simply signal S.O.S.! ♪
It's Megan and Applejack.
They're all right.
The Sea Ponies saved us.
It was great.
If you need us again...
...Just call.
Thanks, Sea Ponies.
♪ Shoop be doo,
shoop shoop be doo! ♪
You're sure this is
the right way?
Sure I'm sure.
(gasp)
Wow! Whoah! Oooh!
Oh, it's so beautiful!
Mr. Moochick?
Come in - come on, come on.
No time to waste.
Unless you want to stumble round
in the dark for all eternity.
- Dark?
- Yes,
Tirrac's going
to force your friends
to bring in the night
that never ends.
How can he be stopped?
Ahh, somebody's got to
sneak into his castle,
and swipe
his Rainbow of Darkness!
That's what gives him his power,
you know...
Ah, here it is, here it...
No, no, no.
That's...that's not it either.
What... Whatchya lookin' for,
Mr. Moochick?
The only thing that might
help defeat Tirrac.
A Rainbow of Light.
Do you have one?
I've got a little piece of one
somewhere...
Somewhere...
I just forget where it is.
But I'll find it, yes, yes...
It's got to be
around here somewhere.
Oh, it's the rainbow!
The Rainbow of Light!
But...it's so small.
Well, it's better than nothing.
But of course it is!
And thank you
for all you've done...
No time for thanks, no time for
thanks, no time for thanks.
You've got to stop Tirrac
before midnight.
You've only got, Uh... Uh...
You've got, Uh...
Goodbye, Mr. Moochick,
and thanks again.
Hey, you haven't seen my watch,
have ya?
I know it was here yesterday.
There it is...
Midnight Castle!
Oh no...
How are we going to cross that?
I have an idea-
the Sea Ponies!
Where are they?
They said they'd help.
♪ Shoop be doo,
shoop shoop be doo ♪
We've got to
get inside the castle.
- No problem.
- We know a way.
Hop aboard.
- See that gargoyle?
- Up there.
Pull his nose.
We tried, master, but...
Then try again.
If by midnight,
my chariot does not roll,
the head of your
little friend will... Well?
(whispers to Tirrac)
Ah, excellent.
But as for you, Scorpan, you...
Scorpan? SCORPAN?
It's okay, Ember.
He's my friend.
We're getting out of here,
Right Now!
Come on, it's almost midnight.
This place is like a maze.
How are we ever going to find
that Rainbow Of Darkness?
We've just got to keep looking.
(gasp)
Hey, where's Applejack?
(laughs)
So, you seek
the Rainbow of Darkness?
(laughs)
It is mine,
and so is your friend.
Applejack!
Stop it.
Run, ponies!
Yahoo! Let 'em have it!
Aaaah!
Seize them!
Whoah!
(scream)
Get back inside.
(cackles)
Oh! Rainbow of Darkness
that darkness sends,
Now begin the night
that never ends.
Aaaah!
Scorpan!
Scorpan?
All is lost.
No it isn't. Come on, Firefly.
Hold on, I'm going
for the double loop again.
(Evil laugh)
No! Guards, catch it.
Way to go, Bow Tie!
Ahh...
Over here.
After her!
I wish, I wish, I wish...
Throw it to Firefly.
Take it to Dream Castle.
Stop her!
Get the bag...
The game is over, little ponies.
The power is mine.
We have a power
of our own, Tirrac.
Take this.
It's not doing anything.
Maybe the Moochick was wrong.
Behold the Power of Darkness!
Our rainbow!
- It's gone.
- We're finished.
(Cackle)
Our rainbow's fighting back!
It can't be.
No! Agh!
Aaaaaaah!
Scorpan!
What's happening?
He's really a prince.
Tirrac turned me into Scorpan
when he took over my kingdom.
Aren't you going to change back
to what you were?
Not me.
I've always been a baby dragon!
A...aa...aaa...achoo!
(All laugh)