♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Danny)
Grogar's got to have
some weakness,
if only we can find it.
I did notice that
whenever Grogar used his magic,
the bell around his neck
became luminescent.
Interesting!
Perhaps the bell
is the repository of his power.
Repository?
Oh, yeah, right.
What did she say?
She thinks the bell might be
the source of his magic.
Get the bell and we win.
It's worth a try.
But how do we do it?
I know. We'll use
your pocket tape recorder.
If we can get
Bray's voice on tape,
we can use it to lure Grogar
outside the city wall
and grab his bell.
There's just one problem.
I left my backpack
at Paradise Estate
when the Troggles took over.
No problem,
we'll just get it back.
(chuckles)
Oh, yeah!
How?
Simple.
We'll take 'em by surprise!
Now listen...
Surprise!
Hi, guys.
(shouting)
Hey, come on, hey.
Stop that Pony!
Yee-ha! Ho!
(Danny)
The window!
It still works.
What happens now?
Now?
Eh, now comes the hard part.
(Danny continuing)
They almost saw us
flying in here.
We've got to be careful.
I spotted Bray
when we were airborne.
I think he is around here.
There he is.
So you call yourselves guards?
This is your last chance.
Grogar didn't capture
all those ponies,
just so you can
let them escape.
Time to go.
STOP THEM!
Okay,
I've spliced the tape together.
Let's see how it sounds.
(Bray's voice on tape)
Grogar,this is your last chance
to capture all those ponies.
It just might work...
if Masquerade can fool Grogar.
Speaking of Masquerade,
where is she?
(Danny)
Wow! Her disguise is great.
(Bray's voice on tape)
Grogar!
Bray, I thought
you were at the dungeon.
(Bray's voice on tape)
This is your last chance to
capture all those ponies.
(Danny)
Okay, Masquerade, run!
Wait!
Give up, Grogar,
we've got you surrounded.
You're wrong boy.
I have got you surrounded.
Uh-oh! He's charging again!
Let me out of here.
(screaming)
Now's our chance
to get the bell.
Spike, wait!
Not bothering you, am I?
(groggily muttering)
Oh, my...might not...
I will...but glony
(Grogar growls)
Uh-oh!
(screaming)
Run everyone!
Run, is going to do you
no good.
There is no place in Ponyland
where you'll be safe.
Well, that wasn't
exactly a big success.
Evidently,
Paradise and Forget-Me-Not
were the only ones captured.
It doesn't look like
we'll ever be able to rescue
Megan and the rest of them.
I sure hope they're okay.
(hinges creak)
Do enjoy your stay, ponies.
(laughs)
Don't worry.
We'll find a way out of here.
Somehow, someway,
we're gonna get out of here.
♪ Escape! Escape!
We gotta escape! ♪
♪ If only we could
squeeze through ♪
♪ And alter our shape ♪
♪ Escape! Escape! ♪
♪ We gotta get out! ♪
♪ We gotta keep
on searching ♪
♪ Till we find the route ♪
♪ To lead us to
our friends ♪
♪ From the awful place ♪
♪ We gotta make a break ♪
♪ I had all I can take ♪
♪ I need some
breathing space ♪
♪ Escape, escape ♪
♪ We're locked up inside ♪
♪ And we can't get free ♪
♪ Though we've tried
and we've tried ♪
♪ However did we do it ♪
♪ Somehow we went
and blew it ♪
♪ And wound up
in a scrape ♪
♪ There's nothing
more to say ♪
♪ All that's left
to do is pray ♪
♪ That someday,
someday, someday ♪
♪ We'll escape, escape ♪
♪ We gotta escape ♪
♪ We'll escape,
escape we gotta escape ♪
♪ Let me out of here!
Escape ♪
(Bushwoolies)
We gotta get out of here!
I have a feeling that huge bell
we found in that walled-up
room is important somehow.
The legend mentioned
something about a giant bell,
but I can't remember
exactly what.
Don't worry,
plenty of time to think of it.
All right! We got one!
(Danny)
We may learn
something of consequence
by interrogating him.
Yeah,
and he might tell us things
if we ask him questions too.
We'll help you, if you help us.
What's your name?
I am Drog.
There is no need
to keep me prisoner.
I've deserted Tambelon.
I want to join you.
This better not be a trick.
It's no trick.
We Troggles
were conquered by Grogar too.
Some of us want to see him
defeated as badly as you do.
All right.
But you better be on the level.
Spike set him loose.
Oh! Thanks.
I should warn you,
Grogar plans to exile the ponies
he's already captured
to the Realm of Darkness
at midnight tonight.
We've got to do something.
I know a secret way
into the city.
I'll lead you in.
I guess we'll have
to trust you, Drog.
Get ready, everybody.
We are going to rescue
Megan and the others.
Nigh!
Here.
Gosh!
No way am I going down there.
It's dark!
Well, not to worry!
I'll light things up.
All is in readiness master,
as you ordered.
Good!
Very soon now there will be
no more ponies in Ponyland.
These steps will lead us
to the dungeons.
Even a dungeon will look nice
compared to this.
It's safe.
(indistinct shouting)
You lied to us.
You betrayed us.
Well, welcome My Little Ponies,
what a pity
you can't stay for long,
for in a few short hours,
you with the rest of your kind
will be banished
to the Realm of Darkness.