♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(laugh)
I just can't imagine a better
day for playing polo, can you?
I've never been
very good at polo.
Polo is not difficult.
Keeping the ball in play
is a simple matter
of potential energy
meeting mass and being converted
into kinetic energy.
Huh?
What Wind Whistler means,
Shady,
is just whap it
with your nose.
Here it comes!
Oh, oh, oh!
Uh!
No!
I'm just not cut out
for this stuff.
Come on, Shady!
It's not that hard.
You just have to keep
your eye on the ball.
I've got it!
(whistles)
I object!
The rules explicitly state
that the ball may not be
engaged by unicorn magic.
Don't panic.
I'll get it down...
As soon as I figure out how.
Perhaps I can be of assistance?
(chuckles)
I've never had one get
away from me before.
Uh-oh!
Hey!
Uh!
Where are we?
Anybody see our ball?
I can't even see my feet!
What is this place?
It is called
the Mystificent Forest.
And there are those who still
hold to the hypothesis
that a strange enclave
flourishes beyond.
Huh?
(sighs)
I'm simply saying
there may be other beings
who live in this forest.
(trembles)
W-w-what do you mean "beings"?
Gnome-like creatures
called Dell Dwellers
who actually live below
the forest floor.
They are the caretakers
of the forest.
They do magnificent work
making rough lumps of rock
into the smooth stones
Danny likes to skip on the
lake.
And where do you suppose these
huge oak trees come from?
Were it not for the
Dell Dwellers,
the forest might not
have any trees at all.
They are very orderly and
well-balanced society.
And they do all this work
without any glory or reward.
You don't think they're
dangerous, do you?
Maybe we've gone
as far as we should.
I want to go back.
Whoa!
Wait up!
Don't leave me here alone.
Whoa!
(giggles)
This is great!
Whoops!
Ouch!
(gasps)
Ow, ow!
(All)
Ow!
What have we done?
Frazzits!
Run! Hide!
Don't let them get us.
Ouch!
Oh, my!
What have we done?
(giggles)
Wind Whistler, quickly!
We must do something!
This is no time for frivolity.
These multicolored
protoplasmic organisms
are ruining the ecology
of this place.
Did I say that?
Wind Whistler!
What is wrong with you?
Look Fizzy, no hooves!
Shady!
Come down from there.
Okey dokey! Whoa!
Shady, this isn't like you.
And Wind Whistler
is acting so silly.
(gasps)
Those Frazzits are
mixing up everyone!
We must do something.
Sorry, Fizz.
You're on your own.
I want to check this place out.
Looks like I shall have
to take charge here.
These Frazzits must go
back into the barrel.
Uh-ho!
I appear to be making
matters worse.
My bubbles work!
But this will take forever.
And I do not believe my friends
and these creatures
can afford to wait that long.
Speaking of friends...
where is Gusty?
There you are!
What are you doing
in there, Gusty?
Hiding.
This is not like you, Gusty.
Come out of there now,
I need your help.
Now, can you make a breeze
and blow these things
back into the barrel?
Please, Gusty?
I'll try.
No! Not that way!
You're dispersing them.
Gently, Gusty.
Please!
Come on!
Just a little harder.
Shady, we need you to knock
the Frazzits into the barrel.
No sweat, Fizz.
Almost done.
(giggling)
♪ Gee but it's a thrill
being somebody else ♪
♪ Somebody other than me ♪
♪ Instead of being
stiff and stern ♪
♪ I'm wild, I'm loose,
I'm free ♪
♪ Gee but it's a blast
being somebody else ♪
♪ Someone who's
part of the team ♪
♪ I'm working
side by side by side ♪
♪ And it's working
like a dream ♪
♪ It's fun to behave
like someone ♪
♪ Who is very
bold and brave ♪
♪ I never knew
it mattered ♪
♪ But it's nice being someone
who's not so scattered ♪
♪ Gee but it's a joy
being somebody else ♪
♪ It makes you
walk on air ♪
♪ It lets you find
the 'you' inside ♪
♪ You never dreamed ♪
♪ No, you never
dreamed was there ♪
Well, that is the last of them.
Nothing happened.
Everyone's still the same.
"This side down."
Hmm...
Gusty, Shady, come here.
I need your help!
Help me turn this barrel over.
This is what is causing
all the problems.
Careful!
"This side up."
(gasps)
I certainly hope
this is correct.
We can't thank you enough.
You saved our Dell
and the entire forest.
Aw, it was nothing much.
That's easy for you
to say, Gusty.
But what really did happen?
Well, when we fell
into the Dell,
We, uh, we kind of knocked
over this barrel.
As long as the Frazzits
remain in the barrel,
the balance of
nature is preserved.
But we inadvertently released
them and upset the balance.
That's exactly right!
But Fizzy took control and
restored everything to normal.
(giggles)
I did?
I mean, how did I do that?
Balance? What balance?
What are you talking about?
As I said,
everything is back to normal!
(All laugh)