♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
We're coming!
And I've got the rainbow.
(gusts of wind)
Okay, rainbow,
do your stuff.
It's working.
The sun is coming out.
It's melting the snow.
Be careful, rainbow.
Look out!
The rainbow saved us.
It protected us, again.
Good work, rainbow.
I guess we'll have to
find some other slaves.
Nope, I want
those little ponies.
But how do we get past
the rainbow?
We'll get the rainbow first,
then the little ponies.
Dream Castle's so beautiful.
All that's left to do
is hang these balloons.
I'll help!
No thanks, Sundance.
You've done enough already.
Oh...
What'd she do wrong?
Everything!
Sundance is a very good jumper.
It's landing she's not so
good at.
(sobs)
Don't cry, Sundance.
Everyone goes through
a clumsy stage.
Even I did.
I've always been clumsy.
But you're a great jumper,
right?
I can jump farther
than any other little pony.
Well, that's wonderful.
Think of all the things
you can do that others can't.
Now if I wanted that
big juicy apple...
I can't reach it.
I can.
See... Great jump.
And you didn't crash
or anything.
Maybe I was just lucky.
You're not lucky,
you're special.
Gee... maybe you're right.
Maybe? Come on.
I can also get to the party
faster than you can.
Wanna ride?
Sure.
My turn. Let me look.
You just looked,
it's my turn now.
No, I wanna see.
Come on, Baby Ponies.
Time for the party.
(All)
Yay! Yippee!
Party time! Let's go!
Baby Moondancer,
where's your costume?
Don't have one.
Don't have anything to wear.
Well, let's see what we can
do about that.
There, you can go as a princess.
Need a gown.
A gown... Let's see.
How's that?
Pretty!
One more thing.
Gee, the Rainbow Locket!
Perfect.
(gasp)
Thank you, Megan.
Now go to the party.
I'll be there as soon as
I put on my costume.
(morphing sound)
(disguised pony)
Hello there, Princess.
Who are you?
I'm going to
the costume ball too.
My, what a pretty locket!
- Can I see it?
- Why?
Uhh... I-I'm a nurse
I have to examine it.
No...
Give me that locket.
No!
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪ Ouch, that hurt ♪
Catrina!
I'll take that locket.
Help!
(Yells in pain)
I'll take the locket... and you.
Help!
Give us a ride, Rep.
Help! Help!
Baby Moondancer.
Take off!
You're too heavy.
Hurry.
Help, Megan! Help me!
Help!
Where are they?
What if we can't find them?
They'd better not hurt
Baby Moondancer!
(laugh)
Who are you?
We're Bushwoolies.
What do you think?
How do we look? Do you like us?
I think they're cute.
(Bushwoolies)
Yeah! She likes us!
Yeah! We're cute!
Simmer down, Bushwoolies.
You aren't looking for a large
cat by any chance, are you?
Yes, we are.
And a funny looking creature who
can change into other things.
Catrina and Rep! They
went down that hole over there.
Yeah, down that hole! Yeah!
What's down there?
That used to be our home, 'till
Catrina made us her slaves.
We've got to get down
there and save Baby Moondancer.
And the Rainbow of Light.
Follow me.
Whoah!
Oh no!
I want you to be my slaves.
No!
If I spare the rainbow,
will you be my slaves?
No!
Then say goodbye to
Baby Moondancer.
Catrina, wait.
That's going too far.
Raaaaaaaaahhhh!
You asked for it, Catrina.
Agh!
Aaaaahhhhh!
Whoa...whoa!
I did it, Megan!
You sure did, Sundance.
Agh!
Help, Rep.
Help me!
I-I don't know, Catrina.
If only you could change
and be good again.
I can change.
I can be really good.
How do we know?
I-I'll prove it.
Just help me!
Okay... Okay,
if you destroy
the witch weed machine.
But that took forever to build.
Can't you think of
something else?
Wait, I'll do it.
But I need some more potion.
I'm... I'm out of power.
Here it comes, Catrina!
The machine, Catrina!
Remember what you said.
(cheers)
Would you please
help me out now?
(trumpet melody)
(wrong notes played)
Let the parade
of costumes begin!
♪ Shoop be doo,
shoop shoop be doo. ♪
♪ Dressed like a dream, ♪
♪ They're all dressed
like a dream. ♪
♪ Take a look
and you'll agree, ♪
♪ They've stepped right
out of a fantasy. ♪
♪ Dressed like a dream, ♪
♪ Like stars that shine
and gleam, ♪
♪ Sporting clothes
so heavenly, ♪
♪ They're lighting up
the whole galaxy. ♪
♪ Isn't it fun getting
all done up, ♪
♪ Pretending you're
someone new-ooh-ooh? ♪
♪ Life is supreme when you're
dressed like a dream ♪
♪ Come true. ♪
You look beautiful, Catrina.
Do you really think so, darling?
Just like the good old days.
Go on, Catrina.
Your public awaits.
I'd be happy to, Rep, dear.
But you're standing on my dress.
Excuse me...
♪ Isn't it fun getting all
done up, ♪
♪ Pretending you're
someone new-ooh-ooh? ♪
♪ Life is extremely supreme, ♪
♪ When you're
dressed like a ♪
♪ Dressed like a,
dressed like a dream... ♪
♪ ...Come true ♪