♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Isn't this a great
spot for picnic?
It's okay.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, look out!
Shoo! Go away!
Whoa!
(All laugh)
You're lucky you didn't fall
in the water, Danny.
(singing in harmony)
Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo
(Sea pony)
Oh, so what's wrong with water?
Water is fun.
Watch.
Wee!
(whistles)
(thud)
(hinges creak)
(Sea Pony)
Wow! Terrific!
A treasure chest!
They're very pretty.
I wonder where they came from.
Virtually, anywhere I would say.
There are a myriad springs
and rapids in Ponyland
strong enough to carry it along.
I sense that there's more to
them than there appears to be.
(thud)
Ah, who cares?
We're here to have fun.
Come on! Let's play volleyball.
Hey! Wait a minute.
Where're we gonna get
a ball to play with?
No problem.
Watch this.
Here it comes.
I got it.
Hey, no fair flying.
Good one.
I wanna eat soon.
Hungry.
Hush now, Baby Lickety-Split,
it won't be long now.
Sweet Stuff, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll pick all the coins up.
Go ahead and finish
your game first.
I got it. I--I got it.
I got it. I--oh!
Oops!
(Molly)
You got it all right, Gusty.
No sweat.
I'll just make another bubble.
I only wish I can make bubbles
that are big and strong enough
to keep our popcorn.
Huh! Wow!
Look at that!
Gee, pretty.
(Molly)
Can you do it again, Fizzy?
(inhales deeply)
(laughter and play)
(laughs)
This is me.
Don't break it, Molly,
you're too high.
Megan, help me.
I'm scared.
Get me down.
She's in trouble.
We gotta do something.
Salt?
Salt has a corrosive effect
if you sprinkle it
on the bubble's surface.
Good idea, Wind Whistler.
Let's go.
Push it that way Wind Whistler.
Over the pond.
Ahh..
(singing in harmony)
Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo
I glad Molly is safe.
But I feel hungry.
I wish there was food stacked
as high as a tree.
This is impossible.
I believe the coins are
responsible, Megan.
I saw Baby Lickety-Split
standing on one
as she made her wish.
And the coin glowed
and dematerialized.
Magic coins!
I think Baby Half Note
might be right.
The symbol engraved
on each coin tells
what kind of wish
the coin grants.
(thundering)
(Danny)
Looks like it's gonna rain.
Picnic's over you guys.
Let's get back to the Estate.
I wish it never rained again.
Never again!
Hurray!
Now we can have
our picnic after all.
I've never seen a storm
clear up that fast before.
I know. It doesn't seem
quite normal somehow.
Posey, what's wrong?
Nothing but disaster.
Come and see.
This is terrible, Posey.
This meteorological debacle
is quite anomalous.
I mean,
it has not rained for weeks.
Something unusual is happening.
I guess I never
really realized...
(sniffs)
...how nice rain is.
♪ Oh for a rainy day ♪
♪ A day with cloudy skies ♪
♪ How I long for one day ♪
♪ Without the sun,
glaring in my eyes ♪
♪ Give me a rainy day ♪
♪ With puddles everywhere ♪
♪ Now it's parched
and warm ♪
♪ Wish I felt a storm
stirring in the air ♪
♪ Endless blue skies
get so boring ♪
♪ Oh don't you wish
it was pouring ♪
♪ Oh, for a rainy day ♪
♪ Sun, sun, go away ♪
♪ Let this be a rainy day ♪
Not gonna rain again ever.
I made wish.
So that's why it hasn't rained.
Come on!
Heartthrob, did use
any of those coins?
Well, yes.
But only one and it was
for such a good cause.
Our Sweet Stuffs' makeup was
positively ruined by the heat.
And there was this coin
with a mask on it.
(Megan)
Sweet Stuff, where are you?
(Sweet Stuff)
Over here.
(Spike)
Why are you hiding, Sweet Stuff?
If you looked like this,
wouldn't you?
Megan, it is obvious
that the metaphysical power
of these coins can have
unforeseen and
hazardous side effects.
Not only that,
but wishing on them can get us
into a lot of trouble.
We better find those coins
and fast.
Magic Star, have you seen
the rest of the coins?
Sure, Megan.
I put 'em in my good
luck collection for safekeeping.
Great.
Go, get 'em.
Maybe we can get ourselves
out of this mess.
There are only three left.
I don't know what any
of these symbols mean.
Try wishing for rain on them.
(All)
We wish it would rain.
(Magic Star)
Nothing.
Now what are we gonna do?
Ponyland's gonna dry
up and blow away.
We'll have to go
ask the Moochick.
He's our only hope.
(feeble rhyming)
Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo
Look!
The Baby Seaponies.
They've run out of water.