♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Just a little higher, Surprise.
(giggles)
Okay, Megan.
Perfect.
Oh boy, the Pony Olympics
are gonna be so exciting!
Come on,
you can do it.
Jump higher.
That's it.
You've got to practice
if you're going to be
in shape for the games.
See, you can actually do
three in a row
if you pull up pretty fast.
Well,
you can try it if you like.
Okay,
let's run through it again.
Okay, Shady,
whenever you're ready.
Oof!
Try again, Shady.
And this time, the rest of you
follow after her.
(whistles)
Agh!
(All shout)
Ow!
(laughs)
Hey, what's that?
It sure is pretty.
Hmm...
Let's check it out.
Come on.
(laughs)
Ouch!
Who turned out the lights?
Huh!
Let's...let's--
Calling Porcina.
Come in,
Porcina.
Oh, la de da de dae.
I'm so gorgeous...
Today!
Is this what you want?
Shrock!
Why are you interrupting me
when I have important things
to do around here?
Agh, showing me
pictures of goons
dancing around
in funny clothes.
Forgive me, your ladyness.
But I thought you might
like this material
that the boys
are modeling for you.
No, no, no!
That's not it at all!
That's just ordinary laundry.
I need some magical material
to repair my beloved cloak.
It's becoming faded
and tattered.
Without new magic, I won't be
able to turn things into glass.
Kazim, kazam,
kazoom!
See, my magic is running low,
and without glass how will I be
able to admire my rare beauty?
You must find a solution!
Hey, how long are we going to
put up with this prima donna?
This spoiled princess?
Just until she creates
a new kingdom for us.
(laughs)
And no one else!
Right!
(All laugh)
(indistinct conversation)
He loves me, he loves me not.
He loves me!
Hi, Shady.
What's the matter, Shady?
(sobbing)
I can't fly like a Pegasus,
I don't have any magical powers
like Gusty and Galaxy,
and I can't even make it
through a simple jumping drill
like any self respecting
Earth Pony.
I'll bet everybody thinks
I'm useless,
and they're probably mad at me
for messing things up.
Oh no, Shady.
I'm sure they're not.
But the best way to find out
is to ask them.
Yeah?
Why not?
Oh, hey!
Watch it!
(thud)
Careful!
Ow!
Oof! Ow!
Ouch! Ow!
Look at that.
Those are little ponies.
Did you see that?
Look, boss.
They're magic.
I think this is a jackpot.
(Shrieks)
Shrock, how dare you
interrupt me
with this image
of a bunch of ponies?
Wait a minute.
Oh, most fair mistress.
It is our belief that
the hair of these here ponies
possess magical properties.
Would that hair not make
a most delightful
replacement cloak
for your loveliness
if woven into a fabric?
(laughs)
Oh yes!
I must have that hair!
Return at once, for we must
prepare a plan for obtaining it.
Soon, my little cutie,
everywhere we look
we'll see me.
ME!
(laughs)
Oh, let's see
where did I put that?
(indistinct mumbling)
I know it's here somewhere.
♪ Look at me, look at me ♪
♪ Soon the whole entire
world will look at me ♪
♪ My reflection will be
all that people see ♪
♪ Look at me, look at me,
look at me ♪
♪ I look at you ♪
♪ Look at you ♪
♪ Soon the world will
mirror everything you do ♪
Though there won't be much
to look at when we're through.
(laughs)
♪ Look at you, look at you,
look at you ♪
♪ I'll make the
world a looking glass ♪
♪ They won't believe
their eyes ♪
♪ Yes, make the world
a looking glass ♪
♪ And you'll get
a big surprise ♪
♪ Look at her,
look at her ♪
♪ She has no idea
what is going to be ♪
♪ And we'll never have to
hear her sing off key... ♪
♪ Look at me, look at me ♪
♪ Look at me... ♪ ♪
Gusty and Galaxy each have
their special talents,
Lickety Split is
a terrific jumper,
and you can fly, Heartthrob.
What can I do
that is of any use to anyone?
I know just how you feel.
Sometimes it seems as though
everything is going wrong.
Like, just the other day,
I wanted some triple fudge
nut caramel ice cream
and all we had was vanilla.
Hmm... This is delicious.
Do you want some?
- No, that's not what I...
- Practice makes perfect.
You simply just got to
set your mind to it, Shady.
I have been practicing.
I try.
Maybe you're trying too hard.
Maybe you need to
have a little fun,
have some excitement.
Like a lovely costume party.
Something glamorous!
What do you think of
my new dress?
Now be honest.
You don't understand.
I want to be useful.
I want to do
something important.
Oh, you're so serious.
You just need a little sunshine
in your life!
Oh, never mind.
Shady, wait.
Don't go away mad.
You can't give up, Shady.
(indistinct)
Hey,
what happened to Shady?
I don't know.
She was here a minute ago.
Boy,
how's that for gratitude?
(laughs)
(All scream)
Come on!
Blow!
(Shrock cackles)
Help!
(laughs)
Whoah!
(wails)
Where are you taking us?
And why?