♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(yawns)
Oh, joy!
Oh, rapture!
It's the first day of fall.
Look how beautiful!
(cheer and merriment)
But don't forget,
there are autumn chores to do.
Winter will be here soon.
Oh!
Do we have to?
Let's play first.
Let's play tag,
okay?
Okay.
(indistinct chatter)
Nah, Nani, Nah, Nah...
Can't catch us!
Can too!
Ow!
Help!
Baby Lickety-Split.
Baby Shady.
Help!
Hang on Baby Tiddly,
hang on!
Ah!
Aaah!
Can't go in,
the water too fast.
Wh-wh-what we do now?
(tremoring)
Help!
Rrowff!
Rrowff, rrowff, rrowff,
rrowff, rrowff
Ah! The monster got Baby Tiddly.
Not monster!
Ah-ah!
Big puppy.
(puppy whimpers)
Puppy ask if
"Baby Tiddly okay?"
Uh,
I fine big puppy.
You saved me.
Only all wet.
(puppy pants)
(giggles)
Puppy make me dry now.
What's your name big puppy?
Rrowff, rrowff.
Dogs can't talk like us.
(giggles)
I'll call you Dinah then.
'Cause you're big
like a dinosaur.
Are you lost?
(whines)
Then come home with us.
(barks)
We keep her, please, huh?
Please, please!
I don't know.
A puppy is a big responsibility.
And I reckon this one's
bigger than most.
Ponies, ponies, ponies... Think!
Where will we keep her?
Where will she sleep?
Anywhere she wants to.
And what will she eat?
Hmmm.
What won't she eat?
We could build her
a dog house.
And... And she could eat
my cupcakes of course.
Well, with winter coming soon,
and her being only a puppy,
I guess we can't say no.
(cheer and merriment)
(Dinah howls)
Never ever gonna
finish baby Tiddly.
No time to play today.
(woofs)
Dinah gonna help us?
(leaves rustle)
Wraff, wraff!
Woah, Dinah,
you work fast.
Now we play!
But first you better wash.
You all dirty.
(barks)
(licking and munching)
Oh! Dinah!
You ate all my ice-cream.
Now, go sit.
I clean up mess.
(whines)
(woofs)
Help?
No.
You did enough already.
(Dinah whines)
(screaming)
Ugh!
What happened, Heart Throb?
This beast sat
on my Valentine collection.
Oh, they're, they're ruined!
(cries)
(sobs)
I hope tomorrow better.
This house looks like it'll
last forever, doesn't it?
Don't say that.
Nothing lasts forever,
especially my nerves.
I know how ya all feel.
♪ What are we gonna
do about Dinah ♪
♪ Dinah's driving
me wild ♪
♪ Give her some time,
what's the big crime ♪
♪ Dinah's only a child ♪
♪ But how're we gonna
manage with Dinah ♪
♪ Dinah's wrecking
things up ♪
♪ What's the alarm?
She means no harm ♪
♪ Dinah's only a pup ♪
♪ She'll ruin us all ♪
♪ And I don't mean maybe ♪
♪ Anyone can make mistakes ♪
♪ Remember she's only a baby ♪
♪ What are we gonna
do about Dinah? ♪
♪ This much I'm
positive of ♪
♪ The best thing to
do about Dinah ♪
♪ Is to give her
plenty of love ♪
♪ Yes, the best thing
to do about Dinah ♪
♪ Is to give her
plenty of love ♪
Ponies, please!
We said Dinah could stay.
So she stays.
Dinah.
Dinah!
Come see your new dog house!
It's finished!
(Dinah whines)
(barks and pants)
(barks)
(Both giggle)
So how much trouble can she be?
Not that she needs
to get any bigger, Cupcake,
but you now,
she kinda grows on ya.
I guess y'all were right
Dinah's a baby
and needs our help.
So allow me.
(woofs)
There you go sugar,
Bon appetit,
as they say.
(woofs)
Oh,
but that was dinner.
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
(whines)
Oh, all right.
I can help Cupcake
bake some more.
Oh, honeybunch.
Don't tell anyone
where you got this.
Dinah, Dinah!
(barks)
Ooh!
Dinah bigger.
(barks and howls)
(dogs bark)
Looky!
(All bark)
What's all this here racket?
Dinah got a whole
lot of friends.
Of course!
I'll bet she was separated
from them by accident last fall.
(whines)
You mean, Dinah will leave now?
Aww, they're
like her family, honey.
She'll be happiest with them.
Tell her she can go.
Tell her
she'll always be in your heart,
just like
you'll always be in hers.
(snuffles and sobs)
It's okay, Dinah.
I understand,
you gotta go.
(woofs)
(All bark)
(All)
Goodbye, goodbye, Dinah!
Well, I believe
you're gonna miss Dinah,
I truly do.
Of course, I will.
After all the
ice-cream cones I snuck her.
(sympathizes)
After all that complaining
you were doing.
Magic Star's right.
I do declare,
friends may have to leave ya
but they'll always be with ya
in your heart.
Thanks Truly.
I needed to hear that.
Even if she was a big ol' mutt!
(dogs howl)