♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
There's gotta be a way out!
Keep looking!
Listen--
(gasps)
I'm afraid we're doomed!
(whinny menacingly)
Stop this!
Please!
(gasps)
(tearfully)
My son..
Mother, can you ever forgive me
for what I've done?
You're my son,
I love you.
Nothing could ever change that.
(sniffle)
Please!
Leave my son
and his friends alone!
I didn't expect them
to hate me so much.
What else did you expect
from them, my son?
You haven't earned their trust.
And Erebus possesses
their spirit and courage.
(determinedly)
Not for long, he doesn't.
(evil laugh)
It seems we're about to receive
some company,
eh Zeb?
Yes, Master,
Knight Shade has done well.
I suggest we roll out
the red carpet
and give them all a welcome
they'll never forget.
(evil laugh)
Capital idea, capital!
(laughs)
♪ Haha! Hee hee!
Do you see what I see? ♪
♪ A bunch of lovely shadows
for the satchel and me ♪
♪ Haha! Hoo hoo!
There's more than just a few ♪
♪ I see some pony shadows,
plus a pair of humans too! ♪
♪ I'll bet
they're tasty shadows ♪
♪ They look
so dull and grey ♪
♪ There's nothing
quite like shadows ♪
♪ To brighten up
your day! ♪
♪ I'll bet
they're tasty shadows ♪
♪ They look
so dull and grey ♪
♪ There's nothing
quite like shadows ♪
♪ To brighten up
your day! ♪
♪ Haha! ♪
♪ Tra la! ♪
♪ We had been
feeling "blah" ♪
♪ But seeing
all those shadows ♪
♪ makes us wanna
shout "hoorah!" ♪
♪ Yippee! ♪
♪ Hoorah! ♪
♪ Sis boom bah! ♪
♪ Yippee! ♪
♪ Hoorah! ♪
♪ Sis boom bah! ♪
(laughs)
Ah, my boy...
You've done well.
This is a fine assortment
of shadows.
(licks lips)
Mmm,
very fine indeed.
Surprise, Erebus!
As of right now,
I quit helping you
steal shadows.
You can't mean that.
I made you what you are.
That's right, you did.
But now I'm making
my own decisions.
That's right,
not only is he quitting,
but we want
everyone's shadow back
and we want them back NOW.
I can't afford to let you
turn on me, Knight Shade.
You and your friends
will pay dearly.
(Erebus hollers)
The master said you'd pay...
...and now, it's time
for me to collect.
Oh...Uh! Oh!
I'll take care of Zeb.
Find that satchel!
Okay, Knight Shade.
You fool, you're out
of your league here.
The satchel should be
in one of these rooms.
We can't help running!
What'll we do?
The bushes, quick!
Hm? Ah, hahahaha!
You can run, my little friends,
but you can't hide.
(surprised noises)
(pants)
Split up and hide!
It's our only chance.
There's the satchel.
Got it!
Now let's go find the others.
Ahh...Oh!
You girls oughta watch
where you're going.
(chuckles)
Come on, Molly,
we've gotta stop him.
Uh!
Oh, darlings!
I'm so sorry!
Are you both alright?
We're fine.
Have you seen Erebus?
Seen him? Seen him?
My darlings, we've been trying
to stay away from him.
(gasp)
Galaxy, use your light!
No you won't!
Zeb, Zeb, quickly!
Bring the satchel!
Keep back!
Mm..
(screams)
I hunger, Zeb!
Feed me!
My pleasure, master.
Let's get
Galaxy to safety.
So the Shadow Satchel seems to
be the source of Erebus' power.
And the longer Erebus
chased after us,
and used up his energy,
the smaller he became.
That's right!
So if we can keep him
exerting himself long enough,
we should be able to beat him.
But we'd need
an army for that.
Well, that's kind
of what I had in mind.
(somewhat weakly)
Quickly, I need more.
That one pony shadow
wasn't enough.
I need more
and I need it now.
But master,
there isn't any more.
And without Knight Shade
there's no way
to lure people to us.
I don't care, Zeb.
I need more shadows,
or I'll take yours!
Yes, yes..
Now!
(laugh)
Oh, come on!
I need your help.
Now remember..
I know, I know,
it's important.
Now remember, Lofty.
Stay low until
you get out of Grayvale.
We can't risk Erebus
spotting you.
We're counting on you.
Lofty, shouldn't
we stay lower?
You're right, Molly.
(caught off-guard)
Woah!
See, it's just so
hard flying like this.
(screams)
Lofty, help!
(gasps)
What a lovely little girl.
Your shadow is just right
for my collection.
(laughs)