♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(laughs)
No!
(screams)
(struggling)
While they're playing cowboys.
I'll just take your shadow.
Woah..!
(thud)
Oof!
Woah!
That was close.
Hold on, we've got
a long way to go.
Megan, there's no point
in talking to the Grayvalians.
They hate me!
You're wrong, Knight Shade.
We need them to get
the Baby Ponies' shadows back.
Grayvalians!
Together, we can overcome
Erebus and Zeb!
Why should we help you,
when you stand with the very one
who stole our shadows!
Because our loved ones have
lost their shadows,
and we want to save them.
We trusted him before,
and he betrayed our trust.
If you don't trust me,
trust Megan and the Ponies!
They-
No! Go!
And leave us alone!
There's nothing we can do.
No shadows?
You let them get away?
I must have more shadows.
Only Knight Shade can get me
all the shadows I need
I will not fail
you again, Erebus.
We've got to get the
shadow satchel away from Zeb.
He and Erebus are gonna come
looking for us,
because we're the only ones
around with shadows.
So when they come,
we can be waiting for them.
I'll stay here with
Lickety-Split and Knight Shade
and try to get them
from behind, okay?
You and the sheriff
can circle through the woods.
We'd better do something,
they're here!
Now's our chance!
There they are, Zeb!
Return to me, Knight Shade,
and I'll forgive you!
You can't fool me anymore,
Erebus!
I'll never return,
And I won't let you
hurt my friends.
Surrender, Knight Shade.
You and your friends
can't stop us.
(fizzing)
(dismayed noises)
You must return to me.
Your friends cannot protect you.
Now feed me.
Give me that shadow now!
Going someplace?
Zeb's waitin' for ya.
(Evil laugh)
Leave this place, Erebus.
Listen to him, Zeb.
He's giving me orders!
Such rudeness,
and after everything
you've done for him, too.
You should have stuck
with me, my boy.
I would have made you famous,
and you could have
supplied me with shadows.
Spare him!
(laughs)
A mother's love!
How touching!
(laughs)
Knight Shade, you don't want
your mother to suffer, do you?
(Evil laugh)
Hey, Boss,
we got 'em!
Aww, we got the
big Cheesies, hurr hurr..
Seize them!
Oh..!
Mother!
Knight Shade, you know I'm the
only one
that has really had the power
to do anything for you.
Remember the fame?
The adoring fans?
It's not worth it
any more, Erebus.
You're a real fool.
Zeb! Another shadow.
This time, get his friend,
who thinks she's been hiding
from us in the bushes.
Knight Shade!
I'll just take your shadow.
No!
Go away, don't bother me.
You!
Because of you and your friends,
Knight Shade turned against me!
Soon you'll join him
in his torment!
I have a surprise
for you, Erebus.
The Flutter Ponies!
They're the army
that can defeat you!
♪ We are the Flutter Ponies ♪
♪ Better run and hide ♪
♪ We can zig and zag
and zoom ♪
♪ Up and down and side to side ♪
♪ We are the Flutter Ponies ♪
♪ Now you've met your match ♪
♪ Faster than a lightning bolt ♪
♪ We're impossible to catch ♪
♪ Too bad for you,
we found you ♪
♪ For soon if we surround you ♪
♪ Your powers will melt
away like butter ♪
♪ Doesn't help
to fume and sputter ♪
♪ Nothing can withstand
our Utter Flutter ♪
♪ Challenge the Flutter Ponies,
and you'll meet defeat ♪
♪ Onward, onward,
Flutter Ponies, ♪
♪ victory is sweet ♪
♪ Onward, onward,
Flutter Ponies, ♪
♪ victory is sweet ♪
Zeb! Zeb!
The satchel, use it!
Erebus! Help me!
The shadows are returning.
Returning the shadows!
(All)
Our Shadows!
Ah!
(panting)
(yells)
To think that those pathetic
creatures caused such problems.
But it'll never happen again.
And we have Knight Shade
to thank for that!
Three cheers
for Knight Shade!
Hip hip, hooray!
I don't deserve your cheers.
I just hope you'll forget
what I did, and forgive me.
(cheer)
Knight Shade wonderfulest,
bravest hero ever.
♪ Uh-uh-uuh-uh! ♪
♪ I'm a talkin' little pony ♪
♪ Knight Shade is my name ♪
(All repeat)
♪ You say
you'd like to meet me ♪
♪ I'd say that's a shame ♪
♪ 'Cause if your feet won't
moonwalk, ♪
♪ we'll never be in step ♪
[All repeat]
♪ You got to do the moonwalk,
because it is so hip! ♪
♪ Do the moonwalk, ponies ♪
♪ Put that sparkle
in your shoes! ♪
♪ Do the moonwalk, ponies ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ Or you'll never
get the blues ♪
♪ Move your feet ♪
[All repeat]
♪ Put a..
..smile on your face ♪
♪ Do the moonwalk ♪