♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
I say we go back in there
and show that furniture
who's boss.
We'd only get thrown out again.
Sweet Stuff, we've gotta find
that peddler and prey he knows
how to undo
the magic paint's effects.
(struggling)
Let me go.
Want baby buggy.
No Baby Cuddles. It's dangerous.
You just stay with us,
understand?
Have to get Buggy...
(gasps)
Keep out!
Stay away!
Hang on, Buggy!
Cuddles comin'!
This is where we met him.
Well, he's long gone now.
We've gotta keep looking.
Buggy, you there?
Oh, Baby Cuddles.
Buggy!
Hey, you!
Come on, Buggy.
(All)
Get out!
Quick!
Phew! Safe.
(panting)
No painted stuff here.
But what are we gonna do now?
Hey, look.
(gasps)
Let me in!
Go away!
- Ah!
- I said let...me...in...
Face it.
We're looking for a piece
of hay in a needle stack.
Oh, I hate to admit it.
But there's only one person
who can help us now.
The Moochick. To the Mushromp.
Go away! Stay back!
Get out!
Silence!
I say you leave.
(yells)
Perhaps then you are
beginning to understand.
Paradise Estate is mine!
Magic paint, eh?
Ooh, I don't-
That's a new one on me.
Oh, my word.
Hmm. I am going to have to see
this situation for myself.
Now let's get a look
at that home of yours.
All our things!
Why are they so frightened?
Work you wretches, harder!
It was my magic
which gave you life.
You are mine now!
I, Beezen, I'm now
master of Paradise Estate.
That's him.
The one who gave us the paint.
Oh, well, that explains it.
Beezen is a powerful sorcerer.
His power is in his wand.
Oh, he must have known of
your need for paint
before you even met him.
Hmm. This has all been part
of a carefully conceived plan
to steal your home.
Our things may have turned
against us,
but Paradise Estate
is still our home.
Then let's go get it back!
Oh, for cryin' out loud!
I was just mopped an hour ago.
Beezen ordered me
to mop you again.
Oh! This sure ain't
like the old days.
Oh, how I miss the Ponies.
They were so nice.
So tidy.
♪ Remember those times
When the ponies were here ♪
♪ They lit up the world ♪
♪ Well, pretty darn near ♪
♪ Remember those times
Till the ponies left town ♪
♪ Things were looking up ♪
♪ Now they're all falling down ♪
♪ With the ponies
You knew where you stood ♪
♪ They dusted every room
And you could use it ♪
♪ Then they went out
the door for good ♪
♪ You never really know
What you got until you lose it ♪
♪ Remembering those times
Almost brings me to tears ♪
♪ To hear the Ponies singing
Would be music to my ears ♪
♪ But why stir up those memories
Of way back when ♪
♪ We'll never
See those ponies ♪
♪ Again ♪
- Ah!
- Get back to work.
Ponies!
Keep the ponies out.
Hold it.
Beezen's probably
got every scrap of furniture
ready to fight us.
And the door
won't even let us in.
Then I say we break it down!
Charge!
Keep them out, I say.
Out! They must stay...
(yells in pain)
Listen stuff. When you
like more? now or before?
Before!
Who do you like more?
Beezen or Ponies?
Ponies!
Then let the Ponies in!
Whoa!
(loud crash)
Let's get Beezen.
You dare trifle with me?
(gasps in disbelief)
No!
Noooo!
He turned them back to normal.
Let's get him!
(Angrily muttering)
(both gasp)
I've got a plan...
(gasp)
He-he-he turned the
whole place back to normal!
There's nothing
to protect you now.
With one flick
of my magic wand
I can snuff
you out of existence.
Are you willing to risk it?
Very well!
Take back the magic paint.
No!
(wand laughs)
For centuries
I've been your slave, Beezen.
But now you're mine.
All mine!
(wand)
Now you'll learn some manners!
- No, please. No! - No power
is needed day and night!
(wand)
Working me into exhaustion?!
We'll see how you like it!
You'll like it!
(All laugh)
This place is in worse shape
than before.
That's fine with me.
There's nothing better than
a sense of accomplishment
to make you feel
all good inside.
What Paradise?
I never thought
I'd hear you say that.
It's certainly is nice to have
everything back to normal.
Normal? Everything?
I miss Baby Buggy.
♪ La la, la la, ♪
♪ la la, la la, la la, ♪
♪ la la la la ♪
♪ la la la laaa. ♪
Awww...