♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony, ♪
♪ How has the world
been treating you? ♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony, ♪
♪ Have your dreams
been coming true? ♪
♪ Tell me what's doing,
anything brewing, ♪
♪ Is something special
in store? ♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony, ♪
♪ Can't wait to see you
once more! ♪
I'll do it,
I'll do it!
You did it all right,
Sundance.
You ruined our sign.
Now we'll never
be ready for the party...
I only tried
to get the ball.
Oh no!
You can't
splash me, you can't.
Baby Moondancer!
(gasp)
(Cheers)
I'm really sorry,
Baby Moondancer.
You all right?
That was fun.
Let's play ball!
♪ What's been occurring,
anything stirring, ♪
♪ Hope your problems
are few. ♪
I'll get it.
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony, ♪
♪ May fortune smile on you, ♪
Come back.
♪ May fortune smile
on you ♪
Ball gone, Posey.
This is no time for games.
Get to work, Bushwoolies!
Take this to Catrina,
and whatever you do,
don't spill it.
There's hardly any left!
Spill it?
No, I won't spill it.
Uh-uh.
(purrs)
Here's your witch weed potion,
your queen-ness.
(purrs)
(hiss)
You furbrain!
You spilled my
precious potion...
Get me some more!
I spilled it.
I told you to be careful.
Now she'll get mad at me.
Too bad.
We're tired of being slaves!
We're going to escape.
Yay! Escape, escape,
escape, escape.
Did you say escape?
Don't drop me!
Please don't drop me!
I'll show you what happens
to Bushwoolies
who want to escape!
Couldn't he just
lose a privilege?
Yeah, a privilege, a privilege!
You have no privileges,
you're my slaves.
(gasp)
No!
How dare you betray me?
Bring me some more
witch weed potion!
She's really not so bad
once you get to know her better.
We don't
want to know her better.
Yeah, we don't want to.
Better hurry,
Megan'll be here any minute.
Can we
blow up balloons, Sundance?
No, but you can give
me that string over there.
Okay.
Uh-oh...
I'll save them.
Whoah! Oops!
Sorry.
You're so clumsy, Sundance!
Yuck!
Now I have to take a bath.
It's Megan
and Sky Dancer.
Hold tight, Megan.
(Cheers)
As our guest of honour,
we want you to wear this.
The Rainbow of Light.
It looks after us,
and keeps us safe.
Thanks, I'll
take good care of it.
- I'm Baby Moondancer.
- I'm Baby Surprise.
I'm Baby Glory.
I'm Baby Cotton Candy.
Oh, look at you.
Please play with us.
We have nothing to do.
Oh, yes you do.
If you want to stay up
for the costume ball tonight,
you need your rest.
But we don't wanna rest.
Into the nursery you go,
and no more complaints.
We never have fun anymore...
I'll take care of them, Posey.
Hey, Megan.
We don't want to take a nap.
We want to play!
Okay, let's not take a nap.
You really mean it?
Sure.
♪ Let's not take a nap ♪
♪ Who wants to take a nap? ♪
♪ Let's let go,
let's cut loose, ♪
♪ Be a locomotive and caboose ♪
♪ Whoo, whoo, whoo ♪
♪ Let's not nap today, ♪
♪ Let's stay awake and play ♪
♪ Let's not sleep,
let's keep busy, ♪
♪ Play a game of leapfrog
'til we're dizzy ♪
♪ Boing, boing... ♪
♪ Boing, boing,
boing, boing. ♪
♪ Let's do somersaults ♪
(giggles)
♪ Let's do cartwheels ♪
♪ Let's stay up until dawn... ♪
♪ Let's have a pillow fight, ♪
♪Let's have a tug-o-war... ♪
(Yawns)
♪ Goodness me,
did someone yawn? ♪
♪ Time we took our naps, ♪
♪ Before we all collapse. ♪
♪ No, it's not... ♪
♪ We're not ready... ♪
♪ Glory wants her bottle. ♪
♪ Where's my teddy? ♪
♪ To your beds,
douse the light, ♪
♪ And put your sleepy heads
down, ♪
♪ and sleep tight... ♪
(Snores)
Catrina's asleep
Now's the time to escape!
Escape, escape,
escape, escape!
Wait.
Let me talk to Catrina.
Maybe I can get you
shorter hours.
Shorter hours, yeah!
Too late for that.
Yeah, too late,
too late, too late, too late!
How about a week off
every summer?
Yeah, a week off, a week off.
No!
Shut off the witch weed machine.
What about better food?
A window so you can see out?
Yeah, a window,
a window, Good idea!
NO!
Bushwoolies unite!
Yeah, unite, unite.
Please, don't
do this to me.
Escape!
Rep?
Yes?
Do you hear anything?
...No.
Neither do I.
The Bushwoolies
have stopped working.
Actually, Catrina,
that's not exactly true.
Then they're still working?
Well, no.
They escaped...
Escaped?
How could they escape?
You were guarding them!
Where are they?
There's one.
There's another one.
They're too fast.
We can't catch 'em.
What am I going to do?
Who's going to make
my precious potion?
It's almost gone.
(giggles)
My new slaves!
Now, how shall I trap them?
Poor Catrina...
You've grown so cold.
That's it! Cold.
I'll make a snowstorm.
What's happening?
It's getting so cold.
I'm freezing!
Help!
That's enough, Catrina!
I can't move.
We're trapped.
I...I...I think I can get out.
Just a little more... there!
Get Megan and
the Rainbow of Light!