♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
There's got to be a way
out of here.
Don't any of the secret tunnels
lead into the dungeon?
I'm afraid not.
We're trapped.
(door creaks)
(All gasp)
Help! Run! Yeah, help, run!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Run!
Sludge!
Ssshhh... Be quiet.
"Quiet?"
I'll give you quiet.
Come on!
Put 'em up!
- Get him, Spike, Atta' boy!
- Give him what for!
(All cheering)
Yeah Spike! Get him!
Wait! I only wanna--
Ouch! Help!
Stop!
Why have you come here?
To help you.
- We really believe that...
- Oh, yeah, yeah, sure, sure!
Listen! If Lavan
destroys Ponyland,
I will suffer along
with the rest of you.
I've suffered enough
at Lavan's hands.
Ice Orgs and Lava Demons
have always been enemies,
but...I believe you.
Uh...sorry about...
you know.
Oww! Ooh! Your hand...
It's so warm.
That's one reason why
Ice Orgs and Lava Demons
can never shake hands
and be friends.
Then let me
shake both your hands.
We can all be friends.
- Thanks, Spike.
- Thanks.
Now let's get out of here.
Let's go! Yeah! Got new friend.
Yeah! New friend, yeah.
What'll we do now?
The locket was our last chance.
We can't search anymore.
It's getting dark.
And I can't fly
much longer, Megan.
I'm exhausted.
There's one other chance,
the Moochick.
The Mushromp's that way.
(knocks door)
Looks like the Moochick's magic
has gone funny too.
Oh, my-my-my...
What? Who is it?
It's me, Megan.
Hmmm. Let me see.
Doh...wait! Stop!
Come back here.
(panting)
Oh... de-de-dear!
Sorry for the mess.
But none of my magic
seems to be working right.
Magic isn't working right
anywhere in Ponyland either,
and we've lost
the rainbow of light.
Oh, dear me!
Oh, that's very bad.
Ooh... very bad, indeed!
Here! Let me explain
what happened.
It all started when everything
in Paradise Estate went haywire,
and then...
Now!
Let it be complete.
(laughs)
Master, what has
happened to you?
Power!
That is what
has happened to me!
I've become the most powerful
creature in Ponyland.
♪ Here's to power -
isn't it grand? ♪
♪ Holding the world
within your hand ♪
♪ Here's to power -
what a delight ♪
♪ Spewing out bolts
of rainbow light ♪
♪ How I revel
in being the master ♪
♪ Barking out orders...
harder! faster! ♪
♪ The man can bark,
but he also can bite ♪
♪ He's living proof
that might makes right ♪
♪ Here's to power -
truly divine ♪
♪ And the best
thing about it ♪
♪ The best thing about it ♪
♪ The power's all mine ♪
(evil laugh)
(volcano erupting)
Okay. Follow me.
(trembling)
No time for that, Spike.
C'mon!
Yeah, I know. I just thought--
That I'd be concerned
about how I looked?
Well, yeah!
I think now we're all aware
that there are more
important things to worry about
than our looks.
You bet!
Not that your looks
aren't important.
- Yeah, important.
- Real important!
- What's important?
- That's important.
- Yeah, important.
- Yeah.
I think we've all grown up
quite a bit
since the start
of this adventure.
Of course, I also still
think I should be Queen.
You? Don't be foolish.
- I should be Queen.
- That's absurd!
I'm the most qualified.
(sighs loudly)
And you say Lavan stole
the magic wands?
Yes! Oh...
He's a horrible creature.
I am quite aware of just
how horrible Lavan is.
No wonder all the magic
in Ponyland is turning bad.
(growling and snarling)
(chewing)
Mr. Moochick! Mr. Moochick!
(grunting and groaning)
(muffled giggle)
(All scream)
Whoa! Ow!
(chomps and chews)
It's eating everything in sight.
Can't you stop it, Mr. Moochick?
I'll try.
(All gasp)
No! I was afraid of this.
My magic's not working right.
- What do we do?
- That's easy... run!
- Aha!
- Now what?
Well I seem to recall
something about...
Oh! No, no, no, no, no...
That wasn't it.
Hmm...
(whistling and signaling)
What's he saying?
I don't know.
Habbit, what is it?
(Habbit continues whistling)
Habbit, what are you doing?
He's going to feed
you to the plant?
(continues whistling)
Hmph!
He's doing no such thing.
He wants Megan to look
in the Book of Lost Answers.
(gasp)
"The Book of Lost Answers!"
That's it!
(All shriek)
- Are you all right?
- Oh... fine, fine, fine.
But I can't seem
to get to the book.
There's got to be a way
around that plant.
Now...what is it rabbit's up to?
He wants us to
go around the house.
Let's go.
(chomping and chewing)
"The Book of Lost Answers"!
But how will we get it?
That's easy.
(bells chime)
(chomps and chews)
(groans)
What does it say?
Oh! This is very bad.
To stop Lavan,
you need your magic wands.
Oh, my!
But we don't have
the magic wands.
We'll get them back.
What do we do with
the magic wands
once we have them, Mr. Moochick?
You must seek
the heart of Ponyland.
But how'll we find that?
It says, in your heart,
you know the way,
and then you must
all work together.
No one can save Ponyland alone.
(angry growl and roar)
(Moochick)
Go now! You must hurry!
Are you sure this is
the throne room, Gnash?
Yes, I'm positive.
It's the throne room, all right.
No place else
in the world feels this mean.
(door creaking)
(All gasp)
Our magic wands...
What's wrong with them?
They've been drained.
Their magic is gone.
(Lavan)
Not gone, little pony...
The magic of the wands
is right here.
It's Lavan!
Run! Yeah, run, run,
run, run, run, run...
Run, where?
(Evil laugh)
(All scream)
(loud smash)
This is end of your quest,
my Little Ponies.
Yaah!