♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
It's from
the Palace de Branforr.
"You are cordially invited
to a weekend traleigh."
"Please bring the newborn
twins.
This party is in their honor."
Aww...
Newborn twins get to go
and we don't.
The party is for them
Baby Tic-Tac-Toe.
I'm sorry.
Newborn twins get
all the attention.
I say we do somethin' about it.
Well, we're all set
for the palace.
Look at me.
Quack!
I'm a duck.
(All gasp)
(loud crash)
Baby Quacker,
why are you going to
all this trouble?
'Cause only babies
get noticed 'round here,
are newborn twins.
(babies cooing)
Newborn babies
need a lot of attention,
Baby Quacker.
It doesn't mean we love 'em
any more than we love you.
Ah! The Little Ponies!
Entrer!
Have you ever seen
anything so glamorous?
Not since I looked in the mirror
this morning, darling.
A bedroom has been
prepared for you.
Dinner is at 8 sharp.
Bedroom?
This is more like a barn!
Pretty sumptuous for a barn,
if you ask me.
Pooh...
Too showy for my taste.
(laughs)
(footsteps)
(gasps)
Have you seen my brother?
Can you help me rescue him?
Uh, we just got here.
Zey took him two years ago.
(knocking)
Where'd she go?
There's something fishy
going on here.
Dinner is served.
My Poochy wants filet mignon.
But of course,
Duchess, Monsieur.
It will be done tout suite.
Never mind that, just be quick!
Ah, mama,
I wish I could have ze nice pet
like what you got.
Ah, my petite-fille,
you will very soon.
(clears throat)
Good evening, Duchess.
Who let those horses in here?
But mama,
zose are ze Little Ponies!
Oh, yeah, right.
(chuckles)
Bonjour, Ponies.
We're honored, your High--
Good.
Let's get some grub,
I'm starvin'.
I need more cushions.
You see, ever since the
Duchess took ze zrone--
Watch it, buster!
Oh, dear, oh dear, excuse moi.
I mean since the Duchess
ascended to ze zrone--
Never mind.
I'm just happy
that the toot-sweet
Little Ponies are here
with their dear newborn twins.
(babies cooing)
Oh, but they're tired.
Take them to the Ponies' rooms.
By the way,
there was a strange
girl in our rooms earlier.
I thought you locked
Suzette in her room?
Uh, she must have escaped
thorough another secret passage.
You must've been seeing things.
(chuckles)
Shall we dine?
(chomps and chews)
I was not seeing things.
Watch yer' mouth, sister!
You could be put out
to pasture, you know.
Ah! Me got great idea!
Let's go to dumb ol' palace
and crash their dumb ol' party.
I-I don't think that's wise!
But if you're gonna go,
I'm going with ya.
I learned one thing tonight,
being upper class
doesn't make you classy.
Ooh, I can't wait to get
out of this dreadful place.
I say we just take the
newborn twins and--
(gasps)
The twins! They're gone!
Come on,
they couldn't have gone far!
Maemoiselles,
you are all under arrest.
We oughta show those
newborn twins who's boss!
♪ Ooh, those newborn twins ♪
♪ They really make me mad ♪
♪ If they met up with monsters ♪
♪ I'd be only too glad ♪
♪ Ooh, those newborn brats ♪
♪ They drive me up
a wall - quack ♪
♪ If they were chased
by lightning ♪
♪ I wouldn't cry at all ♪
♪ Don't be silly,
they're just babies ♪
♪ You're just talking
out of spite ♪
♪ You don't wanna
see them hurt ♪
♪ Why not? ♪
♪ It sure would
serve them right ♪
♪ Ooh, those newborn twins ♪
♪ I'd have no regrets ♪
♪ If someone bought
them collars ♪
♪ And turned them into pets. ♪
♪ Then you'd see us
breaking into grins ♪
♪ Laughing and cheering ♪
♪ Joking and cheering ♪
♪ Sneering... ♪
♪ At those newborn twins ♪
(gate rumbles and slams)
This is awful!
We gotta rescue
the newborn twins!
Good luck.
I know every joist and timber
of this palace.
And there's no way
out of this dungeon.
I'm
the Prince Philippe de Branforr.
This is my palace.
Sorry, the accommodations
are unpleasant.
But the place has gone to seed
since my scullery maid
usurped the throne.
The Duchess is your cook?
Huh! I knew it!
You must help us.
The problem is getting through
that door.
You need ze key.
And ze key
is on ze guard's belt.
Buttons, can you get them?
I think so.
(snores)
No good.
The belt!
(gate slams)
Oh, me, oh!
Ouch!
This way.
(groans)
Doh!
Oh, there is no way in.
Let's go home?
Me think hard enough,
there be way in.
See?
You must come with me.
This tunnel should
lead right to...
the palace guard.
(in French)
Alons, vite, vite!
Regarde! Look!
(All gasp)
(Ponies scream)
Ooh! I'm so happy to have
ze pets like mama,
and we have
so much fun togezer.
(Ponies continue to scream)
No, no, Tumbleweed,
you are mine.
Not what we hoping
would happen to them.
Only now me not feel good
'bout hoping for it...
We gotta save 'em.
(gasps)
The guards! We must run.
We gonna let dumb guards
stop us from savin' newborns?
(All)
No!
Enguarde!
(grunts and groans)
Heave-ho!
(grunting and groaning)
Well done!
Splendid!
(Suzette)
Philippe, you're free!
Suzette, you're safe.
But some friends of yours
arrived,
ze First Tooth Ponies.
- What?
- And ze guards are after zem.
We must help zem.
(gasps)
No, they're not.
Charge!
Ooouch!
(gurgles)
(grunting)
To Margette's room.
(baby ponies crying)
Forget those bratty ponies.
We gotta get the prince
back in the dungeon.
(Philippe)
Too late, Duchess.
Philippe! Ze guards are coming!
Let them.
Seize them.
Seize them all.
Take a good look
at your Duchess.
This is how she treats innocent,
defenseless babies.
Men, who's side will you choose?
Hers, or zat of your true
rightful prince?
(All)
Long live Prince Philippe!
(All cheer)
Alore!
And you, Duchess,
can have your old job back...
in the scullery!
You had to have a pet,
didn't you?
Little Ponies, you helped
restore me to my throne.
I owe you a great debt.
I'd say we're about even...
(All laugh happily)