♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Okay, Paradise,
you're it this time.
We hide and you go seek.
Very well,
but remember you unicorns,
winking out
is against the rules.
One...two...three...
(All laugh)
Paradise
never find me here.
Hide with me, Shady.
(squeaking)
Oh, no!
Paradise find me for sure.
Nine...ten.
Ready or not?
Here I come!
Hey, no fair!
Baby Ribbon winked out.
Baby Ribbon, you know
winking out
is against the rules.
Now wink back in this minute.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay.
Wink all the way back in,
so we can get on with the game.
I'll try.
(laughs)
She has such trouble
winking back in.
Come on Baby Ribbon,
want you to play some more.
Come on, little one,
you can do it.
I did it!
Okay, let's start over.
I'll be it again.
One...two...
I'll hide in the pool.
Do you mind?
(Paradise)
Ready or not?
Here I come!
Someone is hiding
behind that rock.
And I think it's Baby Ribbon.
Oh! Not again!
She's no fun.
Baby Ribbon, we're waiting.
Boy, this is pathetic!
Oh, come on!
She's just a baby.
Looks like she's having
more trouble than usual.
Maybe she winked back
somewhere else.
I'll see if I can find her.
Back in a jiffy.
(Molly)
Something has happened to them.
I just know it.
We better tell Megan.
I wonder where they
could have gone?
(Ribbon)
Baby Ribbon, where are you?
For that matter, where am I?
(gasps)
Ah!
(Megan)
Now let's not jump
to conclusions.
We don't know for certain
that they're in trouble.
I have a bad feeling about it.
I've got to find out
what's happened to them.
Galaxy, wait!
Oh, no! She's gone too.
Now hold on.
After all, it's only been
a couple of seconds.
The unicorns wink in and
out instantly, Megan.
If Galaxy had found
Ribbon and Baby Ribbon,
they'd be back by now.
- What's going on?
- I think they'll be back.
All right, listen to me.
Spread the word,
no more winking out
until we know what's going on.
Is that clear?
Perfectly.
Good thinking, Megan.
Come on!
Let's tell the other unicorns
while there's still time.
(play and laughter)
I'm the queen of the mountain.
I'll wink up there and show her.
(both gasp)
Ah!
Baby Gusty, stop!
(Both)
Oh! no!
(singing in harmony)
Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo
What's wrong, Fizzy?
I wanna cross the water.
Use the rocks.
I'm afraid I'll fall in.
I think I'll just wink across.
(singing in harmony)
Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo
Hi, have you seen Fizzy around?
She just winked out.
But she didn't wink
back in again.
I'm afraid Gusty's gone too.
She was so impatient
to run back here for lunch,
so she winked out instead.
That means I'm the
only unicorn left.
Let's get the other ponies.
We've got to form
search parties
and try to find the unicorns.
It's getting dark.
We're gonna have to get back
to Paradise Estate.
Just let me look
around this rock.
Buttons come back.
Those rocks look like
they might give way.
She winked out.
I saw her.
So did I.
(breathes heavily)
(gasps)
Tambelon
(breathes heavily)
I heard Ribbon say Tambelon,
then I woke up.
Tambelon? Hmm!
It sounds familiar.
Something to do with the
legend of a lost city.
I'm sure that Ribbon was trying
to reach me telepathically.
But from where?
We'll never see them again.
No, no. They'll come back.
But from where?
Where have the unicorns gone?
♪ Where
have the unicorns gone? ♪
♪ Where are those
magical creatures now? ♪
♪ Once upon a time
they frolicked near ♪
♪ What could have made
them disappear? ♪
♪ I keep looking
high and low ♪
♪ They're nowhere
in the neighborhood ♪
♪ I search
every corner that I know ♪
♪ I can't believe
they've gone for good ♪
♪ Bring back
the unicorns please ♪
♪ Don't say they've
taken their final bow ♪
♪ I still need a dream
to dream upon ♪
♪ Tell me where have
the unicorns gone ♪
♪ Oh! where
have the unicorns gone? ♪
According to the ancient legend,
Tambelon is the
realm of darkness,
a sort of in-between place.
It last appeared 500 years ago,
and its ruler, Grogar,
tried to conquer Ponyland.
So what happened?
How did he wind up back
in the Realm of Darkness?
Ah...I don't remember.
But Grogar swore he would return
in 500 years to try again.
That still doesn't explain
what happened to the unicorns.
If Tambelon changes slowly
from the realm of darkness
to Ponyland,
maybe one part changed
faster than the others.
And somehow caught the unicorns
when they were
winking in and out.
You mean they might
be in Tambelon?
(Bray)
Little Unicorns had best eat.
No telling
when the next meal might come,
if it comes.
(cackles)
There's gotta to be some way
to get out of here.
How?
We can't wink through walls
and that door is locked.
Isn't there anything we can do?
I've already done
the only thing.
I just hope my dream message
got through to Megan.
The unicorns
have been fed, master.
Excellent!
Now Bray, we will reach
Ponyland very soon.
Prepare the Troggles
for arrival.
Yes, master, right away.
(Grogar)
Oh, and Bray...
...don't dawdle, mmm.
No, no master, no dawdling.
Of course, not master,
right away, master.
We'll form search
parties again today.
(thundering)
I've never seen a storm
come up so fast before.
This isn't a storm.
It's Tambelon!
In the name of Grogar!
Capture the little ponies.
Run!
Get the little ponies!
(screaming)
It's done master.
Dream Valley is yours.
(Grogar)
Exactly as I planned.
Today, Dream Valley.
Tomorrow, all of Ponyland.