♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Looks a mite dangerous, Score.
That's where
the Little Ponies are, Tex.
That's where Buttons is!
Then that's
where we're gonna go.
Now, you lil' 'uns head back
up to the hills and stay safe.
Come on!
Let's see some teamwork.
Whoa!
Now that's what I call teamwork.
Boy howdy!
I'm beginnin' to understand
why all the Little Ponies
left home.
Maybe.
But there's something
weird about all this.
Truly!
Hey, c'mere,
we wanna talk to ya.
Well how do you like that?
Lickety-Split?
It's us.
It's the Big Brother Ponies.
Not now, I've gotta
get some more ice cream.
(Arabian music)
Heart Throb!
No!
I am Salome,
one of the most famous lovers
in history.
Heart Throb,
don't you recognize us?
Go away,
you're spoiling my performance.
No!
You're gonna listen to us.
Heart Throb...you're so old.
I feel fine.
Now get out of here!
I want to be alone.
Gingerbread!
(All gasp)
I just gotta find Buttons
I gotta know if she's okay.
That gal's face looked like
40 miles of bad road.
Something is not
altogether ship-shape here.
I'll say!
We've got to get them
outta here now.
And we can't let
anything stop us.
(All)
Wooaaaah!
Well shift my gears!
Boy, what a spread!
(All gasp)
Ho-ho-ho!
Blow me down!
Now who coulda' known
that football is my game?
Aye, and there's the
fine ship I've always wanted.
Wait a minute, guys.
This isn't right.
It's too perfect.
Yeah, ain't it just?
♪ Hey let's play ♪
♪ I really enjoy fooling
around with my brand new toy ♪
♪ No let's go ♪
♪ There's work to be done
and after we're through ♪
♪ We'll have time for fun ♪
♪ Hey, let's play ♪
♪ I'm feeling the itch ♪
♪ Horsing around would
be quite a switch ♪
♪ No, let's go ♪
♪ There's trouble ahead
Let's keep alert ♪
♪Or we'll be misled ♪
♪ Couldn't we play
for just a minute ♪
♪ Then be on our way? ♪
♪ No, no, don't go astray ♪
♪ No, no, we mustn't stay ♪
♪ If we do we'll rue the day ♪
♪ We'll play later ♪
♪ Okay ♪
♪ Okay, okay ♪
So, they won't play, eh?
No!
No, don't make me do it
Somnambula.
What you're doing is evil.
I have my youth back
I have my new powers.
You don't think I'm going
to stop now, do you?
Now, sing!
(singing)
(singing continues)
No!
Don't listen to it!
(singing continues)
All aboard?
Yee Haw! It's roundup time!
(singing continues)
Let's burn rubber.
All power back -
Full speed ahead!
(singing continues)
Batter up!
It's a wide-end run.
(singing continues)
He's on the 50, the 40, the 30!
(laughs)
I've got to get out
of here.
I've just got to.
Gotta get out.
Oh, I am out.
(grunts)
Hey, look!
- Hey!
- Over here.
(All)
There she is! Look!
Yeah, I see her!
What do you want?
Have you seen the ponies?
They're in there,
and they're all playing.
What?
Somnambula made me
sing them into a trance.
Who's Somnambula?
She's an awful witch,
who takes the youth for herself
and only gives back age.
Y-you put them in a trance?
Can you put them out of it?
Well, I suppose I could sing a
different song,
but I'm not going back there.
I'm not going anywhere
near Somnambula again.
But you have to help us.
Please!
Help rescue our friends.
(All)
Yeah, help us! Please!
Okay...I'll help.
Will you come with me?
(All)
YES!
Okay, no one's around.
Cover your ears.
(Kyrie singing)
(singing continues)
The Ponies!
Got to help them!
(singing continues)
What am I doin'?
You came!
You rescued us.
Our heroes.
But what's happened to us?
We're so old.
Where's Buttons?
I can't find her.
Yeah! I haven't
seen any of the unicorns.
And you won't, either.
4-Speed, Slugger,
come with me.
The rest of you -
protect the Little Ponies.
And bring that bird.
You heard him.
Let's get down to business.
Yee-Haw!
Let's break it down.
Aaaagh!
Let's try again.
Now you'll know what it's like
to have someone gnawin' on you.
Hey, watch where you're goin'!
This is gettin' us nowhere.
We've got to get it open.
Remember Slugger -
Buttons is probably
on the other side.
It's like
all their magic powers
are being sucked
into that crystal.
So...that's it.
Somnambula's been getting
her youth from the other ponies,
and her new powers
from the unicorns.
Quite right, Kyrie!
And I've no intention
of giving them up.
Woo-Wee!
Sing, Kyrie
- wake the unicorns up.
But she can't.
(muffled squeaks)
Then, I'll stop you myself.
Ah...but you won't.
(laughs)
Buttons!
(gasps)
No!
NO!
No...!
No, no!
Well, tie me up
and brand me.
Ya all's young again!
And everybody's safe
and sound.
What about Slugger?
And Buttons?
Don't worry.
They're the safest
and soundest of any of us.
(All giggle)
Let's hard a port and
set sail for safe dry dock.
I've got a better idea, Salty.
Let's go home instead?