♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(growls)
(Robin Hood)
Steady, steady...
that's it!
Dear me!
I'm not half so good as you,
Robin Hood!
You'll get the hang
of it, North Star.
Watch!
(All gasp)
Ah, impossible!
I've never missed a shot. Ever!
(cries)
There! Clean as a whistle.
Just let me clean
what's underneath and--
(struggling)
What's happening to my strength?
Oh, my dear!
All my life,
my heart has yearned for
one as fair as you.
And you, and you, and you.
(All sigh)
My dearest, my darling.
(smacks)
My only, my one true love.
(gasps)
A wrinkle?
My face, my perfect face!
It's ruined!
(All applaud)
Graceful flowing,
my little Salomes.
(growl in the distance)
Run, my little ones!
The monster!
And what about the
barometric pressure?
The pollen count and--
Oh, I just wished for
a perfect day--
Don't be discouraged,
Lickety-Split.
Give it another try.
At this point, the only thing
that would cheer me up is a
nice, big, ice-cream cone,
and I mean a huge one!
Chocolate, strawberry,
vanilla, butter pecan?
(groans)
Here we go again...
(Lickety-Split clears throat)
Pardon me, but I believe
I can expedite matters.
(clears throat again)
Lickety-Split would like
a 200-foot sugar cone
filled with 200
scoops of rocky road.
Each scoop 2 to 4
feet in diameter
and the entire confection
should be covered with
2 tons of chocolate jimmies.
You got it!
Gee wiz!
You did it!
Indeed, it's exactly
what I requested.
Of course, you expected
something less.
Uh-oh! Make it go away!
But you just called it
"perfection!"
(All gasp)
Make it disappear!
Huh?
(All yelling)
Run! Run! Run!
W-what happened?
How'd ya make it disappear?
I didn't.
That ice-cream cone
should have lasted long
enough for you to eat it.
Yoo-hoo! Prince Charming?
Darling?
It's me,
your little Heart Throb?
My! They certainly are letting
this place get rundown!
(crumbling)
Appalling!
Oh Princey-poo?!
(gasps)
Huh?
What happened to the words?
Where are the pictures?
The storybooks are all blank!
(Paradise)
Megan! Are you there?
Paradise! What're
you doing here?
I wanted to ask you about some
new legends I've just met.
Robin Hood, Chaharazad,
Paul Bunyan.
You met them?
They're only legends in books.
Only-- all the pages in
my books are blank.
Well, they all left the Land of
Legends today
and came to Ponyland.
Let's go to Paradise Estate.
Something weird's
going on here...
and there!
You're Robin Hood, all right.
The great archer.
I seem to have lost my touch.
Really?
(Chaharazad) Run! Everybody
run for your lives!
(Paul Bunyan) It's coming!
(Megan)
What is?
The monster!
(stomps approaching)
(angry growl and roar)
(All gasp)
I'ma comin' to get you!
(Megan)
It doesn't look so dangerous.
Come on!
Hey!
No fair hiding!
We're doomed!
(chuckles)
I found you!
(Lickety-Split)
Monster!
Huh?
Stop it!
Bad monster! Down!
(groaning)
Aww...
Bad monster!
You play too rough.
(crying)
I'm sorry.
This is what you
were so afraid of?
Where have you been?
I haven't had anyone to chase.
I get it!
It can't help
being the monster
anymore than Prince Charming
can help being charming
or Paul Bunyan can keep
from chopping down trees.
See! You all have different
roles in the Land of Legends.
And the monster's role is...
well, to be a monster.
I don't know about that.
(Heart Throb)
Yoo-hoo! Prince Charming!
Princey! My love!
I thought I'd never
see you again.
Unfortunately, you're not nearly
as charming as I remembered.
(sighs)
It's true.
I'm losing my looks.
And I can't swing my
axe to save my life.
And my aim is gone.
Well!
Maybe it's time you considered
going back where you belong?
But we want to stay.
I can't say I blame them.
That place is simply
falling apart!
Falling apart?
The Land of Legends?
Let's help them if we can.
(Heart Throb)
The land beyond the door
(tremoring)
is falling apart!
I think it's because they
left the Land of Legends.
I bet if you all
went back through door,
everything would get better.
Very well, we'll go back.
But not with that thing!
(All)
He's right! He's right!
I don't want to go with him.
But has he ever really hurt you?
Well, no.
But he's made our
lives miserable.
But I only do what I have to do!
I always lose, so you can win.
You are heroes and I'm
always the bad guy.
(cries)
Bad!
♪ I was born to
be a monster ♪
♪ The fates gave
me no choice ♪
♪ I got the
monster's nose ♪
♪ And the monster's toes ♪
♪ And the monster's
gravelly voice ♪
♪ When you're born
to be a monster ♪
♪ What else can you do? ♪
♪ You've gotta grunt
and growl ♪
♪ And hunt and prowl ♪
♪ Like other monsters do ♪
♪ Someone's got
to be the ogre ♪
♪ Or who would heroes
have to fight? ♪
♪ And wouldn't you know,
it's just my luck ♪
♪ I fill the bill
just right ♪
♪ I was born to
be a monster ♪
♪ But I still
have a heart ♪
♪ So please don't hiss and
boo at me with scorn ♪
♪ It's not my fault ♪
♪ A monster, I was born ♪
So you see, I gotta
be the monster.
(All gasp)
Why don't you take him with you?
- I don't know...
- What do you think?
(sobs)
May hap,
we were wrong about you.
We're sorry.
(sobs loudly)
(All grunt and groan)
(All)
-Goodbye! -Farewell! -Farewell!
Goodbye!
(Ponies)
So long! Bye!
Goodbye, Robin.
I shall miss you.
I don't suppose we'll
ever meet again!
You'll see us all
sooner than you think.
We'll always be around.
Tally ho!
(door creaks and slams)
Well, I guess everything
will be back to normal soon.
Righto, everything will be
just ducky...
You miss him too, don't you?
Yes I--
Huh?
Oh! Look!
Megan left her books behind.
And the stories are back!
(gasps)
"The Adventures of Robin Hood."
Lofty, it's him!
And look! "Chaharazad's
Thousand-and-One Nights."
"Once upon a time, there was a
princess named Chaharazad. "
Robin Hood was right.
They will be around forever.