♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Danny)
Well, here's another fine mess
we've gotten ourselves into.
It's my fault.
I trusted Drog
and he led us into a trap.
It was a risk
worth taking, Danny.
Don't worry.
We're not beaten yet.
But midnight is not
far off, Megan.
And when it strikes,
we shall all be banished
to the Realm of Darkness.
I can't help,
but feel that the big bell
we found is important.
It has something to do
with Grogar's power.
I'm certain of it.
(door creaks and slams)
In you go, traitor.
(cackles)
He called you a traitor.
That means you didn't betray us.
A few Troggles
are still loyal to Grogar.
They told him
of my plan to help you.
Well, that wasn't very nice.
But most of my people
are fed up with Grogar.
They would help you
against him,
if you would give us
a new home in Ponyland.
You bet we would.
(All)
Oh, yes. We would. Why not?
But how can we get word
to the rest of the Troggles.
We can't escape this dungeon.
Good news, master.
The Moochick and the baby ponies
have been captured.
That means Ponyland is mine.
This calls for a celebration.
Tell the Troggles that anyone
not found celebrating
will be banished along with
the ponies at midnight.
Er...rh...right away, master.
Now, start the spell
that will banish the ponies
from Ponyland forever.
(thundering)
(crowd jubilating)
Wonder what
they're so happy about?
They're not.
They're just following
Grogar's orders.
(jubilation continues)
That's funny.
It sounds louder over here.
(jubilation continues)
And it gets louder
the higher I go.
It's loudest at this crack.
And there's fresh air
coming through.
If there were some way
to widen the crack,
something
we could force into it.
Barf!
Try this.
I'd rather pour it
in a crack than eat it.
If we could put the gruel into
the crack and make it bubble,
it would expand
and make the crack bigger.
I've got it!
Forget-Me-Not,
you and Peach Blossom,
carry the bucket
up to the crack.
(strenuous effort)
Okay.
Now Buttons,
you move the soup
from the bucket into the crack.
I'll try.
But everybody get out
from underneath, just in case.
Hurry,
We can't hold it much longer.
(Blossom)
Look out! Below!
Phew!
Fizzy, you've got to make
that stuff in the crack bubble.
Okay.
Hey, it's working.
Look out!
(screaming)
I'd say, good show.
Forget-Me-Not, come with us.
We'll find a way
to get the door open.
Hurry! We've got to find Bray
and get those keys from him.
Look, there's Bray!
(Megan)
Not so fast, Bray.
What?
Hey stop!
Hey, hey...
What are you doing?
Get away from me!
I'll take those.
(gasps)
Stop! Come back!
No!
Grogar's gonna be mad
when he hears about this.
Hee-haw!
Let's go everybody.
It's almost midnight.
(Grogar)
Escaped!
You fool!
It wasn't my fault.
If they get out of the city,
you will take their place.
(jubilation)
The ponies are free.
Now it's time
to set ourselves free.
(jubilation)
Help us against Grogar,
and you'll be free!
What do we do now?
We've got to reach
the gates before midnight.
Come on!
(clock ticking)
(ticking continues)
It's Grogar!
Boy, if it isn't one thing,
it's another.
I say! It looks like
we're trapped.
(Danny)
Somebody think of something.
I'm trying, but nothing
rings any bells!
Ring the bell!
That's it!
Excuse me, what was that?
The bell we found
in the hidden room.
Legend says
that when it's rung,
Grogar's power
will be destroyed.
It's our only chance.
North Star,
can you find your way
back to that bell in time?
A mere trifle, Megan.
(Megan)
Then let's go!
It's time
to ring in some changes.
♪ Ring out the old,
ring in the new ♪
♪ Time for a major
alteration's due ♪
♪ Soon enough
we all must sing ♪
♪ Let the bell of
freedom ring ♪
♪ Ring out the news,
speak loud and clear ♪
♪ Come on the day of
liberation's here ♪
♪ Soon the changes
will take wing ♪
♪ Let the bell of
freedom ring ♪
♪ Somehow I can't
help but feel ♪
♪ Any second now,
that bell will peel ♪
(bell rings)
♪ There goes the bell,
we won the fight ♪
♪ Sing out the song
of victory tonight ♪
♪ All the joy our
thoughts will bring ♪
♪ Let the bell of
freedom ring ♪
freedom ring ♪ ♪
(growls)
(thundering)
It's fading away.
But where are Megan
and North Star?
Look! Here they come!
You did it, Megan.
What happened to
Grogar and Bray?
They're gone,
back into the Realm of
Darkness with Tambelon.
(cheer and merriment)
(Megan)
Well, I hope you
and the rest of the Troggles
enjoy living in Ponyland, Drog.
I'm sure we will.
But I still can't believe
Grogar is really gone for good.
Well, it took him 500 years
to build the old bell
even with the Troggle's help.
So I don't think
he'll be back anytime soon.
Look!
You don't think
it's Grogar, do you?
Guess not.
(sighs)