♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
We better think of
something quick.
And this is one hot
bath we won't enjoy!
I wish I was not suffering
from a singular lack
of inspiration.
Wishing! Of course, there're
still two coins left.
Oops!
(coins cling)
Phew!
But which one will do the
trick without backfiring on us?
This is no time for
a equivocation.
Hit one quickly!
I wish we were as
light as a feather.
But only momentarily.
(both scream)
The wish worked!
Yeah! The wish worked!
(Megan chuckles)
This is fun.
Uh!
Bet Niblick's never seen a
treasure like this one.
Does it look like I
need another ruby?
(box slams)
Three tries is all you get.
But I'm not such a bad guy.
So I'm gonna let ya live.
On one condition!
Uhhh...what might that
be, Mr. Niblick?
GET OUTTA HERE! NOW!
(indistinct groaning)
Awww... Looks like we blew it.
I'll be happy to guide you
back to Ponyland, folks.
If that's where you're going.
Where else can we go?
I just hope the baby
Seaponies are okay.
It's all the water I can find.
Sorry!
Don't blame yourself, Shady.
There's no water anywhere.
Gotta be water some place.
I find some.
Baby Lofty, wait!
No water.
(crow caws)
Oops!
(glass breaks)
No water, Molly.
That's okay, baby, you tried.
(fire enkindles)
Something better happen soon.
I say look there!
I do believe it's a fire.
That wasn't exactly
what I had in mind.
I'll check it out.
It is a fire...coming this way!
We've got to evacuate
the nursery.
Hiya! Where're we going?
Ah, it's fun!
(giggles)
Whee!
Get the baby Seaponies too!
The rest of us can start
digging firebreaks.
Looks bad, Ribbon.
You can't stop it.
We'll fight it as
long as we can.
But tell the others to get
ready to abandon Dream Valley.
Oh, no!
Come on!
(Danny)
We better not wait
any longer, Ribbon.
We gotta leave!
All right, let's--
Look! Over there!
It looks like Megan
and the others!
Maybe they found a
way to make it rain!
(Megan)
What're we gonna do?
Can't stop it.
There's only one chance, Megan.
Try the last coin.
Maybe you can
wish the fire out.
It's worth a try.
I wish the fire was out!
It isn't working!
It must be the wrong
coin for that wish!
(coughs)
Wind Whistler! Am I
ever glad to see you?
Climb on, hurry!
Thanks for saving my life.
I can hardly do
otherwise, Megan.
I would risk anything
for a friend.
For friendship after all is the
most important treasure
there is.
Friendship!
The clasped hands of course!
Now, I know what to do!
Megan! Is there any hope for us?
I think so,
if there's still time!
Keep fighting the fire.
Whistler, fly faster than
you've ever flown before!
You heard her,
let's do what we can!
Where we going, Megan?
Back to Niblick's house.
Mr. Niblick, Mr. Niblick!
(door slams)
You again?
You gotta lot of nerve showin'
your face around here.
Wait! I have a perfect treasure
for youe
and it'll come from
one of your own coins!
This better be good or else...
It will be!
I hope, I wish...
(All scream)
Run for it! Run! Help! Let's go!
Oh! What a pit--
Hey!
Who asked ya?
I might as well see
what the inside is like,
though I know
I am going to regret it.
Incredible!
What did you do?
Have a bunch of ogres
down for the weekend?
Well... Maybe I did let it go...
A little...
Oh! You can say that again.
Why not open a window?
Or Seven...
(indistinct muttering)
(Megan gasps)
You!
This was your doing.
It-it seemed like a
good idea at that time.
A good idea?
It was a great idea!
- It was?
- Sure!
I didn't realize
how lonely I was.
And this place sure could use
someone who likes to clean!
I don't believe it.
What did you wish for, Megan?
Only the greatest treasure
of all, a friend.
(Niblick)
This guy's worth more than all
the magic coins in Ponyland.
Name your price?
Undo the effects of the coins,
starting with the weather spell.
You got it!
(thundering)
(singing in harmony)
Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo
(cheer and laughter)
It's so nice to have
everything back to normal.
You said it!
(bubbling)
I got my old bubbles back!
And we got our water back!
I-uh...I don't know
how to thank ya.
I mean this guy maybe a pain
when it comes to
keeping things neat,
but he...well, I never had a...
I know what you're
trying to say, Niblick.
Friendship is a wish come true!
♪ Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo ♪
♪ Friends, are a treasure ♪
♪ Friends, bring
such pleasure ♪
♪ Lifting spirits
up to the sky ♪
♪ Don't know what I'd
do without my friends ♪
♪ When you're
lonely, friends ♪
♪ They're the only certain
cure to shake off the blues ♪
♪ True with a friend you
never can lose ♪
♪ Of all treasures,
what do we choose ♪
♪ Friends, friends ♪
♪ Lifting spirits
up to the sky ♪
♪ Friends, friends ♪
♪ Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo ♪
♪ Friends, friends,
friends ♪