♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Raptorians cackling)
Must tell the little ponies!
(All)
Yeah, yeah! Tell Ponies!
Let's go! To Paradise Estate!
(All)
Tell 'em! Tell 'em! Let s go!
Yeah yeah,let s tell 'em!
(All)
Tell 'em! Tell 'em! Let s go!
Yeah yeah, tell 'em!
(Raptorians cackling)
Ooh ho ho ho ho hooo!
- Watch it!
- Oh! No!
- Ugh! Oof!
- Oof!
Oh boy! Soon we're
gonna have our own territory.
Yeah, more space than
we knows what to do with!
OK, let's move it!
We haven't got all day -
come on!
Hey, we're moving.
You needn't get rough.
Ow!
(Danny)
Geronimo!
(All squeal)
Danny!
Sorry, Danny is feeling
a little rambunctious today.
Today?
Come on, come on! Tell ponies!
We've got to tell them!
(All)
Tell ponies, tell ponies.
Gotta go to Paradise Estate.
(All)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Stop!
(chaos)
(bubbles)
Stop!
Oh no, not again!
Ugh!
(All)
Tell 'em, tell 'em.
Tell 'em, yeah, tell 'em.
What's with you guys?
(All)
Thank you! Yeah, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Thanks, thanks a lot. Thanks.
Well, what is it?
(breathing heavily)
Ponies kidnapped!
Yeah, ponies kidnapped!
(All)
Yeah, ponies kidnapped,
Yeah yeah kidnapped!
What do you mean,
the ponies have been kidnapped?
Raptorians come with nets
and take them away!
(All gasp)
Which ponies?
Lickety Split, Heart Throb
and Gusty.
(All gasp)
Oh no!
Well, which way
did they go?
The Black Mountains!
We must form a search party
and follow their trail
while it's still fresh.
Uhh, Magic Star, Paradise
and North Star,
you come with me
and the Bushwoolies.
The rest of you stay here
in case they manage to escape
and make their way back here.
(Bushwoolies)
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Be careful.
Hurry back!
There must be something I can do
that no other pony can do.
There must be something!
My question is why?
What do they hope to gain?
Where in the world
have you been?
Have you heard, have you heard
about their kidnapping?
We're so worried.
What kidnapping?
A dozen Raptorians abducted
Lickety Split, Heart Throb
and Gusty
and took them with them
to the Black Mountains,
the Black Mountains.
Megan formed a rescue party
and went after them.
If only I hadn't been
so overly sensitive.
I should have stayed to listen
to what the other ponies
had to say.
But Shady,
you had no idea
that something
would happen to them.
But maybe I could
have helped them escape,
or I could have run for help,
or... Oh, dear!
Shady, it's not your fault.
Now I'm not only useless,
but I'm a deserter besides.
Deserter?
Oh, no! Not that, Shady.
No, never!
Wait a second, I don't get it -
what s she talking about?
(sobs)
Shady!
Shady! Shady,
come back!
Shady!
♪ All wrong, all wrong ♪
♪ All my plans always
go all wrong ♪
♪ All right, all right ♪
♪ Everything's gonna
be all right ♪
♪ All wrong, all wrong ♪
♪ I'm a klutz
and I don't belong ♪
♪ All right, all right ♪
♪ There is always
some hope in sight ♪
♪ I try to be
so helpful ♪
♪ As practical as salt ♪
♪ But everything I do
goes haywire ♪
♪ Shady it's not your fault ♪
♪ No one in the world
is perfect ♪
♪ It's time you
saw the light ♪
♪ You mean to say
I'm not all wrong ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ All right ♪
- Look!
- Bushwoolie fur?
It must be their
shedding season.
Maybe we better
follow the trail.
And we can be extra help
for everyone
in case they need it.
That's a brave idea.
Let's go.
Really?
You think so?
Ooh..welcome, welcome.
(laughs)
Ooh! Welcome, welcome!
Ooh! It's so beautiful.
It's perfect.
Just what I needed
to repair my cloak.
But first, the hair
must be absolutely squeaky clean
through the wash with them.
Look! over there.
It's Gusty's headband.
Our first clue.
(All)
Way to go, way to go,
way to go North Star?
The ponies must be around
here somewhere.
Spread out!
- Clues, clues..
- We want clues.
Hey! Megan.
Come here, quick!
This must be where
the Raptorians took the ponies.
So, what are we waiting for?
Come on! Help me push it.
Uh...It's no use.
We'll have to find
another way in.
But how?
Hey! our grand-daddies
used to live in these caverns.
We can find a way in there.
Wonderful!
(All)
Alright! Yeah! Yeah!
Wonderful.
Now, let me see.
Ah-ha this way.
(All)
Yeah, yeah, yeah this way!
No...
Thatta' way.
Thatta' way, thatta' way,
yeah, yeah, yeah!
Which way?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, thatta' way.
Uh... But then again...
Mmm...
Move it, move it, move it.
(Raptorians cackle)
(magical incantation)
Kazim, Kazam, Kazoom...
(All gasp)
Ooh dear, this cloak
is practically worthless now.
Do something quick!
Not so tight!
Be sure they get good and clean.
Yes, yes.
Your most lovely highness.
(machinery creaks)
(switch clicks)
(boiler whistles)
(wheels ratchet)
(ratcheting continues)
Atchoo!
Soon, we'll have a better place
to live than this cramped dump
and we won't be needing
no Porcina, no more.
(All laugh)
If only I could do something
to save Heart Throb,
Lickety-Split, and Gusty
all by myself.
I owe them that much.
We'll figure out something.
I don't want
anybody else's help.
Well, I am coming
along with you, just in case.
Okay.
(laugh)
Snip! Snip! Snip!
Ooh..! Do you think
they'll hurt us?
No, Heart Throb.
Look, all they want is our hair.
After that, they'll let us go.
I don't know, Gusty.
I think they want
more than that.
That's right.
This won't be
the end of it my pretties,
not even when we have
harvested your lovely dresses.
Why, then your job
is just beginning
and then your precious Ponyland
will never be the same.
What do you mean?
Why, thanks to your hair
Porcina will turn
all of Ponyland into glass.
(All gasp)