♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Bushwoolies)
Oh, boy! this is fun. Fun, yeah!
(All)
Fun, Yeah. Yeah, yeah! Fun, fun.
Gosh, that looks like fun.
Come, join us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Join us.
Ouch
(All)
Yeah! Ouch, ouch.
Ah, how about tag instead?
What's tag?
(Bushwoolies)
Yeah, what's tag, what's tag?
Huh! How do you play it?
It's easy, I'll be "it".
Everyone runs away
from whoever is "it" and...
Wait!
I didn't tell you the rules.
I'm supposed to tag you.
Was it something I said?
Well, excuse me!
Aah
Hah!
Oh, gosh,
I'm terribly sorry.
Huh!
Can I help?
I really didn't mean
to get in your way.
Thank you, but NO!
This is not a job for amateurs!
If you're finished,
we could play a game.
Any game, your choice.
A game?
I've got better things to do
with my time than play games!
Hi, Fizzy.
(Gasps)
Ah! Oh...
What are you doing?
I've lost Ribbon...
...or is it Galaxy?
(Giggles)
Well, oh, shoot.
I don't even remember
where home base is.
You're playing hide and seek?
Oh, do let me play too!
For sure!
We'll start over.
Olly Olly oxen free!
Sweet Stuff wants to play!
She said she'd be "it"!
Huh?
Gosh,
I didn't say that exactly...
Sweet Stuff didn't
really say that, Fizzy.
Uh...well,
I uh, was thinking that
when you read
my mind Ribbon, but...
That's all right.
I'll be "it".
Okay, everybody.
I'll count to twenty,
and then come looking for you.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13...
18, 19, 20!
Okay, here I come,
ready or not!
(Squirrel)
Excuse me!
Oh, no!
It isn't bad enough
to stand on my acorns.
You have to lie on them too?
Shhhh!
I'm playing a game and I...
A game?
You call this a game?
You don't understand.
Well, hello-oo!
Hi! I guess,
I'm "it" now, huh?
That's right!
18...19...20.
Okay, here I come!
I hear somebody.
Huh?
Hmm...
(giggles)
I guess hide and seek just
isn't a game for Earth Ponies.
Gusty's right.
I'm not good enough.
Look, everybody,
let's make a new rule
that you can't wink in or out.
No, no! I don't want to spoil
the game for the rest of you.
(singing in harmony)
Shoo-bee-doo
shoop-shoop-bee-doo
Wanna play with us?
A game?
Oh, that would be great.
Oh,
but I can't swim very well.
Oh, you can play
right where you are.
(giggles)
Go Sunshower!
That's it,
hit it, Water Lily.
Get that.
Ugh! Oof!
Oh, I get it now.
I'm being used as a goal post.
I'm sorry, but I don't
wanna play anymore.
Okay, these are
the lists of items to find.
Choose a partner,
and the first team to return
with the most items wins.
You have until sunset.
A purple cone, a sea shell...
I trust
it will not be difficult.
Oh, I know where to find that!
(indistinct chatter)
Want to join the
scavenger hunt, Sweet Stuff?
Well...
Of course you do.
Now who needs a partner?
Whizzer?
Come on,
you can be with me.
What is this last item, Megan?
Something that is one
even when it is many...
But that is illogical.
You'll know it when you see it,
and that's all I'm gonna say.
Next on the list
is a sea shell.
Let me get the shell.
I haven't had a chance
to find anything yet.
You can find it, but you're
gonna have to find it fast!
I'll find it,
and I'll find it...first.
Oh!
It's okay,
I've found the sea shells.
Now what's next?
A book with a red cover.
Okay, let's go back
to Paradise Estate
and check the library.
I can't keep up
with you, Whizzer.
You go on by yourself.
You go get the book then,
I'll get the next item.
No, I'll just hold you back.
You go on.
I'm sorry!
I'm no good at anything.
I think I'd just better go home.
(Bushwoolies)
Help! Help!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
help, help, help!
How'd you get up there?
Bushwoolies playing tag.
Ran into Truly.
Yeah, yeah! Ran into Truly!
Smack into her.
Asked if we could help...
Yeah, yeah, yeah
help, help!
And she said
we could go fly a kite.
Yeah, fly a kite, fly a kite!
Hang on, Bushwoolies!
Okay, get ready to let go
of the string.
No, no...there's too many of you
to catch at once.
Let go of the string
one by one.
One. By. One?
What's that? Huh?
Yeah, what's that?
Okay,
just don't go anywhere.
Bushwoolies
not going anywhere.
Yeah, nowhere,
nowhere, yeah.
All of you do
everything like you're one.
Weee Weee.
Yeah Weee.
Hey!
You're the treasure!
We're the treasure?
Yeah, we're the treasure!
Yeah, we're rich, we're rich,
we're rich, we're rich!
We're rich, we're rich,
If you come with me,
we can win the treasure hunt.
Uh-oh! We have to hurry.
Come on.
(All Bushwoolies)
Oh, boy! Oh, boy! Oh, boy! Yay!
Well, you have the most treasure
so far--
everything but the last riddle.
Marvelous.
Hey, wait you come over and see
the stuff in this pile, Megan!
They're all real treasures.
Where's Sweet Stuff, Whizzer?
I thought she was your partner.
Ah... well, um, actually, well,
she thought it would be
better to separate.
But I bet Sweet Stuff
and I can still win.
If she gets back in time.
Oh, here she comes now.
And look who's with her.
Oh, wow! Look over there.
Hey, what are the Bushwoolies
doing here?
They're not part of the game.
Oh, yes they are.
They're the last item.
- I don't believe it!
- What?
(Wind Whistler)
Impossible.
Congratulations, Sweet Stuff!
You've won the game.
You figured out that
the bushwoolies are...
...Something that is one,
even when it is many.
(Bushwoolies)
Congratulations!
That's great! Yeah! Wonderful.
Dig in, everybody.
Oh, yeah. I love Ice cream!
Love ice cream, oh boy.
Ice cream was for eating,
not playing in.
We're supposed to eat ice cream?
Yeah. Not to eat?
Not in here?
Uh-oh, we're sorry.
Uh-oh, sorry, sorry,
didn't know! Yeah, sorry!
Don't worry.
It's all right if you like to do
things differently from us!
♪ Don't be upset, ♪
♪ If you're not like
folks you've met, ♪
♪ Be glad you are
who you are, ♪
♪ No need to frown, ♪
♪ Don't go putting
yourself down, ♪
♪ Be glad you are
who you are, ♪
♪ Don't think
you're weird, ♪
♪ 'Cause no one else
is like you, ♪
♪ It doesn't mean
you won't go far. ♪
♪ Everyone is special, ♪
♪ Everyone a star, ♪
♪ Be glad you are
who you are, ♪
♪ Why get depressed, ♪
♪ 'cause we're different
from the rest, ♪
♪ Be glad you are
who you are! ♪
♪ No need to pout, ♪
♪ Or to feel like
we're left out. ♪
♪ Be glad you are
who you are, ♪
♪ Don't think
you're weird, ♪
♪ 'Cause so one else
is like you. ♪
♪ It doesn't mean
you won't go far. ♪
♪ Each of us is special, ♪
♪ Each of us a star, ♪
♪ Be glad you are... ♪
♪ We're glad we are... ♪
♪ We're glad we are
what we are. ♪