♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(screams)
We heard a scream,
what happened?
My hoof! Look at my hoof!
The beautiful polish
has chipped.
All that fuss over
chipped hoof polish?
I gave you the ancient recipe
for polish,
made from glitter scent.
But did you use it?
Then this is your fault,
Starburst.
I did use your polish.
Some Princess Ponies don't know
as much as they think they know.
I know enough to be Queen.
It takes more than just
knowledge to be the Queen.
Right! It takes the ability to
appreciate the beauty in things,
which I have.
What?...No.
To be the Queen,
a Princess Pony has to have--
A knowledge of every
part of one's domain.
That's not enough.
Starburst is right.
A Queen needs to have
a very special talent,
for understanding
her subjects...
like me.
No! no!
That is not what I was
going to say.
(panting)
Hi! What's going on?
(all)
I'm going to be the Queen.
Oh! Some shortcut.
We've been walking for hours.
Okay, let's try again.
Which way leads to Dream Valley?
-This way. -That way. -Yeah.
-That way. -You bet.
Ah! Right. Okay.
What was that?
-A light.
-It was a light.
-Yeah, it was. -I saw it.
-Yeah, bright.
Come on. Let's go!
This isn't Dream Valley.
-No, not Dream Valley.
-No it isn't.
-Not Dream Valley.
-No.
Of course,
it isn't Dream Valley.
What is it then?
And who're you?
This is the Royal Paradise.
Only royalty lives here.
I am Princess Royal Blue,
a guardian of the magic wands.
Really?
-Guardian?
-Oh, my!
-Imagine that.
-Wands? -Wands, yeah.
It's true.
We are the Princess Ponies.
And it is our duty to protect
the magic wands.
And it is your duty to come
and judge the contest.
-Contest?
-Oh, boy, contest!
-What's a contest?
-Oh boy!
What contest?
The contest to decide
who will be Queen.
You shall be the judge.
You'll probably pick me.
Why?
Because I'm the best qualified!
(All)
-What? You are not.
-What makes you think you are?
(All)
-You have some nerve! -You're so
rude! - I don't believe you.
♪ By right, I should be Queen ♪
♪ Look what I can do ♪
♪ Take a day,
all dull and gray ♪
♪ And change it into blue ♪
♪ By right, I should be Queen ♪
♪ No one can compare ♪
♪ One, two, three
and you will see ♪
♪ Flowers everywhere ♪
♪ Watch me make
red robins blue jays ♪
the north wind blow ♪
♪ I'll turn one jay
into two jays ♪
♪ Presto, chango,
hail and snow ♪
♪ By right,
I should be Queen ♪
♪ Anyone can see ♪
♪ The royal crown
and great renown ♪
♪ Are meant for only-- ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ No me ♪
♪ No me... ♪
Who should be Queen?
Well, Gee, I don't think
any of you really...
I mean
you're all so good.
Let's let the Bushwoolies
decide.
(evil laugh)
The time has come.
Sludge!
Yes, master.
Prepare for attack.
I want those magical wands, now.
Yes, master, right away, master.
Your wish is my command, master.
I should be Queen.
No, I should.
Whoever heard of the Queen
with dirty hooves?
I can fly and you can't.
So I should be in charge.
Gee, I remember
Paradise telling us
the legend
of the Princess Ponies,
and how they guard the
magic of Ponyland.
I never thought they'd act
like this.
(All)
-Yeah, yeah, me too. -I agree.
-Never. -Yeah.
(tremoring)
(Spike gasps)
It feels like an earthquake.
Oh, my!
- What's happening?
- Oh!
(evil laugh)
It's Lavan,
ruler of the Lava Demons.
Run!
-Run. -Run. -Run.
-Run to the palace. -Run.
-Run!
-Hurry, run!
(evil laugh)
(both gasp)
I'll take these, ladies.
(cackles)
Give me your wand.
I'll fly out of reach.
Flying won't help you.
Ah!
(cackles)
Hey! You can't do that.
(laughs)
Is that the best you can do?
Yahh!
Hey, what happened?
-Where'd he go?
-Where'd we go? -Yeah. Go.
They're gone.
Our magic wands are gone.
If Lavan tries to use the wands,
he might upset the magical
foundation of Ponyland.
Master, I know
it's not my place to ask,
but what are you going to do
with the magic wands?
They have the ability
to transform me,
into a crystal beam
of lava's power!
The power to do anything.
What a wonderful thought to be
a beautiful crystal creature...
You are a fool, Sludge.
Beauty does not matter,
only power matters.
Let the transformation begin.
(evil laugh)
(yelling in pain)
Something's wrong.
(Sludge yells)
Gwaaaaah!
If Lilac would just get
her hooves up out of the dirt
and get on her way, we'd...Ah!
(tremoring)
Now what?
What is it, Megan?
I don't know.
Whatever it is, it's bad.
I can sense that.
Hey! What's going on?
(screams)
Fizzy, this is no time
for jokes.
I didn't mean it, Megan.
It just happened.
Aaahh!
(squishing)
(wind howling)
It was warm a second ago,
what's going on?
I figure that someone
or something has upset,
the magical powers of Ponyland.
Paradise! The fireworks
came from that way.
Right away, Megan.
I'll go investigate.
Sludge! Ready my lava board.
Mm-mm-my Lord?
The Ponies, fool.
I must capture
the Princess Ponies,
to learn how to use
the wand's magic.
(thud)
(groans in pain)
What happened?
What we're afraid of...
Ponyland's magic
is breaking down.
Okay, someone's
got to get Megan.
And it's got to be you.
(Lavan growls)
What are you doing?
Head for Paradise Estate,
find Megan.
The Bushwoolie will show you
the way.
(evil laugh)
You are all my prisoners.