♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Locket laughs)
Gotchya now, Locket.
Oh, this is exciting!
Faster, Locket.
Oh! Oh!
Catch it, Twilight.
Oh! I just don't know
who to cheer for.
(chuckles)
You'll never catch me!
(All chuckle)
Tag, you're it!
(chuckles)
(All)
Whoa! Whoa!
What was that?
Some kind of huge bird, I think.
And it looked like
something was chasing it.
But what would dare to chase
a bird that big?
Ooh! Come back here you!
Oh, please, please come back!
You're my last hope!
Look!
Who is that?
Oh, all is lost!
All is lost!
The poor thing.
Oh, oh, we simply must help him.
Come on, girls.
We'd better go see what
this is all about.
I have a feeling
we're gonna find out...
whether we want to or not.
Oh, woe is me.
Who are you?
You have wings.
Who you are doesn't matter.
Come with me!
Come on let's go!
Don't waste time.
Come on you...
But where are we going?
And why?
And who are you?
My name is Garth.
But does it matter
to you where we're going?
You have to come!
It matters to us!
We can't help you
if we don't know the problem.
Right, of course.
Well, my problem
is that my true love
is in an enchanted slumber
in a floating castle
that I can't catch.
Oh! How romantic!
You see my problem?
Well, actually...no.
It's like this.
Listen, can we at least get
moving while I tell it?
I'm in a hurry, you know.
Of course, we can, darling.
Oh, you poor tragic thing.
Let's go.
So, why do you need us?
To reach the floating castle.
See, my true love
is named Ariel.
Her father was a wizard
who cast a spell
that put her to sleep
in a floating castle.
(gasps)
Well, come on!
We don't have all day!
He did this, so only the man
who is in love enough
to brave the dangers
of the floating castle
reach the chamber wherein
she sleeps, kiss and awaken her,
will be good enough
to marry her.
Listen.
Wouldn't we reach this floating
castle faster if we flew?
Well, of course, we would.
Will you fly with me
and tell me about...
about your true love
and what you would do for her?
♪ For my true love,
I would climb a mountain ♪
♪ I would cross the desert ♪
♪ Or sail the ocean blue ♪
♪ For my true love,
I would face an army ♪
♪ I would fight a dragon ♪
♪ Or cut him right in two ♪
♪ I'd travel
to the stars above ♪
♪ If I were asked
by my true love ♪
♪ My true love ♪
♪ So come what may ♪
♪ I will go the distance ♪
♪ Let it hail and thunder ♪
♪ And still I will
come through ♪
♪ There is nothing
I won't do ♪
♪ For my true love ♪
♪ My true love ♪
(Heart Throb pants)
Is it much farther
to this castle?
(Garth)
It's here somewhere.
It moves around, so we'll have
to search a little, okay?
We'll find it, don't worry.
Won't we, Locket?
Locket? Locket!
Hey! I found something.
Look!
(gasps in amazement)
(Garth)
There it is!
(Locket)
It's certainly large.
How do we get in?
I don't know.
I've never been
this close before.
The legend says there
are challenges to be faced.
Well, then, let's go face them.
Hey! Where'd it go?
Did you see that?
I told you it moves.
Well, so do I.
(frustrated)
It's too fast for me.
Locket, you try.
It's pretty high
up, Heart Throb.
If anyone can go that
high, it's you, Locket.
You can do it.
(pants)
I have just got to sit down.
Come on, Twilight.
Wish me luck.
Go get it Locket!
(All)
Hurray!
Oh, this isn't going to work.
Of course, it will, somehow.
Not a chance.
Come on, Garth, cheer up!
We'll find a way in.
No, we won't.
You ponies can't fly fast
enough or high enough.
We can fly faster
and higher than you can.
Come on, everyone!
Make up now!
We all have to work together.
Work together!
That's it!
If we approach
from different sides,
one of us will be able to land.
Oh! That's brilliant!
Yeah!
We could do it like this.
Ready?
Go!
Hurray! We did it!
Let's go!
Move in and land!
(spewing)
(both gasp)
Ah! Whoa!
What was that?
Part of the wizard's spell,
I guess.
It's supposed to scare us away.
Well, it didn't work.
Hang on!
Let us pass.
(both gasp and scream)
Ah! Oh!
Are you all right?
You're soaked.
I'm fine.
Maybe we'd better look
for another way in.
Let me try from up here
at one of the towers.
Hah! This'll be easy!
(growls angrily)
Easy, did you say?
(growls)
It's hopeless.
We'll never get into the castle.
You must never say "never."
Remember your love.
She's there waiting
to be rescued.
Now come on!
We need a new plan.
Didn't you have some rope
in that sack of yours?
Yes, lots of it.
I thought so.
Now here's my plan.
(Garth)
Hurray!
(Garth laughs)
We've got it!
(All scream)
Whoa! Whoa!
This isn't working!
(All scream)
(screams)