♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
♪ I'm a talkin' little pony ♪
♪ Knight Shade is my name ♪
♪ You say
you'd like to meet me ♪
♪ I'd say that's a shame ♪
♪ Cause if your feet
won't moonwalk ♪
Baby Heart Throb,
please, sit down.
Knight Shade, Knight Shade!
Woooo!
♪ Do the
moonwalk, pony do ♪
I can't hear a thing.
And I can't see, either.
Let me take care of this.
Baby Heart Throb, please,
sit down and be quiet!
♪ Do the moonwalk, ponies! ♪
♪ Put that sparkle
in your shoes ♪
♪ Do the moonwalk ♪
(laughs)
Well,
I guess that cooled her down!
I wasted a perfectly
good ice cream cone on you.
Ohhh.. lost ice cream cone..
Then we get another one
for Lickety-Split!
Oh! We come too!
But I promised your mothers
I'd bring you right back.
Oh, come on, Megan.
They'll only be gone a minute.
Well.. okay,
but come right back.
Promise!
C'mon, c'mon,
hurry hurry hurry!
Oh, my, my...
what have we here?
Ah, my fair young maidens,
how do you do?
(giggles)
My name is Zeb,
what might yours be?
(gulps)
Um, Baby Heart Throb.
Baby Half Note.
Baby Lofty.
Gee, are you workin' shell?
Not really.
I am Knight Shade's
personal manager.
(gasp excitedly)
Knight Shade?!
My my, you must be fans..!
How'd you like to meet him?
Would we?
Then, come along, my lovelies,
I'll take you to meet
the great star himself.
It's a pleasure
to meet all of you.
Can we come back and
see you tomorrow, Knight Shade?
Oh, sorry.
We're movin' on right away.
Aww, why you have to go?
Oh, ugh, tomorrow we have to
play in a village called,
Rosedale!
Ye, ye, Knight Shade!
Perhaps our new friends would
like a tour of the campgrounds
before we move on?
Ah, er, sorry
I can't accompany you,
but I've got some
business' to attend to.
Well,
okay Zeb, we won't take long.
(sighs)
We're gonna have to go
get 'em, Molly.
The rest of you,
wait for us here.
(door knocks)
Hi, we're looking for
three baby Ponies.
Have you seen them?
Well, yes, I have, they were
here just a little while ago.
I sent them home
to their mothers.
You did! Oh, good.
Thanks for your help.
No problem.
(laughs)
No problem at all.
They went back
to Paradise Estate.
What? Where's
my ice cream cone?
Never mind, Lickety-Split.
Come on, guys.
Let's go make sure the babies
got back home alright.
So, what do you think
of our little set-up, eh?
Nice, very nice!
Say, you three don't have any
musical talents yourselves,
do you?
Oh, I do! I wanna be
backup singer for Knight Shade.
(giggles)
No kidding.. You want to
sing backup for Knight Shade.
Well,
I'm very flattered.
And Baby Half Note sing
better than Baby Heart Throb.
(singing out of tune)
Do-re-mi-fa-so-la-tiii-tii-doo!
That was very nice!
But, wouldn't you be better off
tryin' it together?
Rather than as rivals?
♪ Bright lights, how we
love bright lights ♪
See how much better you can do
when you work together?
So, you wanna
join the tour, huh?
Make up your minds quickly,
we're getting ready to move on!
(All)
YES!
They're not here and they're not
in the nursery..
Where can they be?
I don't know, but here come
Heart Throb and Lofty.
We've got to tell them.
Tell us what?
That.. the babies are gone.
The babies!
(freaks out)
Take it easy, Heart Throb.
You mean you lost
them at the concert?
Lemme explain while
we go back to look for them.
Megan, what do you think
has happened to our babies?
Do you think they could have
been kidnapped by Knight Shade?
That monster!
I'm going
to go after him right now.
No, Lofty.
We'll have a better chance
of finding them
if we go back to Paradise Estate
and organize search parties.
That's right,
the Baby Ponies are missing,
but we're going to find them.
Lofty, why don't you lead
the main search party?
Okay, Whizzer,
you can carry messages.
Now, Galaxy, you come with us.
Fizzy, you go with
the other group.
♪ Bright lights,
how I love bright lights ♪
♪ Pretty to see,
shine one on me ♪
♪ Bright lights,
how I love bright lights ♪
♪ All in a row, look
how they glow ♪
♪ It's so much fun,
I like it a lot ♪
♪ Singing and dancing,
up here in the spot ♪
♪ Bright lights, how we
love bright lights ♪
♪ We all agree,
all of us three ♪
♪ It's bright lights... ♪
♪ Bright lights... ♪
♪ Bright lights...♪
♪ For me..♪
♪ Dee-lee-dee,
dee-lee-dee, dee-dee ♪
♪ Bright lights ♪
♪ dee-lee-dee,
dee-lee-dee.. ♪
♪ Bright lights... ♪
(gasp and pant)
That was great!
Why don't you take a break?
Woah...!
You alright, Baby Half Note?
Feel kinda dizzy...
You've probably just had a
little too much excitement
for one day.
Oh, y-yeah, yeah, Zeb.
That's right.
Uh, maybe you'd all
better take a nap.
Don't feel so good myself.
Me either.
Look sick!
All pale!
Like ghosts!
Feel sick... too sick to fly.
Baby Lofty!
Baby Lofty, your shadow.
Your shadow is gone.
All shadows gone!
(gasps)
Where is shadows?
Hello! I'm Camembert, the Mayor
of Muensterville.
How can I help you?
Hello, Mr. Bert.
We're looking for a musician
called Knight Shade.
Knight Shade,
you say..
Knight Shade, Knight Shade..
Well, have you seen him?
Possibly, possibly..
Yes or no? We really
need to know where he is.
Well, you're
not going to find out.
(lever creaks)
(gasps)
(all scream)
Oh, how'll we
ever find our babies now?
Ah...what's wrong?
(crying)
You tricked us, stole shadows.
Not our friend made us sick!
Now give shadows back!
Baby Lofty right!
No, no..
Knight Shade no thief!
Ah, well, uh..
(laughs) Somebody stole your
shadows, eh?
That's some joke!
No joke! Is true!
You laugh, we go home.
Where you goin', babies?
(gasp)
(laughs)
You know, you
shouldn't be out after dark,
alone..
(laughs) Yeah.
Somethin' bad
might happen to ya!
(gasp again)
(sniff and cry)