♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(laughs)
(Evil laugh)
Gusty!
That rock-thing's
gonna be plum sorry
he messed with our Gusty...
She is beyond help.
Logic clearly dictates
that we save ourselves.
Gosh, Wind Whistler,
how could you just go off
and leave poor Gusty?
What else would you
expect from somebody
with no feelings, Buttons?
No, Truly,
Wind Whistler's right,
we've gotta go on without Gusty.
Well, whatever we're gonna do,
let's snap it up.
Bye-bye, Gusty!
We'll be back!
She knows, Truly.
She knows.
Woah!
Track 'em!
Y'know, Gusty was on
the right track after all.
This one's for you, Gusty!
Buttons, don't!
Betcha can't catch me!
Oh Yeah?!
Another one?
Huh? Where'd she go?
Yoo-hoo!
Over here.
Hey, there she is.
She's drawing them off.
To the Mountains, then, quickly!
No, this way!
(groans)
Oh, I hope
Buttons is okay!
Oh, I'm sure
she's fine.
Buttons! Y'all did it!
It doesn't take
much to outsmart a rock.
Okay.
Now all we have to do is
find this Eminence guy.
The Moochick said if we go to
the Purple Mountains,
we couldn't miss him.
Greetings!
Uh.. Excuse me,
whoever you are,
but do you know
where we can find
His Elevated Eminence?
(laughs)
You're standing on him.
Remarkable!
This entire mountain
is a living, sentient being.
Greetings,
Your Elevated Eminence!
Uh.. yes, greetings,
Your Eminence.
We've come to ask
for your help.
You see, Crunch the Ro--
Oh, Crunch!
He is definitely out of control.
And it's all my fault.
You see, I needed a guard
to protect the Heartstone,
which is the magical gem
that gives me feelings.
I created Crunch the Rockdog
to protect the gem,
but I neglected to put any
heart into Crunch himself,
accidentally creating a cold,
ferocious beast!
But I discovered
my mistake too late.
To make him indestructible,
I had put a piece of
Black Lava Rock,
from the roiling depths
of the Volcano of Gloom,
into his collar.
It gives Crunch the power
to turn anything to stone!
There's only one thing
powerful enough to defeat him...
the Heartstone!
You must take it
and stop Crunch!
Well, I.. guess that doesn't
sound so difficult.
Where is the Heartstone,
anyway?
Deep within me.
And, how do we,
uh, get there?
I'll guide you.
But, I'm not exactly certain
what will happen
when the Heartstone
is removed.
W-what could possibly happen?
Which way?
To the left.
One more jaunt to the right
and you're there.
It's beautiful!
Take it, Megan!
Ooh..
Maybe I shouldn't...
Go ahead, my dear.
Which way, Your Eminence?
(screams)
Uh-oh!
(All yell)
Careful, Megan!
Give me my Heartstone!
What's the matter with him?
If His Eminence,
gets his feelings
from the Heartstone..
..Then without it, he's turning
into a major-league grouch!
Run!
Hurry!
This way!
- Hurry!
- This way!
Come on, let's go!
No! That way!
(cough)
(coughs)
Look!
(roars)
I've found you.
Who wants to be
turned to stone first?
You've gone too far
this time, Rockdog.
No, Truly!
No, Truly, don't go!
Stay here!
Go ahead.
Huh? Go ahead?
What are you
talking about?
What's the matter with you?
You really
don't like anyone, do you?
I mean it! Go ahead!
I don't care
what you do with her.
You're crazy
if you think I'll buy that.
I'm perfectly serious.
I've been surrounded by these
romantic idiots for so long,
it is refreshing
to find one such as yourself.
Wind Whistler!
How could you?
Pay no attention
to them, Crunch!
You really don't care
what I do to her?
That sentimental fool?
Certainly not.
Good, cause
I'm gonna turn her to stone!
Haha! I thought so!
You do care, don't you?
Wait!
I'll prove I'm on your side.
By giving you your next victim.
Yeah, that's it, Wind Whistler,
bring me to him.
The Heartstone!
Please, Heartstone,
do something.
No!
(yaps)
It worked!
She's alright!
(cheer)
Hey you guys,
look, it's me!
Hooray, it's Gusty!
I knew you wouldn't turn
against us, Wind Whistler.
Yeah, yeah! We're okay,
we're okay!
Yeah, yeah, fine!
I feel good!
Hooray! We found you!
(laughing)
Stop laughing! Stop cheering!
Why are you so happy?
There's nothing
to be happy about.
Stop it or I'll bite ya.
I bet all he needs
is a little heart.
Yeah, then
he'd be a nice puppy.
(yaps)
Now hold still!
Look..!
I can't believe
how happy he looks!
Well, of course he does!
(yaps)
Well, I guess we'd better get
this back to His Eminence
before he turns
into a permanent grump!
♪ It's wonderful
to have a heart ♪
when you can care ♪
♪ It's wonderful
when feelings start, ♪
♪ and the feelings
in your heart ♪
♪ Are the kind
you wanna share ♪
♪ Discovering
you have a heart ♪
♪ Makes the gloom in
your soul depart ♪
♪ You smile
up at the sun ♪
♪ For a new life
has begun ♪
♪ It's wonderful
to have a heart ♪
♪ Discovering
you have a heart ♪
♪ Makes the gloom in
your soul depart ♪
♪ You smile
up at the sun ♪
♪ For a new life
has begun ♪
♪ It's wonderful
to have a heart ♪
Thank you
for all your help!
I'm pleased that Crunch
now has a heart of his very own.
Goodbye! Goodbye, Eminence!
Bye bye!
Wind Whistler, uh, we're sorry
we said you had no feelings.
And we, uh, we wanna
thank you for doing
what you did back there.
Why? Logic alone dictated
my actions.
It would have been
too much trouble to carry
three heavy stone statues
all the way home.
Just kidding!