♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Rooooaaaghhhr!
Our beloved Valley is no more,
Megan.
We'll never save it now.
There's still time,
Rosedust.
All we have to do is
get past Ahhg.
That's all?
If we would have done something
about the witches
in the first place,
this never would have happened.
We'll find a way to get the
Sunstone back in place,
you'll see.
(Stonebacks snorting)
That's it.
The Stonebacks.
What about the Stonebacks?
With their help,
we can tunnel under Ahhg,
and get into the valley
that way.
What do you say, Stonebacks?
Can you do it?
(snorts)
Come on! We've got to
go where he can't see us.
(snorts)
Come on, Flutter Ponies.
We can help too.
(snorts)
I don't hear the tinkle
of Utter Flutter any more.
(Laughs)
That's 'cause
Ahhgy's doing his job.
Nobody's getting into
this valley now.
To the setting sun, and the end
of Flutter Valley.
Soon it will be ours.
There must be something
we can do
to stop this from happening.
We've tried everything.
And I'm all out of surprises.
That's a surprise.
If only Megan were here,
she'd know what to do.
If only we had more help,
we could do it.
Megan.
Megan, we're here.
- Yeah, we're here.
- We're here.
Hi, Megan.
Hello, Baby Cuddles.
Is there still time?
Just. But we
need everyone's help.
We can help.
Yeah,
we're good diggers.
- Real good.
- Yeah, good.
- So are we.
- No, we aren't.
What about the Stonebacks?
(snorts)
(blows raspberries)
I told them
they want to be friends,
but it may take a while.
No, right now
we all have to work together.
Together?
With Stonebacks?
Yes, with Stonebacks!
It's our only chance.
Start digging.
We did it, everybody!
We did it!
Huh? Roooooooaaaaaaghhhr!
(cheers)
What was that?
Look.
It's the Flutter Ponies.
No, Flutter Valley was
almost mine.
I was so close.
Come on!
No, you can't do this.
Flutter Valley's mine.
- Megan.
- Let us out.
Blast it, Flutter Ponies.
Gee, are we ever glad
to see you.
Same here,
Fizzy.
Come on! Let's get the Sunstone
back where it belongs.
(All)
Pull! Pull! Pull! Pull!
Good work, Flutter Ponies.
You're getting it.
Just a little more.
Hurry, it's almost sunset.
(cheers)
What's that?
It's Bumble and her swarm.
Oh no!
It can't be.
What are we gonna do?
(buzz)
No, Bumble.
Don't do it.
Out of my way, Sting.
I want that Sunstone.
Look out, Sting.
Oof!
Uhh!
Leave the Flutter Ponies alone.
The Sunstone is theirs.
But I want it too.
It grows flowers with
all that delicious nectar.
You're fat and greedy
and selfish, Bumble.
You only think of yourself.
I am not fat.
If you promise to
leave us alone, Bumble,
you can come here
any time for the flowers.
Well, I...
That's very kind of you,
Rosedust.
I don't know what to say.
Say you're gonna be nice,
and maybe I'll come back
to Bumbleland.
I'll be nice.
Oh, thank you, Rosedust.
Oh, what a wonderful day.
Come on,
let's go home.
Goodbye, Sting,
and thank you for your help.
So long, everybody.
Bye bye, Morning Glory.
Come visit me.
I will.
See you.
Goodbye.
(All)
So long. Goodbye.
Thank you!
The Sunstone
is starting to work.
Just a few more minutes
of sunlight
and the Sunstone
will be back to normal.
(cheers)
I guess you were right,
Honeysuckle.
There are some bad things
in this world
we have to be careful of.
But you were right too,
Morning Glory.
Even bad things
can turn out good.
Look at Bumble.
Not everything is good.
Look.
(Stoneback snorting)
Oh no!
The sun is gone.
Without some more sunlight,
the Sunstone will fade forever
It's terrible!
I didn't see that cloud before.
It just magically appeared.
Maybe it will go away.
(cackles)
Oh,
it's the witches.
I'd know that cackle anywhere.
(cackles)
Yes.
It is us.
And we've come to claim
the valley for our own.
(cackles)
No sun,
no Sunstone.
No Sunstone,
no pretty valley.
In a matter of seconds,
it will be dark, dank
and dreary forever.
(cackles)
That's what you think, Hydia.
To the skies, Flutter Ponies.
We'll blow that cloud so
far away, they'll never find it.
Wish you luck,
Flutter Ponies.
- Yeah, good luck.
- You'll need it.
Shift to Utter Flutter.
You're doing it.
It's working.
(cheers)
Give me that.
Do something, Hydia.
It's moving.
Lerton, momminic,
scronic, blacksner!
The witches are winning.
Harder, Flutter Ponies.
Give it all you have.
(cheers)
Now get the witches.
Run, girls.
Run!
I thought Flutter Valley
was ours, Mom.
Yeah, some magician you are,
Mother.
Don't call me Mother!
Ma! - Mommy!
Mama! - Mother!
♪ From the sun
comes light ♪
comes power ♪
♪ When the sun starts
to rise in the skies ♪
♪ The flowers
start to flower ♪
♪ From the sun
comes hope ♪
comes laughter ♪
♪ With the sun
in its place we'll embrace ♪
♪ The happy ever after ♪
♪ Summer, winter, ♪
♪ fall and spring, ♪
♪ It makes
the whole world sing ♪
♪ From the sun
comes hope ♪
comes laughter ♪
♪ Here's to the
sun up above ♪
♪ From the sun... ♪
♪ Comes love... ♪