♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Bull snorting)
(Both)
MEGAN!
He doesn't look
very happy to see us.
We can't stay here,
Morning Glory.
Megan has to be
around here somewhere.
Let's find her.
Oh...
(buzz)
Oh no.
Oh, Bull.
Yoo-hoo.
Up here.
Hey, Mr. Bull,
bet you can't catch me.
Come on, Sting.
Wake up.
(snorts)
(whinnies)
(Morning Glory)
Yoo-hoo, Mr. Bull.
You missed me.
(Morning Glory)
Try again if you can.
What's going on here?
Megan,
it's me, Morning Glory.
- (Bull snorts)
- Look out.
Do something, quick.
Be right back.
Hurry.
We've got to get the
bull back into his stall.
Over here, Toro.
Come on, boy.
(snorts)
Come on, Sting.
Wake up.
What happened?
I'll tell you later.
Just follow me.
Open the stall door.
(snorts)
Okay, Toro.
Come and get it.
Got him.
Thanks, Megan.
Oh, this is Sting.
Nice to meet you.
The Flutter Ponies
need your help.
What's the trouble?
It's the witches again,
and Bumble.
My ex-queen.
They stole the Sunstone,
and if we don't get it back to
Flutter Valley by sunset,
Flutter Valley will be no more!
(Megan)
We better hurry then.
Uh-oh.
I just realized
you're too big to fly on me.
Me too.
No problem.
You hold this side,
and you hold this side,
Morning Glory.
It's a magic carpet.
I'm ready if you are.
Check.
To Ponyland.
We did it!
(crow caws)
Punch, punish,
puny, purgatory...
Here it is.
I got it - purple.
Do it, Draggle.
Turn those
puny little ponies purple.
I'll try, Mama...
I mean Hydia.
Oh, when the furbob gets back
with help,
you'll be sorry, witches.
Get on with it, Draggle.
Make 'em purple.
Skirmin, forster,
mandeboo, marcus, farcus, yuck!
Well?
Oh, I left out a "yuck."
YUCK!
(laughs)
Look what you've done.
You nincompoop.
(wails)
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll get it off. Here.
Wait...
It's coming.
Get away from me.
It's not coming off.
I'm still purple.
Me too.
Now we have to go all the
way back to the Volcano of Gloom
to get it off.
And if I miss the sunset,
you'll be one sorry witch.
I'm already sorry.
Come on, Hydia.
Let's get on purple.
You too, Ahhg.
(sobs)
Oh, what did I do wrong?
There are plenty
of other witches.
Why did I have
to get Draggle?
(crow caws)
Uh-oh!
What am I going to do?
I've got to get help.
I know, I'll go back to
Furbobia and get more furbobs.
No.
Oh, I can't do that.
The stonebacks are there.
Paradise Estate.
I'll go there.
I can't.
I don't know where it is.
Oh me, maybe somebody else
should have escaped.
What a fix.
Everyone's counting on me
to be a hero,
and I can't even make up
my mind how to be one.
Or if I can,
or if I even wanna be one.
Now what do I do?
Oh...
♪ Why am I so wishy-washy,
Always in a bind? ♪
♪ How can I be a hero,
If I can't make up my mind? ♪
♪ Tell me why I'm so contrary,
When I'm under stress. ♪
♪ How can I be a hero,
If I'm such a nervous mess? ♪
♪ Heroes never waver, ♪
♪ Rushing to and fro, ♪
♪ Should I pause or
act more braver? ♪
♪ I don't know. ♪
♪ I just don't know. ♪
♪ Nothing ever seems to suit
Where am I to turn? ♪
♪ I wanna be a hero, ♪
♪ Perhaps
someday I'll learn. ♪
♪ Oh no,
I'll never learn... ♪
Down there.
It looks like a Bushwoolie.
Maybe he's got some word on
the Flutter Ponies.
Who are you?
I'm Morning Glory,
a Flutter Pony.
And this is Sting,
and Megan.
We thought
you were a Bushwoolie.
The Bushwoolies are my cousins.
I'm a Furbob,
and I have to rescue
some little ponies.
What a dilemma.
Maybe we should
rescue the ponies first.
No, I think we'll need the
Flutter Ponies
to defeat the witches.
Furbob is right.
Let's go to Bumbleland
and free the Flutter Ponies,
get the Sunstone
and then go to Flutter Valley.
Let's do it.
Are you sure
we're doing the right thing?
Yes. Come on.
It's about time, Pointer.
I'm famished.
(slurps)
Oh, so tasty.
Without the Sunstone,
it's back to the old ways,
Flowers are hard
to come by around here.
Not for long.
Bring me the Flutter Ponies!
(buzz)
What do you
want with us now, Bumble?
I want the Sunstone,
and you,
right here in Bumbleland
to keep Flutter Valley alive.
The Sunstone
belongs to us.
Yeah, you stole it!
No matter.
The Sunstone must be retrieved
or it will do
none of us any good.
Suppose we help
you dig it up.
Will you give it back to us?
(laughs)
Give it?
Give...
Give it back?
You will dig it up
because you are my prisoners.
Let the work begin!
(slurps)
(snoring)
Darn.
I thought I had it that time.
Make the hole bigger.
If we could just get the honey
off our wings we could fly.
Then we could do
something about this.
I have a better idea!
Be careful, Honeysuckle.
Hey, where do you
think you're going?
Er... I'm just thirsty.
It's hard work.
Hey!
Hey, what is going on here?
Let me down.
No, no don't let me down.
Help!
You're not going anywhere,
Bumble.
Not until we get the Sunstone
and go back to Flutter Valley.
You'll never get away
with this.
Pointer, do something.
I'll save you,
your Bumbleness.
No, Pointer.
Not that way.
No!
(screams)
Get the Flutter Ponies!
Oh!
Whoopsy...
Help!
Honeysuckle...