♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(laughs)
(All gasp)
That shell!
Maybe I can move it
with my unicorn magic,
and put it between
these jaws to stop them.
Try it, Buttons.
Hurry!
All right!
It's working!
That's it, Buttons.
Take it nice and slow.
(All gasp)
You saved our lives,
Buttons.
Or bought us some time anyway.
Now if we can just get loose
before that shell gives out,
maybe we can stop Squirk
from turning Ponyland
into a giant aquarium.
Then, by cracky,
it's up to us, Pluma.
Maybe together,
we're strong enough.
Oh my!
I'll try it, grandfather,
but I just don't know
if I... I mean...
I'm not sure I can.
Doh, for Christ's sake, girl
Just quit belly-aching
and change!
It's working!
Your ropes, they're breaking.
Way to go, Grandpa.
Quick, everybody.
Jump!
Make your air bubbles, Fizzy,
so we can get out of here.
It won't be long now, Squirk.
Soon the whole land will be
flooded, and you'll rule again.
I know that, Crank.
Shut up!
(laughs)
I wonder if Squirk's found
the Flashstone yet.
We can find out easily enough.
Come on!
There's your answer.
How are we ever going
to stop him?
I think I know.
Come on!
Let's go back to Paradise Estate
and I'll show you.
It won't be long before the
water reaches here, I reckon.
We're not accomplishing anything
waiting for it.
Just hang on, Gusty.
It's Danny we're waiting for.
He thinks
he's figured out a way
to get the Flashstone
away from Squirk.
Look!
My nets!
Right, we can catch
Squirk and Crank in 'em
just like a couple of fish.
We just have to flush
those two out of the water
long enough to drop
the nets on 'em.
I think I know
a way to do that.
Okay, but we've still got to get
the Flashstone.
Leave that part to me.
There's no trace of Squirk.
You sure?
We've looked everywhere.
Then he must be down
there somewhere.
Keep circling and wait
for our signal.
Okay, Pluma,
you know what to do.
Oh, can't I do it once, Squirk?
Come on,
I never get to do nothing.
That's because I'm ruler,
and you're not.
Oh, I never get nothing to do.
Hey boss, look!
Let's check it out.
You! You've escaped!
Yes!
But we, uh,
we've come here to ask you...
that is, tell you actually,
that... well,
it's okay if you...uh,
if you want to rule us.
You've got
to be kidding.
Just stop flooding the land,
Squirk,
and we'll do whatever you want.
Maybe you'll even be,
you know, a good ruler.
(Spike)
Just don't get us wet, okay?
There he is.
The signal!
Let's go!
As the ruler's best friend,
I'd just like to say...
Shut up!
I'm so glad
you've all seen the light...
so to speak.
(cackles)
Uh, could I say one thing,
your Squirkiness?
What?
Drop it!
Hey! No! Agh!
Okay, Buttons,
do your stuff.
Get them, Squirk!
Blast them!
They can't do this to a ruler!
Shut up, and quit splashing.
You're lousing up my aim.
Hey!
Wind Whistler,
let's move.
Come back with my Flashstone!
Okay, Wind Whistler,
now we finish the job.
Here goes!
She's stopping the flood.
Do it again, Megan.
Make it go away.
(gulp)
Oh no...
The tide has turned, boss.
Agh! Do something!
You're the ruler,
you do something.
(screams)
(both scream)
(All cheer)
Well done, Megan.
Magnificent!
Not quite done. Yet.
♪ In no time at all ♪
♪ We'll have things
back in shape ♪
♪ Everything will be
the way it was ♪
♪ Birds will
start to sing again ♪
♪ Bees will
start to buzz ♪
♪ In no time at all ♪
♪ You'll be
shouting out with glee ♪
♪ At the change you thought
could never be ♪
♪ Though the task is
far from small ♪
♪ And it seems like a
mighty long haul ♪
♪ With a little
faith and trust ♪
♪ We can fashion
dreams from dust ♪
♪ In just no time at all ♪ ♪
But why did you destroy
the Flashstone, Megan?
A power like the Flashstone's
can be used for evil
too easily, Fizzy.
We're all much
better off without it.
Maybe, but we couldn't have
gotten our home back without it.
That's right,
our home's okay now.
See, Baby Heart Throb?
I told you
it would be all right.
And I do hope you can forgive
me for pretending to be a ghost.
Well, next time you'll know that
we're your friends,
and you can trust us.
Speaking of home,
well, it's high time
we went back to ours.
Goodbye, everybody.
And thank you.
Thank you all for your help.
(All)
Goodbye! See you! Bye-bye!