♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
right by your side... ♪
(All laugh)
And now!
Gingerbread and Shady
will compete in
the earth pony jumping finals.
(trumpet melody)
Oh!
Yaay!
(screams)
HELP! HELP! HELP!
HELP!
No one helps dragons!
Oh no, well,
you're absolutely wrong.
We do and this is how we do it!
(in pain)
Oh, uggh!
Yeah, Whizzer.
Hey!
Who blew out the candles?
Stand still beast.
Meet your fate like a man!
But I'm not a man!
I'm a dragon!
Whooaaoohh!
(screams)
Hang in there, Spike!
You've caused enough trouble
with that.
Now, who are you
and why are you trying
to hurt our friend?
I am Squire Alonso
and this is my
faithful steed, Panza
And I wasn't trying
to hurt your dragon.
I was trying to slay him,
to do a good deed.
How is getting rid of me
a good deed, huh?
Tell me, huh, huh!
Everyone knows dragons are evil.
That's not true!
(speaking together)
Spike s a real friend!
Spike s a nice little dragon!
I think, we're in trouble again.
But I read all about dragons.
They always catch princesses
and hold them in dungeons.
Not this dragon.
He's my friend!
I'm sorry, Spike.
Please forgive me.
It's just that
I must do a good deed
to become a knight.
But everything
I try turns out wrong.
♪ All I want
is to be a knight. ♪
♪ Fighting evil
and doing right. ♪
♪ But it seems
my chance is slight. ♪
♪ Everything I try, ♪
♪ Always goes awry. ♪
♪ I start fighting
an evil witch. ♪
♪ Should have managed
without a hitch. ♪
♪ But, her pets made me
sneeze and itch. ♪
♪ Everything I do, ♪
♪ Always goes askew. ♪
♪ Once I tried my best. ♪
♪ To rid a town of rats. ♪
♪ I was so depressed. ♪
♪ All I did was
frighten off the cats. ♪
♪ Damsells call me
when in distress. ♪
♪ I show up
but it ends up a mess. ♪
♪ Never once have
I known success. ♪
♪ Still my wish
is strong to be, ♪
♪ Don't tell me
it's wrong to be, ♪
♪ Oh,
how I long to be a knight. ♪
I say,
let's help this guy.
He sure needs it.
Something tells me we can find
a good deed for you to do.
You think so?
Hmpf!
Here we go again.
I know you'll do a good deed
with just a little help.
So we're gonna help him,
huh, huh?
Yeah, let's help him!
I'm willing.
Let's do it!
Aww, whose idea was this, huh?
We've been walking,
and walking, and walking.
Spike,
we're helping
a would-be knight
to do a good deed!
We're helping a
would-be dragonslayer.
Megan, listen.
And look!
A castle!
But why is there a wall
of briars around it?
Must be like a moat.
To keep people out.
(Woman singing in the distance)
That voice.
It's so beautiful.
It must belong to a princess.
Maybe she's trapped
inside...in trouble.
We've got to rescue her.
Right now!
Briar wall?
It's so big!
I can light the
way with my horn.
Great!
Then let's go!
(gasps for breath)
Finally!
The outer wall.
Good work, Alonso.
Hello! You in there,
in the castle.
I, Squire Alonso,
am here to rescue you.
Over here.
I found a door.
Come on.
Oops!
It's Sir Huguenot
The bravest knight of all time.
His lady Princess Aileen.
And Emelita, Aileen's
fairy godmother.
So, who need rescuing?
No one needs rescuing.
Who are you?
Why have you intruded
on the wedding feast
of my godchild
and her groom?
Wedding feast?
Oh, no!
We thought the briars were there
to keep the princess a prisoner.
I conjured up the briar ring
to keep her out of trouble.
This hero, Aileen's wed,
attracts misadventure,
the way an old bone
attracts dogs!
Not anymore
my dear Emelita.
I've retired.
You mean, you've
given up your quests?
Quests are for younger men.
I ask Moffat here,
the wizard at court,
to find a replacement
to serve my king.
A replacement?
I'd do anything.
Well, gee Alonso,
Maybe we should leave.
An excellent idea.
Music - play.
Uh, so sorry
for the intrusion.
Good night.
I was so dumb.
And in front of the wizard.
Oh, cheer up, Alonso.
We could still find
a good deed for you to do.
Sure.
In eighty years or so,
when I'm too old
to lift a sword...
Maybe we should all go back
to Paradise Estate and rest up.
Yes. Let's go back and
everybody can take a rest.
I guess, I just don't have
what it takes to be a knight.
Hey! What are you
throwin' at me?
Huh?
It's bad enough that
I'm stuck on my back.
Now, you're gonna
throw things at me?
Well, are you gonna
help me turn over?
Oh, yeah!
Sure.
Let me...
(grunts and groans)
Come on. That's it. Good try.
Hey, what's the matter?
You're so heavy!
Great. Now, you make
cracks about my weight.
Alonso, I hope you're not
thinking of this as giving up
Hey, Alonso.
She is been nice to you.
Why don't you talk to her?
You know,
you've gotta be nice and...
Alonso is missing!
We'd better go look for him!
I have a feeling
he's in trouble.
Come on!
(grunts and groans)
I knew it...
The simplest little
thing I can't do right.
Great. I'm stuck
and the only guy
who can do me
a good deed is a quitter.
I'm not a quitter!
I just don't have any way
to turn you over.
Huh!
Wait a minute!
Call me a quitter, huh?
What are ya gonna do?
(breathing heavily)
This is the place
where we saw him last.
Oh, what'll I do
without him around?
He's such a nice guy.
One, two, three, and ugghhhh!
Congratulations!
You've just passed
the top-up-turtle test!
I did? I have?
Yes!
I was looking for
a replacement for Sir Huguenot,
and I decided to give you
a little test.
Now, I know
I've found that replacement
I was looking for - You!
Me?
Yes, my boy.
Not everyone would have kept
going when things were that bad.
I need a knight
who won't give up.
A true knight! A knight with
a stout heart.
You got him!
And I'm taking him with me.
Well, I can't leave
without thanking you first.
If not for you, I might have
given up a long time ago.
You had it in you all the time.
Bye, bye.
And remember...
Be nice to dragons.
I will, Spike.
And I'll remember
all of you, too.
Always!
Good bye.
Good bye, bye, bye...
Bye, bye...
You know.
For a would-be dragonslayer,
he wasn't that bad.
Spike!
(laughs)