♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(breathes heavily)
Uhh!
Woebegone!
Come back here.
You miserable little wretch.
Oh, phew!
(thundering)
Oh, dear!
I've got you now, Woebegone.
(roars)
Oh, my!
You're all looking so
bright and colorful today.
(sniffs)
And who are you?
Sshhh! I'm in big trouble.
An aligatorsaur is after me.
Can I hide here a while?
Just till he's gone.
You can hide in there.
By the way,
what's an aligatorsaur?
You're about to find out.
(stomping)
Ahhh!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Has a little squirt and tattered
wretch run through here?
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
Besides,
what's a big guy like you
chasin' a little squirt
for anyway?
Yeah, you should be
ashamed of yourself.
Why don't you pick on
someone your own size?
If he's here, you'll find out.
If not, count yourselves lucky.
He's big trouble.
Aww...
(thud)
Are you all right?
I'm fine, thank you.
Except for a tiny pain
in my big toe.
Aww, you're hurt!
Aligatorsaurs are big.
But they're really light
on their feet.
I'll be fine...really.
Wait!
We can't let you go.
You will if ya know
what's good for you.
See that?
I did that.
I thought that
big aligatorwhatsit did it.
That's true.
But I brought him here.
Bad luck follows me everywhere.
Oh, we won't hear another word.
You're staying with us.
- No ifs...
- Ouch!
...ands or buts.
There now.
You just rest easy for a while.
Then you can be on your way.
You just don't understand.
Aw, come on, uncle Woebegone.
Stay and go nappy time with us,
pwetty pwease?
When you wake up you can
have gingerbread cookies,
and milk.
Those are gingerbread cookies?
I don't know what happened
to them.
But they still taste good.
It's starting again.
First your cookies crumble,
then boom!
Your whole house falls down.
(crumbles)
Nonsense! Now get some rest.
I'm warning you.
(all scream)
Help! Help!
Is everyone okay?
All safe, Posey
but awfully scared.
We have to sleep outside?
Of course not.
We'll find a place for you
in the Estate.
Go with Masquerade.
Where's Woebegone?
He must still be in there.
(loud knocking)
He is so still...
- Is he--
- Achoo!
You're alive!
Not if we don't get out of here.
Good idea.
Surely now you realize
that you've got to let me go.
Oh, I don't know.
It looks to me like the roof was
gonna collapse... eventually.
Now stop being so hard
on yourself.
You just need
a good night's sleep.
Maybe you'd like to tell us
why that giant creature was
chasing you so ferociously?
I passed through his
village and demolished it.
Ohh, come on!
Surely your whole life
hasn't been just an accident
waiting to happen?
Well, if you really
wanna know,
it started
when I was just a lad.
My homeland was a
beautiful, tropical garden.
Everything was lush and green.
Me and a couple pals were
kickin' around a kaleidostone
then Hand-me-Down spotted her.
Look!
It's the old witch.
Come on. Follow me.
I got an idea.
Wait for me.
She-she's never
done us any harm.
You don't wanna have fun?
Then just watch.
We're gonna dump her
in her own brew.
Come on, Tattle!
(taunting)
Okay, okay. Wait a sec.
I'm comin'.
Won't leave me alone, eh?
Wanna play rough, do they?
Okay.
All right. You distract her
with the kaleidostone,
while Tattle and I
turn over her pot.
And don't blow it.
Ah, ha!
(hissing)
(bells chime)
Please don't hurt my friends.
They really didn't mean
any harm.
(loud splash)
There I was, floating
in the soup with her,
and was she ever mad.
(walls and roof crumble)
Uh...
It's okay.
Only one wall fell down.
At least, we won't need
an air conditioner.
Come on.
We'll have to find you
another place to sleep tonight.
Good.
Then I can finish my story.
Uh, some other time.
We've had enough excitement
for one night,
thank you.
(dripping)
(thundering)
If I stay here any longer,
Paradise Estate will be anything
but a paradise.
(thundering)
Uh-oh!
(chandelier creaks)
Oh!
Thank goodness
they're heavy sleepers.
Well, at least that didn't fall.
For a second there I thought my
bad luck was working overtime.
(groans in pain)
(sighs sadly)
Gusty. Lickety-Split.
What's the matter?
Woebegone's disappeared.
He's gone.
Oh, good!
If he stayed any longer,
Paradise Estate would've become
a disaster area.
You don't actually believe
that bad luck stuff?
What difference does it make?
All that matters is
that he's hurt.
And that he needs us
to take care of him.
Come on!
If they're gonna bring that
little jinx back,
I'd better reinforce
the whole Estate.
Ohh...
♪ Come back, little hobo,
come back ♪
♪ We want you for a friend ♪
♪ Forget it. I'm a jinx ♪
♪ You'll hate me in the end ♪
♪ Come home, little hobo,
come home ♪
♪ Come play with us a bit ♪
♪ You're making a big mistake ♪
♪ I'll only make a mess of it ♪
♪ Telling me to stick around ♪
♪ is taking quite a gamble ♪
♪ Paradise Estate will turn
into a shamble ♪
♪ Please stay, little hobo,
please stay ♪
♪ You mustn't go away ♪
♪ Alright, alright, okay ♪
♪ I only pray that
you won't say ♪
♪ You rue the day I said
I'll stay ♪
(bushwoolies)
Thank you very much.
Uh-ho!
Look who's back.
And he probably brought his
bad luck with him.
There's no such thing
as bad luck.
And the nursery of Paradise
Estate didn't really collapse,
the moon's made of
green cheese,
and I'm the Queen of England.
Of course, the nursery of
Paradise Estate collapsed,
but no one was hurt.
Lickety-Split's right.
I am bad luck.
And if you don't believe it,
watch.
Ohhhh...
Never mind that.
That old tree,
uh, must have been
filled with termites.
But I am a jinx.
Run to the Estate fast.
It's dangerous to be
in the same place
as that Woebegone character.
Whoa!
(resisting)
(All gasp)
Help me!
Help!