♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Good return, Spike!
(laughs)
Get it, baby Tiddley.
Good one.
I got it, I got it.
(grunts)
Oh...Baby Tiddley-Winks.
Way to go, Baby Tiddley.
It's yours, Spike.
(sneezes fire)
There, there!
Yeah, yeah,
it's all right, all right.
You all right, Baby Lofty?
Oh, it's okay.
No, this won't happen again,
will it Megan?
Not a big flame like this.
Well, Spike you're getting
to be big dragon now.
And I wouldn't be surprised
if your fire breathing powers
get stronger as you grow.
You'll just have to learn
how to control them.
Growing up isn't so great.
(sneezes fire)
Hey, everything's okay.
Nobody got hurt.
I can't make it go out.
Spike, it's no big deal.
You're a dragon,
dragons breathe fire.
Swell.
Who's gonna show me
how to use my fire breath?
That's what I wanna know.
I can read up on dragons.
You know, their history
and everything.
Oh, books are one thing,
But what I need is experience.
I need to go find some dragons.
You mean, go on a quest.
But that could be dangerous.
Maybe so,
but the only way I can learn
how to be a dragon
is from real dragons.
Okay. But you're
not goin' alone.
Oh, maybe this wasn't
such a great idea.
We haven't seen anybody so far.
Much less any dragons.
(bird screaming)
Oof!
(laughs)
Who are you guys?
I'm Spike and this is Danny.
Are you all right?
Yes I'm all right.
I just don't know how to fly.
I was separated
from my parents a while ago.
And I've been looking
for them ever since.
If only
I could find...my parents.
(sighs sadly)
(sneezes fire)
I know what ya mean.
♪ Someone to look up to ♪
♪ That's what I'm
looking for ♪
♪ Someone who will
show me the sky ♪
♪ And teach me
how to soar ♪
♪ Someone to look up to ♪
♪ My goal
is just the same ♪
♪ Someone who will
help me to learn ♪
♪ To tame my
dragon's flame ♪
♪ Someone who will teach me
right from wrong ♪
good from bad ♪
♪ Someone who will show me
where I belong ♪
♪ Someone like a
mom or a dad ♪
♪ Someone to look up to ♪
♪ I have no one
right now ♪
♪ But I will find
that someone ♪
♪ Someday, somehow ♪
What's your name?
Weston!
Well, come with us, Weston.
After I find some dragons,
you can come back
to Paradise Estate with us.
Yeah!
Sure.
I guess it's better
than just waiting here.
Maybe we should
look down there.
(cackles)
This isn't quite
what I expected.
They look awful scary.
I've got to go talk to them.
Good luck looking
for your parents.
You want us to stick around?
Nope.
These are my dragons.
I have to face them on my own.
Good luck, Spike.
And what have we here?
(stammers)
If you please, sir,
I thought maybe if it wouldn't
be too much trouble,
you might allow me to
join your band?
Whatta we want him around for?
Little pipsqueak like him
would only get in our way.
Wait!
You wanting to join a
dragon camp is all very well.
But we dragons
have certain criteria,
which must be met.
We generously offer to protect
the citizens of a nearby village
for a token consideration.
The selection of their
best food stuffs and delicacies.
But the townspeople
have been slow to respond
to our magnanimous offer.
So a little visit is in order.
You may accompany us
so that we can judge
how good a dragon
you really are.
(marketplace chatter)
(roar)
(yelling)
(growling)
Help! Help!
You?
Me?
Yes, you. Pick that up!
(evil laugh)
This isn't right.
- This is awful.
- We've gotta stop 'em.
Come on,
let's go to Paradise Estate.
And then they marched
back to their camp
with all the food they'd stolen.
I think I'll just see
what they're up to.
Well! My boy.
(burp)
What do you think of
the dragon life now?
Terrific, isn't it?
Of course, this doesn't
mean you're in yet.
Ya know, ya might have more fun,
if you were more like
my friends, the little ponies.
Little ponies?
Yeah, yeah.
The little ponies live
in Dream Valley
and play games all day
and make cookies and cupcakes.
Cookies and cupcakes?
And swim in the waterfall
and pick flowers.
Why... We'd love to visit
the little ponies.
Take us to Dream Valley,
and you'll be one of the gang.
Especially, if they
give us cupcakes.
They're coming here.
I think we should prepare a
proper welcome for 'em.
I have an idea.
(laughs)
(grunting in sequence)
What's this?
How did they know
we were coming?
Welcome, we've been
waiting for you.
Yes indeed.
We have a big meal
all ready for you.
With cupcakes?
I can't believe how easy
this is gonna be.
Move outta the way, Spike.
Smart move ponies.
Give us food and keep it coming.
Yeah.
Especially the cupcakes,
'cause if you don't
there's gonna be trouble.
Hey, wait a minute
these are my friends.
Not anymore.
You're one of us now.
Ah... cupcakes.
(laughing)
But you don't
have to be mean.
They'll share
everything they have.
We just wanna make certain.
Hey Guys!
Surprise!
(All yell)
And you can expect
more where that came from
if you start any more trouble!
Yeah, I wanted to learn
how to be a dragon, not a bully.
Go!
Let's get outta here.
Don't forget.
Okay, okay we're goin'.
Just havin' a little fun.
No sense of humor.
Boy, some people.
What's the matter, Weston?
Aren't you enjoying yourself?
Oh, yeah!
Everything's wonderful here.
It's just that...
Weston, look!
Mama! Daddy!
I guess I'll never learn how
to be a grown up dragon now.
But if being a dragon
means being a bully.
Nah! Look how many different
kinds of ponies there are.
Earth Ponies, Pegasi,
Flutter Ponies,
so there are probably all
different kinds of dragons too.
When the time is right,
you'll find the ones like you.
You really think so?
Well, then maybe for now being
here is the right place to be.
Anyway, I did learn
one thing from the dragons...
Yeah, what was that?
(sneezes fire)
(both laugh)