♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Baby Ponies crying)
Come on, Sniffles,
take food from Baby Fifi.
Hmm... taste good.
This is not t-t-tasty
good food, Sniffles!
(giggle)
See Milkweed, nice ducky.
Quack, quack, quack
Go on...play.
♪ Babysitting...Babysitting. ♪
♪ Babies fussing crying
spitting ♪
♪ Babysitting...Babysitting. ♪
♪ Oh, my aching head
is splitting ♪
♪ Caring for a cuddly tot
takes a lot ♪
♪ Your nerves get shot ♪
♪ quack quack quack ♪
♪ Babies cause
all kinds of trouble ♪
♪ hey, you two. ♪
♪ And with twins,
your trouble's double. ♪
♪ Babysitting...Babysitting. ♪
♪ Babies fussing crying
spitting ♪
♪ We say "yes" ♪
♪ they say "no" ♪
♪ We say "stop" ♪
♪ they say "go" ♪
♪ No wonder that we
feel like quitting ♪
♪ Babysitting. ♪
Come on, snookums,
Baby Lickety-Split says
time to eat.
That does it!
Come on, we take
newborn twins for walk.
Walk, where?
The Satin Slipper Sweet Shoppe.
That keep them quiet.
Scoops...
Fudge sundaes, all around.
I am sorry, Baby Lickety-Split,
we're out of ice cream.
- Ah! It unheard of.
- That impossible!
It terrible!
(All crying)
Rocky Ripple has shut down
the Mixville Ice Cream Works
to drive Fudgy McSwain
out of business.
Fudgy who?
Fudgy McSwain. He runs
the Creamy Confection Foundry.
He makes all the ice cream
toppings in Ponyland.
They really hate each other.
And the saddest thing is they
used to be such good friends.
Then there only
one thing to do.
We gonna make those two
friends again.
Come on.
There it is,
Mixville Ice Cream Works.
Is the Rocky Ripple guy
gonna even listen to us?
You kidding, Baby Tic-Tac-Toe?
Bunch of cute kids like us?
He do anything we ask.
Never!
Fudgy McSwain's a thief.
I've spent years...
Oops! Wrong way.
I spent years developing
my greatest ice cream flavor
double banana, marshmallow,
colada...
And on the day
I'm ready to start
making my greatest creation,
the piece of paper
with the recipe disappears...
and Fudgy McSwain took it.
Hmm...
This be tougher than I thought.
The Creamy Confection Foundry.
Fudgy McSwain listen to us.
What? No!
Why should I crawl to him?
It's me that's owed the apology.
But Rocky Ripple just confused
'bout you that's all.
(both twins crying)
And our newborn twins
want their treat.
All right, then.
I'll speak to my old friend
and set things straight
for you ponies.
So you see, Rocky. I could
never have taken the recipe.
Without your ice cream,
I'd be out of business.
And I'd be willing
to help you look for it.
Old friend.
(All cheer)
Yay!
So...you pretend
to be my friend,
so you can abuse me in this way?
Now see here.
See how you like it
when you're up to your eyeballs
in butterscotch topping!
We better get out of here before
we make any more trouble.
Fudgy, wait! S'il vous plait,
if you please?
Insult me, will he?
I'll teach him a lesson
he'll nay soon forget.
Fudgy, please,
this is not right.
(babies cooing)
(Ponies plea together)
Oh, no!
(All Ponies gasp)
(All giggling)
- Quack, quack...
- Goodbye.
(babies squeal in delight)
Me know this must be fun full,
but...
I'll drown him
in chocolate syrup.
I'll destroy him
with chopped nuts.
We better warn, Rocky.
Rocky Ripple, you're finished!
Fudgy McSwain, use this.
It's no good.
Ice cream's 'sposed to
make people happy!
I've not yet begun to fight.
Why, you!
Ya quick frozen faker...
I'll plow you under!
Ooh-la-la!
We must stop this!
We gotta get newborn twins
some place safe.
Come on, we take 'em
to Satin Slipper Sweet Shoppe.
Why Satin Slipper?
No ice cream there.
(All Ponies shouting)
(baby twins crying)
It's just what I feared,
an all-out Ice Cream War.
Quack... Newborn Twins
hungry, Baby Fifi.
Well, there is plenty
of ze ice cream for them to eat.
No, they can't have that.
It's been on the ground.
Oh, well.
I was saving this
for a special occasion.
It's the very last ice cream
I have.
(crying loudly)
Oh, Milkweed dear,
everything all right?
have some nice ice cream.
(slurping)
What you got there, Milkweed?
The secret recipe!
(gasps)
Then Fudgy didn't steal it.
Rocky must have gotten careless
and dropped it
in the ice cream mixture.
Come on, gang,
we're gonna put a stop
to this silliness.
Ya marshmallow maniac,
I'll stop you
if it's the last thing I do.
Aye, and it'll be
the last thing ya do!
Ya double-dip dog!
Oh...wait!
They gonna destroy
each other.
Watch it! I need to stop it.
(tires screeching)
Baby North Star,
are you all right?
- Look!
- The recipe.
We find in carton
of your ice cream.
Uh, I guess I do get
confused once in a while.
Well, Fudgy, looks like
I owe you an apology.
Can ya ever forgive me?
Old friend?
Of course,
if ya can forgive me.
Now that's more like it.
I'll start makin' ice cream
again right away.
Aye, but what's ice cream
without toppings
me old chum?
(laughs)
We're back in business again.
And to show you
first-tooth Ponies
how grateful we are,
you can have all the ice
cream you want for free.
(Baby twins cheering)
(groans in disgust)
Me think me seen 'nuff
ice cream for one day.
Suddenly me have craving
for nice salad.
(both laugh)