♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Help! Somebody, help!
Help us!
Oh,
it's getting so hot up here!
Hey,
watch where you're dripping,
Forget-Me-Not.
Maybe if
the honey melts enough,
we'll be able to move again
and get out of here.
You're right, Rosedust.
It's working.
Yeah, I can move
my wings again.
I can almost fly.
If only I could
get out of here,
I could help the other
Flutter Ponies.
Oh, it's all Sting's fault.
I thought he was my friend.
I am your friend.
(gasp)
Sting!
But I thought you left
to join Bumble?
I did, but I couldn't find her.
You mean she
flew away without you?
Guess so.
Guess she isn't
really my friend.
Well,
we could still be friends.
I'd like that, Morning Glory.
Let's see if we can save
the rest of the Flutter Ponies.
We have to move the Sunstone.
No sweat.
I'll take care of that.
What are you gonna do?
Mission accomplished.
But the Sunstone is gone.
So what? The fire's out.
So what?!
It's a calamity!
Without the Sunstone,
Flutter Valley will be no more.
It's finished.
Oh, well that's
a definite problem.
Keep trying, Flutter Ponies.
We almost made it.
Try harder.
There must be something
we can do to help.
You'd better help yourself
first, Morning Glory.
Grab her, Sting!
No, Bumble.
Morning Glory is my friend.
Don't be ridiculous.
The Flutter Ponies
are not our friends.
They're my friends, Bumble.
You realize of course, Sting,
that your attitude borders
on betrayal.
Well, what you've done
isn't so nice either.
Let the Flutter Ponies go
and I'll apologize.
Never.
They're mine.
Pointer, take Sting
and Morning Glory prisoner.
Got you, your Bumbleness.
Get them!
- Duck!
- Agh!
To the air!
Hey, Sting's flying.
He can't do that.
After them!
Oh my...
I am beautiful!
I've been waiting
for this chance, Sting.
Well, you've got it, Pointer.
Way to go, Sting.
Whoah!
Let's get out of here.
(laughs awkwardly)
Sorry, your Bumbleness.
(laughs sarcastically)
(screams)
We made it.
We're free.
The Flutter Ponies
have escaped.
There's too much honey
on my wings.
I can't fly.
Then run, Flutter Ponies, run.
Oh, if only we could fly again.
We never were great runners.
I want that Sunstone back,
Flutter Ponies,
and you're going to help me.
The Sunstone's ours, Bumble.
We need it to bring
Flutter Valley back to life.
Oh, come on, come on, come on!
Hydia hates me,
she hates me not.
She hates me, she hates me not.
she hates me...
Oh!
Hydia hates me,
she hates me not.
Ouch!
How much longer until
Flutter Valley rots, Hydia?
Soon.
When the sun sets,
Flutter Valley will be dark,
dank and dreary - for good.
Just the way we like it.
(laughs)
Oh, we're running out of time,
little ponies.
If we don't get the Sunstone
back here soon,
we can kiss
Flutter Valley goodbye.
If only one of us could
just escape and get some help.
But how do we get past Ahhg?
Roooaaaahhhhggggrrr!
(gasp)
I have an idea.
(whispers)
Oh no, you won't.
I won't do it.
Nope, uh-uh.
Please, Furbob. You have to,
it's our only chance.
Yours too.
Okay.
But this better work.
Close your eyes, Furbob.
I don't want to get
any bubble in them.
It's working!
Go, Fizzy! Way to go!
You can open your eyes now,
Furbob.
(laughs)
Hey, this is fun.
Hey Ahhg,
bet you don't have
many friends, do you?
Rooooaaaaggghhhr!
Want to play with our friend?
Roooaaagghhhr!
All you have to do is
let him out,
and he'll play with you.
(gasp)
(laughs)
Whoah!
It worked.
Run, Furbob.
- Get help.
- Run for it.
Roooooaaaaggghhhr!
(cheers)
Oh, you let them escape,
you buzzoff! Oof!
Rooaaaaggghhr!
Whoah ho ho hooo!
Don't be upset, Hydia.
It's okay.
Yeah, what can
one skinny old furbob do?
You'll see, witches.
You'll see.
I don't know if
I did the right thing.
By leaving Bumbleland?
All I ever wanted
was for Bumble to like me.
I like you.
Thanks, Morning Glory.
But there's only two of us.
How can we possibly save
the rest of the Flutter Ponies
and the Sunstone too?
Look, a rainbow!
What good is a rainbow?
It's just pretty, that's all.
Megan lives on the other side.
I remember the little ponies
telling us that.
Who's Megan?
She always helps
the little ponies
when they're in trouble.
Maybe she'll help us.
Let's go!
Do you know how to get there?
No...
But it can't be that difficult.
We have to try.
♪ Stretch yourself
to the limit, Sting ♪
♪ Show what you can do ♪
♪ The outlook is iffy ♪
♪ But you'll come through ♪
♪ Stretch yourself
to the limit, alright ♪
♪ Rush right into the fray ♪
♪ Right ♪
♪ In just a jiffy ♪
♪ You'll find your way ♪
♪ If you encounter
obstacles ♪
♪ Try not to lose
your nerve ♪
♪ Though you may
get thrown a-curve ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Keep your courage
in reserve ♪
♪ That's right, Sting ♪
♪ Stretch yourself
to the limit ♪
♪ Aim your sights
at the sky ♪
♪ You can work wonders... ♪
♪ You can ♪
♪ If you just try ♪
(laughs)
This is where Megan lives?
It looks like the place
the little ponies told us about.
Let's see if we can find her.
I've never seen a Megan before.
What would she look like?
Well, she's kind of big,
and...and has long hair -
only on her head,
and... Oh... Well,
you'll know her when
you see her.
Megan!
Are you here, Megan?
Not here.
What if she's gone
on a trip or something?
Oh, she just has to be here.
We need her.
Uh-oh...
Is that Megan?
(snorts)
Run!
In there!
Over the rainbow is not such
a safe place to live either.
If only Megan were here.
Oh no!
(snorts)
(Both)
MEGAN!
(snorts)