♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(All scream)
This will teach you not
to steal my treasure!
We didn't steal it.
We spent it.
Niblick listen!
Let us go and I promise
we'll bring you back
a treasure of equal value
to the one we spent.
Interesting proposition.
She's right Mr. Niblick.
Equal value...
I promise.
Humph...
Did she say equal value?
We'll get you something better.
Hmm...
On one condition though.
(All)
Huh!
Megan, dear!
Have you slipped your bridle?
We are hardly in a
position to make demands.
If we bring you
another treasure,
do you promise to undo the
wishes of the magic coins?
Sounds fair.
Not that I care anything
about being fair.
Okay, you got it!
(All sigh)
Come on in.
Okay, here's the deal.
You bring me somethin' better
than my magic coins,
which ain't gonna be easy,
and I undo the spell.
Can't you undo the spell before
we find you another treasure?
Ponyland needs rain before
it turns into a desert.
I live in a desert!
Look you're wasting my time.
Come back with somethin'
I like and we'll talk.
♪ What do you give
to a troll? ♪
♪ What gift would
he like best ♪
♪ How about a lucky charm?
♪
♪ How about a brand
new smoke alarm? ♪
♪ What do you give
to a troll? ♪
♪ To make him
feel impressed ♪
♪ How about a nice fake fur?
♪
♪ What about a fire
extinguisher? ♪
♪ How about some gingerbread?
♪
♪ How about a dictionary?
♪ How about a
beautiful bouquet? ♪
♪ Maybe we should
just call it a day ♪
♪ And give the guy a
fireworks display ♪
♪ What do you give
to a troll? ♪
♪ I think it's very clear ♪
♪ Whatever you
give to a troll ♪
♪ The answer isn't here ♪
♪ Whatever you
give to a troll ♪
♪ The answer isn't here ♪
What do you think Niblick
would like, Puck?
I know.
I think that old troll
would like to have...
...The Heart of Fire.
What's that?
It's a huge ruby in the
crater of fire mountain.
Or he might go for the beautiful
Golden Rose
in the Haunted Garden.
Then there's always
the Emerald Idle
in the ruins of
the City of the Ancients.
Well, I guess we better split
up and try for all three.
That way, we're sure
to get at least one.
(Lofty)
Try to get a few drops on them.
It might keep them going.
We're gonna have to go
back to Paradise Estate.
There's no other choice.
But what if there's no
water there either?
There will be, Molly.
There has to be.
This place is full of bad luck.
I just know it.
Ah, you're imagining things,
Magic Star.
It's just an old garden.
Spike. I think
these hedge animals are alive.
Of course, they're alive,
Heart Throb.
They're plants.
Look!
There it is!
Wait a minute, Spike.
What if these things
are guarding the rose?
Ah, you've been listening to too
many of Paradise's stories.
(plants growls)
(gulp)
Then again, maybe you
got something there.
Darlings,
may I make a suggestion?
Run!
(Magic Star)
Run where?
(Heart Throb)
Do I have to think
of everything?
Wait a minute.
I said these monsters
are just plants, right?
Well, plants hate...
fire!
Let's go!
Quick thinking.
Niblick's gonna love it.
I hate it!
Oh, duh!
I mean,
Niblick, surely you jest.
I mean it's definitely new.
It smells real nice.
Here, try it.
You dimwitted dragon.
I can't--
A...A...Ah-choo!
As I was saying,
I got rose
fever for this breath.
I sure hope the others have
better luck than we did.
(Puck)
The Emerald Idol's in there,
but be careful.
It's guarded by a
series of traps.
Why does that not surprise me?
Oh, come on.
How bad can it be?
(Galaxy)
I'm taking no chances.
I'll just wink over
there and grab it.
(tremors)
(Gingerbread)
Oh! Galaxy!
Don't worry, we'll
get you out of there.
Careful! Careful!
The floor is booby trapped.
(Galaxy)
Be careful, Gingerbread.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm okay.
I'll have you out of there
in a jiffy, Galaxy.
And I'll get the idol.
Hurray!
I got it!
Yahoo!
(Galaxy)
No, Puck.
Uh-oh!
Puck! Get the idol outside!
I'll free Galaxy.
Right!
(Gingerbread)
I sure wish I could wink
through this thing.
(Galaxy)
Hurry, wink out of here!
(Puck)
Wow! Talk about a tight squeeze.
(Galaxy)
We did it.
We got the Emerald Idle.
(Gingerbread)
Let's take it back to Niblick.
You cracked it, mini-mind.
Nice try.
But you gotta do
better than that.
(Fizzy)
Once we get to the top, how
do we get the Heart of Fire?
(Wind Whistler)
I suggest we traverse that
overpass when we encounter it.
(Fizzy)
Ah!
(Megan)
She means
We should cross that
bridge when we come to it.
Oh, right.
We just came to it.
And there isn't any bridge.
How're we ever gonna get it?
(Megan)
Can you fly over to
it Wind Whistler?
In theory, yes.
In practicality,
the thermal updrafts from
the lava may make it difficult.
Still we shall see.
(Both)
Wind Whistler!
No use, I fear.
The air currents destroy
my equilibrium.
Now what do we do?
It's too far for me to wink to.
Hmm...
Fizzy, you can't reach it.
But maybe one of
your bubbles can.
Yeah.
They're still
real big and strong
because of the wish I made.
If you send it close enough,
perhaps we can retrieve the gem.
(Fizzy)
Megan, the bubble is so
big, it's hard to control.
You concentrate on flying,
Wind Whistler.
I'll grab the gem.
(Both)
Ah! Ohh! Ah!
Oh! Megan, Wind Whistler,
I'm so sorry.
That's all right, Fizzy.
We got the ruby.
Now we'll just fly back in.
Not yet.
The turbulence is
still too great.
(Both)
Oh! Ah!