♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(All scream)
Did you do that?
That was marvelous.
Yes, well, I am a Gnome.
And Gnomes have powers
over earth and stone.
But we're back to
where we started now.
But the castle's
made out of stone.
Can't you use your powers
on it to get us in there?
(struggles)
Not really.
The castle is
magically protected.
I can't do anything with the
stone in it unless I'm inside.
We could catch the castle
without any trouble,
if it weren't for those
creatures guarding it.
The Undine and the Salamander
uh... a water creature
and a fire creature.
Yeah, them.
If we could just find a
way to dry up the Undine.
Yeah!
Or put out the
Salamander's flame.
We can.
It's simple.
I think she's heard
too many fairytales.
No, no.
It's a perfect plan.
We'll just use them
against each other.
It just might work!
Let's give it a go!
(loud smash)
Hey, you!
Undine!
Your mother wears galoshes.
(laughs)
(roars)
(Locket)
Yoo-hoo! Salamander.
(Purple)
Your fire's not that hot.
(Locket)
And neither are you.
(growls angrily)
(teases)
Na, na, brrr!
(chuckles)
(growls)
(gasps in surprise)
(groans)
(All rejoice)
Yeah!
Okay! Let's go before
the castle can pull away
from these mountains again.
Inside! Quickly!
Oh, this is so exciting!
Boy, it sure is
spooky and confusing.
We could get lost in
here real easy.
We need a guide.
I think I might be
able to provide that.
(incantation)
Show us the way to Ariel.
That's great.
How'd you do that?
It was nothing.
Let's not waste any more time.
I want to find
Ariel, my true love.
Be careful, ponies.
Just because we're inside
doesn't mean it's safe.
We won't have any problem.
Just watch.
Everything's going to
fall right into place.
(gasps)
Whoa!
Are you going to believe
me when I say "be careful"?
I certainly will.
We're almost there.
I can feel it.
Oh, my!
Oh! This is so wonderful!
Ariel, my beloved.
At last, we'll be together.
Look out!
(All scream)
(screams)
We've got to stop them
so that Garth can awaken Ariel
with a kiss.
Oh, really?
I thought we had to stop them
because they'll make
baked Alaska
out of us if we don't.
(Evil laugh)
My wings are soaked.
I can't fly.
Help!
(growls)
Thanks, Heart Throb.
Thanks, Locket.
(growls angrily)
(growls)
Help! Do something!
Get us out of here!
(All scream)
(screams)
Ah!
No! Nothing can happen
to my true love.
(growls)
(loud whirling)
(ponies scream)
No!
Thanks, Garth.
What can we do?
The castle!
Make the castle shake, Garth.
(groans)
(growls)
(tremoring)
Now is our chance.
Jump on, Garth!
(struggles)
(awakens and sighs)
Look!
Thank you.
Look there!
Oh, my goodness!
Ferdinand! Andrew!
My dear boys, what
are you doing here?
- My lady.
Who are they?
And what are they doing here?
My name is Ferdinand
and this is Andrew.
We were the suitors
for the hand of Ariel
that made her father
cast the spell.
These boys caused
so much trouble,
my father made them my
protectors all these years.
You're not going to take
one of them
for your husband now, are you?
Oh, no, no, no.
They're nice boys, but
they're not for me.
Oh, thank goodness!
Well, thank you all very much
for coming and waking me.
And now I must be going.
Wait! I woke you from the spell.
You're supposed to be mine now.
Look! I don't mean
to be rude or anything,
but the spell wasn't my idea.
I'm not ready to
fall in love yet.
But...but it's not fair.
(All gasp)
What's happening?
The spell's over,
now that Ariel's awake.
The castle's starting to fall.
You didn't land the castle
before you woke me?
Give me a break.
I was busy.
We'd better get out of here!
But there's not enough
of us to carry everybody.
Garth, do something.
Why should I bother?
I don't care anymore.
(All scream)
Garth, how could you?
- Please!
- You've got to help us!
Please! Not for my
sake, but for theirs.
Any moment the whole
castle will crush.
That's it!
Come on!
Oh! hey!
Make the sand soft, Garth,
like you did before.
Oh, all right.
Look at what he's doing!
Please come back inside.
You could fall...
(All scream)
It worked!
Now let's get back to Ariel.
Get away from it, quickly!
That was close!
Are you all right, my beloved?
Fine, thanks.
A little dusty.
Well, I guess you'll be on your
way now to begin your new life.
Just a moment!
Garth's right.
It's not fair.
Yeah. Are you sure you
won't change your mind?
Well, there's always
that possibility.
(All)
Goodbye!
- Goodbye! - Farewell!