♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
As Valentine watched
her friend gallop away
into the darkening sunset,
a single lonely tear
rolled down her face...
...The End
(sobbing)
Why would Valentine's
friend gallop away at sunset?
(sniffling)
..huh?
It is illogical to begin
a long journey
just as the sun is setting.
Who cares
what the sun was doing
when he had to leave
his one true love?
Yeah, how can you ask
a question like that
at a time like this?
Time like what?
(groan impatiently)
(sobbing)
I fail to understand
this display of sentiment.
It is just a story, after all.
Wind Whistler, it's too bad
you weren't around
when the Feelings Fairy
was passing out feelings.
(laughs)
I do have feelings..
Which I think
you two just proved.
Yeah, by hurting 'em.
Way to go, Buttons.
Moi?
(laugh)
Look out!
Crunch the Rockdog comin'!
Run for your lives!
Yeah, run for your lives!
Run! Yeah, run, run!
Ow! I'm sorry! No, I'm sorry!
It's okay!
I'm glad you're sorry.
Let's go left!
Right, left! Yeah, right left!
Right left!
That's it, take it to the left!
Right!
♪ I hate soft ♪
♪ Anything that's soft
and squishes ♪
♪ Leaves me feeling
mean and vicious ♪
♪ I hate soft ♪
♪ I hate nice ♪
♪ Puffy clouds
and puffy pillows.. ♪
♪ Sleeping lambs
and weeping willows.. ♪
♪ Make me mad ♪
♪ Nice is bad ♪
♪ I hate sweet
and cuddly things ♪
♪ Anything that's gentle ♪
♪ Don't give me
no hearts and flowers, ♪
♪ I ain't sentimental ♪
♪ I hate soft ♪
♪ So don't get in MY way,
'cause if you do ♪
♪ I will make life hard... ♪
♪ for you ♪
(evil laugh)
I have feelings..
I merely refrain from expressing
them at the drop of a hat.
Don't feel bad, Wind Whistler.
They didn't mean it.
HELP! HELP!
(panting)
The Rockdog from
the Purple Mountain,
oh, it was horrible.
Terrible, I tell you.
Turned to stone.
(gasps and wheezes)
Made marshlands
into rocky valley!
Oh.. No more green,
and.. and- and- and- and- and-
Crunch the Rockdog
turned Bushwoolies-
turned Bushwoolies- to STONE!
I'm gonna give that obnoxious
Rockwhatis a piece of my mind.
I can't go nowhere 'til I change
into my travellin' outfit.
Everyone!
Please remain calm!
Calm? Calm?
Only someone with no feelings
could remain calm
at a time like this.
I meant that we need
a plan of action.
She's right!
But we better find out
what makes this Rockdog tick.
And for that, we'll have to talk
to the Moochick.
Don't you worry, lil' fella.
We won't let that
walking stalagmite hurt you.
(gasps)
Hello?
Mr. Moochick?
Ooh- get it, ooh- ooh,
no, no no no, ooh, no- no,
that way!
(shrieks)
What's going on here,
Mr. Moochick?
After it!
I'll get it! There it is!
That is a.. a very smart stick.
Huh! too smart, if you ask me.
Doesn't know its place!
Aha!
Oh, he's scared!
Yes, he certainly is.
Aww, the poor little thing.
Perhaps it feels unappreciated,
or overworked?
Unappreciated?
Overworked?!
Let it have some fun.
- Yeah, give it a day off!
- Let's do that.
Well, alright!
It can have a day off
every time the mushrooms bloom.
Hah! Hm.. oh yes, yes,
that is more like it.
Now, what are you folks
doing here, hmmm?
Have you heard of
a Crunch the Rockdog?
He comes from somewhere in the
Purple Mountains.
Oh, no no no,
never heard of him.
But! If he's
from the Purple Mountains,
then you should talk
to His Elevated Eminence,
the Mountain King.
Ooh! Just head for
the Purple Mountains,
you can't miss it.
Thank you, Mr. Moochick.
At least, I think
it's His Elevated Eminence..
or is it His Royal Rockface..?
Hmmm..
This is bad, alright...
Purple Mountain!
So that's where we'll
find His Elevated Eminence, huh?
(rumbling noise)
What was that?
C-C-C-C-C-CRUNCH THE ROCKDOG!
(roars)
Look out! Behind you!
No, lil' fella! Don't do it!
Behind you! Behind you!
Behind me? Behind me?!
Oh, look!
(laughs)
Two for the price of one.
(yell frantically)
One...
Two...
(Evil laugh)
(gasp)
I can handle him.
Danny, don't!
It's just a dog.
(gasps)
Oh no!
Hey, you!
Yeah, you! You fossilized mutt!
You're a bad dog!
Bad! Bad dog, sit! sit!
(laughs)
Heel, heel!
You- you granite mongrel!
(continues to laugh)
Down boy! Lie Down... Down!
He's completely blown our cover.
At this point, I fear our
only recourse
is to make a run for it.
I think you're right.
(laughs)
What's so funny?
C'mon, Danny!
(laughs)
Heel! Sit!
After them!
Go on without me!
Gusty! What in tarnation
are you doin'?
Go on! I've got an idea!
We're not leaving you!
I'll draw them off,
and catch up at the Mountains.
Gusty,
I must protest.
Here's dust in your eye!
See? I'll blind 'em
with a small dust storm,
and I'm outta here!
Uh- oh...
Uh, come to think of it..
a little dust wouldn't have
much effect on rocks,
would it..?
Going somewhere?
(evil laugh)
Good! 'Cause I'd like you to..
(laughs)
..stick around!
(continues laughing)
Forever!