♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(bubbling)
Help!
- Help!
- She's done for!
No!
(Baby Shady coughs)
It's no use...
Hang on! Baby Shady!
It's all right now, Baby Shady.
You're fine.
Masquerade saved you.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Nothing's gonna be okay
until that walking
bad luck charm is gone.
I'm sorry Woebegone,
but you know that's true.
That's okay, Lickety-Split.
No one has ever been this kind
to me for so long as you.
But I've got to leave
before you start hating me.
That would never happen.
♪ I better go now, before
you hate me later ♪
♪ I'm going while the
getting's good ♪
♪ What's your worry? ♪
♪ What's your hurry? ♪
♪ We like having you
in the neighborhood ♪
♪ But if I don't go now
you're gonna hate me later ♪
♪ No matter what I do
it goes wrong ♪
♪ Don't be foolish ♪
♪ Don't act mulish ♪
♪ Here is where
you belong ♪
♪ Maybe you're right,
why should I move? ♪
♪ Don't be uptight,
things will improve ♪
♪ We think you're just swell
and we'll think so later ♪
♪ No matter
come what may ♪
♪ You wouldn't mind? ♪
♪ Cross our hearts
and hope to die! ♪
♪ Oh great! ♪
♪ Terrif! ♪
♪ I'll stay! ♪
It's just no use.
(thundering)
(thundering continues)
(All scream)
(bees buzzing)
Ahh!
(thundering)
Ahhh!
No!
(buzzing continues)
I'm sorry all these terrible
things are happening to him,
but I just don't see why
we should all suffer?
It doesn't have to be this way.
Golly!
It looks like
there was a fire!
Woebegone!
Where are you?
Please! Come down before
you hurt yourself.
What's the use?
I'm bound to get hurt
no matter where I am.
I just don't want you to.
So please! Go away!
(thud)
See?
No, I really don't.
Why is this happening to you?
The last time I tried to tell
you, Paradise Estate collapsed.
I hate to think what
might happen this time.
Oh, finish the story, please?!
Now let's see.
Where did I leave off?
Oh, yeah! I remember now.
There I was...
face to face with the old witch
floating in a pond of her
potion
which I knocked us into.
My friends were in
no position to help.
Help!
Even if they wanted to.
It was an accident.
It was just bad luck.
Things like this are
always happening to me.
If it would help any to say,
I'm really sorry.
Whoa!
Sorry?
You haven't begun to be sorry.
You say bad luck follows you?
Would you to be the clumsy
that you seem to think you are.
The world would
be a fearful place
for all folks near and far,
so arm yourself
with charms of luck
that may will serve you well,
for you crumbled your own cookie
and your future
is in this spell.
But, when you have a
change of mind
and believe your deeds
both good and true,
your small black cloud
will shrivel up
and the sun will shine on you.
That'll teach him a lesson.
A curse!
She put a curse on me.
(laughs)
(groans)
Ooh!
You should have seen him.
He just shoved that ol' witch
right in her own potion... Wham!
Oh, I didn't really.
It was just an accident.
Come, come my boy!
You're a hero!
Nah, I just--Really?
Absolutely!
What's going on?
What are you doing?
(wood creaking)
(thud)
Ah! Look what you've done,
you hooligan!
But I didn't.
Sure!
Just like you didn't push
that old witch in the soup.
You don't go messing around with
witches
without paying the price.
Now be off with ya...
Ya little jinx!
I guess I really am a jinx.
There! Maybe that'll
stop any bad luck
that might be hanging over me.
(thundering)
There he is!
There's the little jinx!
Woebegone, this is your fault.
I'd better leave before the
whole town floats away.
Until now, all anyone's
wanted to see of me is my back,
as I leave town.
We'll always be your
friends, Woebegone.
We don't believe in curses.
Really?
(thunders)
But maybe you feel just a
teensy bit guilty about
what happened to that old witch.
Maybe!
You've brought all that bad luck
down on yourself.
How?
Well, you believe it'll happen,
and so it does.
If ya stop believing it,
it'll stop happening.
Maybe that's what
the witch meant.
Your own bad attitude
brought your misfortune.
It even created that
little black cloud.
And when anyone felt sorry
for you and tried to help,
you believed it would be bad
for them and so it was.
The witch just brought
all your fears to life.
Maybe if you believe
in yourself,
only good things
will happen to you.
I am good. I am!
You must believe in yourself.
I am not bad luck.
I defy you to strike me.
I did it!
You sure did.
You overcame your
own worst enemy...
...yourself!
What do you want?
I wish to congratulate
my friend, Woebegone
and you as well.
You have broken my spell,
which means you have learnt a
great lesson about yourself.
All that you touch
shall be plagued no more
the evil be gone,
the good will endure.
Look at your leg.
The bandage is gone.
She fixed my leg.
She fixed my leg! Oh, thank you!
Yippee yahoo!
Oh, thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!
All right. Let's go! Let's go!
Posies' garden's fixed!
Yippee!
Lickety-Split, Lickety-Split!
Why did you bring him back for?
I just had the nursery repaired.
He's not gonna hurt the nursery.
He's not bad luck anymore.
Look! No more
little black cloud.
And I'm not hiding it
under my hat either.
I'm cured of my bad attitude,
so now nothing bad will happen.
Well, I'm going home now.
If the witch's spell is broken
that means my village
has been restored.
Have a safe journey.
I will. Thanks to you.
(all gasp)
It's okay.
It could happen to anyone.
So he's a little clumsy.
Well, nobody's perfect.