♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Howls)
Help!
Ghost is here!
Go away, ghost.
But you called me
to come back.
Well, we...we just wanted
to tell you to leave us alone.
Yeah.
This is my house!
And I want all of you to
leave!
Wait a minute.
This is our house.
Indeed!
How can you ask us to leave?
Hey, what's going on?
Look!
Oh my gosh, what is that?
It looks like some kind of
squishy bug or something. Yuck!
I am the ghost of
Paradise Estate.
Come on, let's catch it.
♪ Oh, I wouldn't try that
if I were you ♪
♪ You never know
what I might do ♪
♪ I'll disappear
then peek-a-boo ♪
♪ I'll hold your nose
'til you turn blue ♪
♪ I'd get out fast
if I were you ♪
♪ Before you end up
in a stew ♪
♪ I'd say a'hey,
stay toodledoo ♪
♪ You bit off more
than you can chew ♪
♪ I'd get out fast
if I were you ♪
♪ You won't
catch me ever ♪
♪ No one can match me... ♪
♪ I'm simply much
too clever! Clever! ♪
♪ I think it's time
that you were through ♪
♪ Or something
awful may ensue ♪
♪ Before your darkest
dreams come true ♪
♪ I'd get out fast...
I'd get out fast... ♪
♪ Oh yes, I'd get out ♪
♪ fast, fast, fast, fast, fast,
fast, fast, fast, fast... ♪
♪ If I were you! Boo! ♪
(howls)
Come on,
we can catch that spook.
Stop, please.
We just wanna talk to you.
Ghosts don't talk,
we howl ...ow!
(howls)
Ghosts don't get stuck either.
Look.
(howl fading)
Oh, I can't move.
Help me.
Who are you?
Oh, my name is Pluma.
I'm a Penna.
We're magical creatures.
We have the power to transfer...
To, er...trans...
Er...change shape.
Though I seem to
have lost control of mine.
Oh, there.
Then you're not a spirit?
Oh no! Dream Valley
used to be my home.
But today I came here
from a land far, far away.
Why did you scare
us all out of the house?
I...I got you all out?
Every one of us.
Oh, good.
Hey, what is this?
It's a trap.
Help!
Get us out.
Let us go, please!
This is probably
a practical joke, right?
I don't think so, Gingerbread.
Actually, I was... Well,
you see... I...
I was forced to
come here by Squirk.
Oh!
Who is Squirk?
The meanest thing
I can think of.
And he has been for about
ten thou...oh, er,
twenty hundred... No, it was
Well, a long, long time anyway,
which is when all this started.
Long, long before
you ponies lived here,
when all this land- every place
around here - was underwater,
and ruled by that slimy,
no-good Squirk.
Squirk was a tyrant all right,
an evil and nasty dictator...
oh, he was simply awful!
He didn't allow anyone
to say a word against him.
If they did, he used the
power of his magical amulet,
the Flashstone,
to punish them.
And he used it,
oh, mercilessly.
Oh, he was
just plain CRUEL!
(cackles)
(laughs)
Over the years,
the water mysteriously
sank back
into the earth.
Nobody knows why or how or...
That is, well,
er... It just started to go.
And soon, other creatures
came to live here,
including my kin, the Pennas.
Ruff, my grandfather,
was their leader.
The Pennas didn't
come to...to fight,
they simply wanted
a place to live.
But Squirk -
he didn't want the Pennas
living in the vicinity.
No, I should say not.
He wanted all the land
to himself
and so, using
his powerful Flashstone,
Squirk tried to chase
the Pennas away.
But my grandfather,
brave and tough as he was,
refused to be bullied.
Er... Huh?
Hey!
What? Whoah!
And, with great courage,
he took the Flashstone
away from Squirk.
He threw one half into
the deepest part of the river,
and the other half
into what came to be known
as Dream Valley, a place
Ruff knew Squirk could never go.
Squirk hid underwater
for years,
waiting for my grandfather
to get old, weaker...
Squirk didn't care.
He'll live for centuries.
Where's your
grandfather now?
Squirk has kidnapped him.
He's holding
grandfather Ruff hostage
to force me to
cooperate with him.
What does all this have to
do with us or Paradise Estate?
Uhh, well...
You'll see.
I'm so sorry, little ponies.
Oh, I really am!
I don't want to do this.
But I have no choice.
Eah! Eah...eah!
Uh...Eh!
Can't you unicorns
just disappear and re-appear
outside the net?
Yeah, then you can stop
that crazy bird.
No, unicorns can only
wink out through empty space.
Yeah, we can't wink through
stuff like this net, you know.
Then we'll never get free.
It's too strong.
Maybe I can untie us.
Try it, Buttons.
Hurry.
That's it, Buttons.
You're doing it.
It's working.
You did it.
Hooray!
One down, two to go.
Faster, Buttons.
Hurry.
Come on, you can do it.
Oh!
Oh no! Our house.
Come on.
Pluma, stop.
Whatever it is
you're doing, stop it.
Stop!
Our house!
You're gonna wreck it.
(Gasp)
Paradise Estate!