♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Look! The baby Seaponies!
They've run out of water!
They will not long survive
out of their natural habitat.
I know Wind Whistler.
But where do we find water to
put them in?
There is a pond due south
about a mile.
Okay.
Ribbon, Whistler, Lofty,
Lickety-Split, Danny and Molly,
you get the baby Seaponies
to water.
The rest of you,
come with me to the Mushromp.
You think they'll be okay?
It's up to us to make sure.
Right.
Aa...how do we do that?
By getting to the Moochick
and finding a way
to make it rain.
Come on!
(Spike)
Oh boy! I sure hope
the Moochick is figuring out
a way to keep things cool.
(fan creaking)
Welcome! Welcome!
My, my, I thought it was too hot
for anyone to come visiting.
It's because of the heat
that we're here Mr. Moochick.
I guess!
I don't suppose
everyone can enjoy the comforts
of modern technology
like Habbit and I.
A magic coin like these
started the heat wave.
Aah...oh..yes, yes, yes, yes.
These look familiar now.
Where have I seen them before?
Ooh, let's see.
Yeah, ooh, oh, well,
it's around somewhere.
Now where did I put that thing?
Oh, it...where is the...
Oh, I know it's around here
somewhere,
I just saw it now.
Oh..mmm...oh
where it could be?
I have woken up...
I have just had it yesterday.
Now! There it is!
I knew I'll find it, ow!
There's a lot to be said
for a well-organized library.
Now, according to this,
the coins come from
the treasure collection of
Niblick the Troll,
who lives far away
in the dangerous Crimson Canyon
that's beyond the jewel desert.
Of course, mm-hm.
That's all very interesting,
Mr. Moochick.
But can you do anything
to reverse the effects
of the wish?
Ooh! No, no, no, no,
absolutely not.
I'm afraid, you see,
since the treasure
belongs to Niblick,
only he can reverse its magic.
Hmm...okay.
Then we'll just go talk
to this Niblick
and ask him to help us.
Ooh...I don't know.
Trolls are usually crotchety
and ill-mannered.
And Niblick's even crankier
than most.
We don't have any choice.
Come on again!
We're off the Crimson Canyon.
Thanks for your help,
Mr. Moochick.
No, you're quite
welcome, I am sure.
Habbit!
Had you seen the book
I was reading?
I don't know
where it got through.
Oh no!
Its dried up!
Whistler, you couldn't know
the water would dry up
this quickly.
Is there somewhere else
we can go?
We just have to find water
for the Seaponies.
It's even too hot to fly.
This weather is simply death
to my complexion.
We'll have to ration
what's left of the water.
Everybody gets one cupful.
Ow...oh.
That's okay Spike.
You can have some of mine.
Thank you, Galaxy.
If we do not find water soon
Wind Whistler,
we'll be as bad off
as the poor baby Seaponies.
We've come too far
to retreat now, Megan.
The only course is
straight ahead.
Uhh..how much further
is it Megan?
Ya...I'm thirsty.
Come on guys!
Cheer up!
Everything's gonna be all right.
Sure it is, I guess.
You know, a song might make us
feel better.
♪ When the road ahead
looks bleak ♪
♪ Let a song carry you along ♪
♪ When you can't find
the answer you seek ♪
♪ Let a song carry you along ♪
♪ When you feel about to drop ♪
♪ Stop and whistle a tune ♪
♪ Soon you'll be on top of
the world ♪
♪ And the world
will be a balloon ♪
♪ Music lifts your spirits ♪
♪ And keeps you going strong ♪
♪ So when everything
seems to go wrong ♪
♪ Let a song carry you along ♪
♪ Music lifts your spirits ♪
♪ And keeps you going strong ♪
♪ So when everything
seems to go wrong ♪
♪ Let a song carry you along ♪
Don't you feel better now?
Ugh, singing made us
even more exhausted...ugh.
Water...must have water.
Galaxy, the cactus!
Use your horn on the cactus.
There might be water.
Hey, you're right!
Water!
(All gasp)
Mm...it's too bad we can't
take any to the baby Seaponies.
There used to be water here.
Well, there isn't now.
We just have to keep looking.
And hope it isn't too late.
Megan,
I don't wanna scare anyone.
But I have the distinct feeling
we're being followed.
Let's get out of here, huh,
can we? huh, please!
(all gasp)
Hiya...hiya...hiya,
Hoo..hoo...hoo
My name's Puck.
Who are you?
Uh...well, my name is Megan.
And my friends are--
So what are you doin' here?
Well, we're--
(chuckles)
Let me guess.
You're trying to find
Niblick the Troll...right?
You must be!
He's the only one
who'd live around here.
(chuckles)
Come on!
I'll take you to his house.
Well, uh...it--
It looks like we've got a guide.
If we can keep up with him.
This way, this way,
not far now.
I think
we're still being followed.
(grumbling)
And now I'm sure of it.
Puck, get us out of here!
Right!
Just follow me!
Trust me.
Hoo..hoo...hoo.
I know these gullies
like the back of my hand.
Oops!
(hungry growl)
We're trapped!
Goodbye cruel world.
As much as I hate to say it,
we'll have to use
one of the coins.
Goblins are afraid of light.
I wish there was light!
(all scream)
Hey! It worked.
And the magic didn't backfire
on us this time.
Time to go, time to go.
Hoo..hoo...hoo.
Niblick's house
is not far from here.
Sorry about
getting lost last night.
But I know my way now.
Look!
There it is!
Nah! I say hello!
Hello there!
Aah, would you be so kind
as to lower the bridge?
Sure!
But you gotta give me
your crown.
(both gasp)
Out of the question.
Now lower it I say.
I'm off to slay a dragon
and rescue a damsel.
Not unless you pay the toll.
(angrily mutters)
Th-th-this is outrageous.
Wrong!
This is your living.
You don't like it,
grow a pair of wings.
No!...Er...Very well.
I agree.
That's more like it.
(horse whines)
Oh!
The Moochick wasn't kidding.
That troll's bad news.
(gears ratchet)
(bridge slams)
Aah, I shall report you
to my father, the king.
Aah! Put an egg in your sandal
and beat it.
(giggles)
Yo-hoo!
Um, Mr. Niblick!
Would you like to know
what happened to your
chest of magic coins?
Bring 'em on over,
and I'll give you discount
on the toll.
Hold it! hold it!
I don't see no coins.
What's the deal?
Well, uh...uh...that is we--
Well, we spent them.
It was an accident,
I'm sure you understand.
You spent my magic coins?
My coins! My coins!
Ohh-ho-ho!
(gears ratchet)
(All scream)