♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony &
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
right by your side? ♪
Ooh, agh, ouch! Ow,
ooh, ahh, ouch!
(sighs)
(snoring)
Excuse me...
Uh, I think you'd better
wake up, your Bumbleness.
(snoring)
WAKE UP, YOU BUMBLEHEAD!
W...wh...what? Who? What?
What is it? What is it?
It's me, your Bumbleness.
I...I...I'm really sorry,
but I think you should know
that the Sunstone is
burning up the flowers.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's just heating them up.
But it burned my finger.
See.
Then be more careful next time.
Now be gone.
I'm not through
taking my nap.
I tried to warn her.
I really did.
It's getting awfully
warm in here.
What's going on outside?
Hey, watch where
you're dripping.
Sorry, Honeysuckle.
But there's nothing I can do.
There's nothing any of us
can do.
We could be stuck here forever.
Be brave, Flutter Ponies.
When Morning Glory
reaches Paradise Estate,
the little ponies will help us.
If Morning Glory
reaches Paradise Estate!
Sting,
can we talk for a minute?
What is it? I'm busy.
Well, if you keep the Sunstone,
we won't have a home anymore.
By sunset it will
wilt away to nothing.
You're breaking my heart,
Morning Glory.
Look, I just do what Bumble
tells me to do, understand?
Even if she
tells you to do bad things?
I'm good at bad things.
See?
But wouldn't it be more fun to
fly gracefully through the sky,
and play with your friends
in the white puffy clouds?
(sniffles)
What is it, Sting?
(Morning Glory)
What's wrong?
(sniffles)
I can't fly.
Well, that's silly.
I mean, all bees can fly.
Well, I used to fly,
but I wasn't very good.
So I just don't do it anymore.
Gee, if we only did
things we were good at,
we'd never try to make
ourselves better.
I think you should try again.
♪ Stretch yourself
to the limit ♪
♪ See how far
you can go ♪
♪ You may do wonders ♪
♪ You never know ♪
♪ Stretch yourself
to the utmost ♪
♪ See how far
you can move ♪
♪ First you'll make
blunders ♪
♪ Then you'll improve ♪
♪ Keep on working ♪
♪ keep on striving ♪
♪ Pretty soon you'll be
arriving at the top ♪
♪ Just don't stop ♪
♪ Stretch yourself
to the limit ♪
♪ Aim your sights
at the sky ♪
♪ You can work wonders ♪
♪ And you can fly ♪
(giggles)
I can fly!
Oh, thanks, Morning Glory.
You're a good kid.
My pleasure, Sting.
Uh...
(coughs)
I-I think I'll go now.
I have to try and save
the other Flutter Ponies.
Bye!
Why did you do that?
I thought we were friends.
I've got a job to do,
Morning Glory,
and keeping you
in a cage is it.
I think it's ugly.
You're right. It is ugly.
You said it was filled with
colorful flowers
and green trees.
It is...
I mean, it was...
Oh, I mean it used to be.
(sniffs)
Phew, it smells terrible!
And what happened to the
Flutter Ponies?
Where are they?
The Flutter Ponies are gone.
My Little Ponies!
(cackles)
Bumble and her bees have them.
And we have Flutter Valley.
And there's nothing you
can do about it.
(cackles)
Oh, yeah?
Whoaaah ho ho!
Reeka, Draggle,
get those little ponies!
Oof! Whooooaaaah!
I SAID GET THEM!
Surprise!
Whoah!
(gasps)
Surprise!
What are you doing here?
We left you in Furbobia.
I had a feeling you
might need me.
(giggles)
Well, I've got a surprise
of my own.
Ahhg!
Get 'em.
Rooooooaaaaaggghhhr!
Run, little ponies, run!
Nice try, little ponies.
But you're mine now.
(laughs)
What you gonna do with us?
Oh, I'll think of something.
In the meantime,
we can all sit back and watch
the sun set together.
(laughs)
(snores)
Aaaahhh!
Pointer. Pointer?
Where are you?
You called, your Bumbleness?
Tell me something, Pointer,
do you see anything
unusual going on?
I, uh,
I think Bumbleland's on fire.
Very observant, Pointer.
Do something about it!
(gasps)
Bumbleland's on fire.
No wonder it's so hot.
Oh no! We're trapped.
I guess Morning Glory
didn't make it
to Paradise Estate.
We don't know that,
Honeysuckle.
We can't give up hope.
Don't give up, Flutter Ponies.
The little ponies
will save us somehow,
I just know it.
Sometimes it's hard
not to give up hope.
What am I going to do?
My entire kingdom is burning!
Help!
(screams)
Ooh.
Oh! Whoah! Whoah!
Whoah! Whoah!
Load up, swarm.
Down here!
Drench the Sunstone!
Drop it!
(coughs)
Not me!
The Sunstone,
you bumblebrains!
Sorry, your Bumbleness.
We'll get some more.
No, we'll wait till
the fire burns itself out.
Then we'll return.
Let's get out of here.
You know,
I forgot just how good
it really feels to fly.
I'm glad I could
be of assistance.
(gasps)
Sting, look!
There's smoke coming
from Bumbleland.
It looks like a fire.
I'd better check it out.
Oh, no!
All the Flutter Ponies
are there.
Bumble? Pointer?
Where is everybody?
What did you find?
Bumbleland's on fire,
all right.
And all the bees are gone.
Sting, please let me out.
I have to save the rest
of the Flutter Ponies.
I can't, Morning Glory.
But you have to.
I thought we were friends.
We are friends.
Then you'll set me free?
No, I can't.
I'm still a bee.
Come back, Sting!
Help me!
(all)
Help! Somebody,
please help us! Help!