♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Look at that rainbow go.
Aha, just a couple more clouds
and we can start
picking the cherries
for cherries jubilee.
Yahoo,
nice job!
It sure was.
Okay, Rainbow of Light,
back where you belong.
Oh, come on, Megan! Cut loose!
Have some fun with this thing!
Danny!
What's wrong with a little rain?
(All gasp)
I mean it makes things grow.
Maybe even little sisters.
Danny!
Portable weather.
Great idea, huh Megan?
Cut it out and act your age.
Hey, look, I'm sorry.
I'll put everything
back the way it was.
I was just foolin' around.
The Rainbow of Light is the most
powerful magic in the world.
We can only use it
once in a while
and only for special things.
Okay, okay, I got it.
Anyway, it's just as well.
The sun's out.
Get a load of this.
Say cheeseburger!
We can go up for a flight and do
aerial photography of Ponyland!
Terrific! Let's go!
Danny, you be careful.
We'll be fine!
Let's just go straight.
Sounds good to me.
That was straight?
Sure! But there's a
tail wind today.
(laughs)
Oh! This is so exciting.
It is! it is!
But just wait.
It's gonna get
even more exciting.
We're gonna be the most
famous gizmonks in the world!
Gock and Gluda the Great.
Inventors of the one and only
steam-powered, multi-tasking
double-ant whistle.
Tamers of the only
lesser crested snicklewhacker
in the world!
Inventors of gadgets and gizmos
and hyper super-duper
technical things.
Some of which we don't
even know what they are, yet.
♪ But here is
the fun part ♪
♪ Inventing is such fun ♪
♪ In fact, that's number one
on our list. ♪
♪ Give that
dial a twist, ha-ha. ♪
♪ Inventing is so great. ♪
♪ Who knows what you'll
create if you try ♪
♪ Put that out to dry ♪
♪ We don't always know
what we've made ♪
♪ But inventing
gizmos, ha-ha ♪
♪ Is a lovely trade. ♪
Aha,
(laughs)
Oh, I'm impressed with us.
(giggles)
Wait!
Are you sure that's right?
Ah! Uh-ow!
Oooo oh oh! Ooo Ooo!
(laugh)
♪ It's creating something
no one else has done ♪
♪ It's a gas,
oh! It's a blast. ♪
♪ Inventing, inventing,
inventing... ♪
♪ is such fun!
I love it, I love it. ♪
(laugh)
And soon, we'll have the
neatest gadget of all.
The Rainbow of Light.
Yeah.
But we'll have to get it first.
Hey,
did you see that?
Uh-huh!
And look!
Those two are with a girl
who had the rainbow.
Execute plan A.
(laughs)
That was the best landing
we've had, yet.
Yeah. Well, I still think
I'm going to make you
a saddle with seat belts.
Where did this come from?
I think maybe where
that thing came from?
Ah... Nice monster...
(screams furiously)
Is this the sort
of the adventure?
I'll get back to you on that.
What a mess!
All right strangers.
You are prisoners
and resistance is useless.
Give us that!
Why should I?
(screams furiously)
Oh...why shouldn't I?
Here.
- Trash.
- Garbage.
Useless!
Wait a minute! Not the walkman!
No! It's a computer! Don't!
But no luck.
So...
Time to send a message.
Drudge! Drudge!
Yes sir.
Yes ma'am.
You have to go to Dream Valley
and tell the girl
with the locket
that her brother
and his pony friend
are going to be held here
until they give us the locket
with the Rainbow of Light.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Whatever you say.
And in the meantime...
Wow!
Look at that!
It won't be long, now.
We gotta find a way
out of this place.
But how? We're sealed in
and locked up!
Listen!
(whispers)
(laughs)
Last one, Megan.
Thanks, Gusty!
It went fast with your help.
Megan!
There's someone
who's asked to see you.
It's something about Danny.
What is it?
The Great Gizmonks,
Gock and Gluda have sent me
to tell you that they have your
brother and the pony, Surprise
and will give them back to you
when you give them
the Rainbow of Light.
Go home and tell
the Great Gizmonks
that I'll get back to them.
Eh, fine!
But, Megan...
Wind Whistler,
quick, follow her!
And as soon as we know
where these gizmonks are
we'll figure out
how to rescue them.
Boy!
You guys have some really
awesome techno-stuff in here!
Yeah! Awesome!
My!
Very perceptive of you!
I really like that
sub-etheric discombobulator
you have over there.
Well, eh,
how nice.
And that whistle!
A ant whistle.
Yeah, it's radical.
Really terrific!
(both)
You think so?
Oh! we could really
learn a lot from you.
Ahh!
Drudge is back!
Whoa!
Hiya, Drudge!
Are you all right?
What about the girl?
She said she's thinking it over
and she'll get
right back to you.
Oh, all right.
Drudge! Let them out.
But don't you
touch anything.
Oh, no!
We won't touch anything.
All this must have taken
years to put together.
(lever creaks)
(wheels ratchet)
(siren whistles)
(alarm rings)
No, no, no, no, no,
you mustn't!
Oh, look at this
terrific experiment!
Oh, look out!
(indistinct muttering)
(giggles)
You're doing this
in purpose.
We sure are.
We're gonna blow this joint.
Please take me with you.
(indistinct muttering)
The creature went in there,
Megan.
We're never going to
break into that place.
And what are those
strange noises?
Let's go down there.
Hey! Can you tell me
what this is over here?
Well, certainly.
(multiple overlaying
strange noises)
All right!
Thanks very much!
And that was all
I wanted to know!
Oh! No!
No rainbow is worth this!
Look!
Are they attacking us?
I don't think so!
Take them home!
My goodness!
Oh! No!
Hi, Megan!
What have you two been up to?
Being irresponsible.
In a responsible way!
(laugh)
(babbles)
Hey, Drudge, you okay?
Yes, thanks to you two.
You've set us free
from the gizmonks.
And after we rebuild this place,
we'll start making some
really useful things.
We'll help you anyway we can.
Well if Gluda and Gock
come back,
just lend us these
two heroes again.
Huh-oh, it was nothing.
We would've
done it for anybody.
(laugh)
Well, let's get home
before we miss
all that cherries jubilee.
Yum! I forgot.
Right. Heroes first.
(tremoring)
(All laugh)