♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(All scream)
There it is!
Then that's where we're going.
(All gasp and scream)
Ice! Look out!
- Don't go near it!
- Cowards!
More of you?
No matter,
I'll deal with you too.
Wrong! We'll deal with you!
(struggles)
Everybody out of here, now!
Bushwoolies! We are leaving.
- You bet! Leaving!
- Outta here.
- Wait for me.
- Gone, Yeah!
No matter where you run,
I can find you.
I will find you.
It doesn't look good,
does it Wind Whistler?
No, the desertification is
proceeding at an alarming pace.
At this rate, it will consume
Paradise Estate
in a matter of hours.
Well, we've gotten away
from Lavan and his demons,
now what do we do?
The Moochick said we have to
find the Heart of Ponyland.
The Heart of Ponyland?
I seem to recall
an ancient legend about that.
I remember too.
A magical talisman
far beneath Lavan's kingdom.
What does it do?
According to the legend,
it's the source from which our
magic wands draw their power.
Maybe if we can bring
the wands to it,
we can recharge
them with magic!
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's get moving.
What is it?
Master, we can find no trace
of the Princess Ponies
and their friends.
Incompetent fool!
(screams)
Ah!
If you want anything done right,
you have to do it yourself.
How are you Princesses
holding up?
Oh, well enough.
Considering...
Considering what?
Considering how ugly
these caverns are.
And that there are no
plants or trees or flowers.
And that...hm, sorry.
I didn't mean to complain.
♪ It's been a long hard road
that we have traveled ♪
♪ A long hard road
that we've been down ♪
♪ But we've learned
to be less selfish ♪
♪ Travelin' down
this long hard road ♪
♪ It's been a long hard road
that they have traveled ♪
♪ A long hard road
that they've been down ♪
♪ But they've learned
a hard one lesson ♪
♪ On this scary episode ♪
♪ They have learned
to be less selfish ♪
♪ Yes, we have learned
♪ Travelin' down
this long hard road ♪
There it is!
The Heart of Ponyland.
(All gasp in amazement)
Now I remember.
According to the legend,
we have to lay
our wands in the crowns
and then their power
will be restored.
Well, no time like the present.
Oh, no!
It's Lavan!
Get away from there.
(All scream)
(Evil laugh)
Oh, with every new minute,
I learn how to control
my powers more.
You have no chance!
Oh! What's going to happen?
Lavan controls
the high ground.
He can stay where he is
and pick us off,
or he can come down and get us.
What else can he do?
He could give up.
(All scream)
Ah!
But I don't think
we should count on that.
I'm gonna make
one last surveillance flight
before we return to the others.
Be careful, Wind Whistler.
(struggles)
Wind Whistler!
Oh!
I-I can't move it.
Go get the others.
But there's not enough time!
By the time
I get back with help...
Ooh, we're done for now.
Lavan's going to destroy us all.
Unless we fight back!
How?
He's too powerful.
Here's my plan.
I'll distract him
while you and then we...
(whispering)
Ponies! Surrender!
And I might let you live!
Never!
(laughs)
If that's how you want it...
Charge! Bushwoolies!
(All)
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Oh boy, Charge!
Yeah, Bushwoolies
like to charge.
Yeah, yeah, charge, charge!
Let's go! Yeah.
Uh-oh...
(Lavan groans)
Drop those wands!
Nah! I just made it!
(Bushwoolies taunt)
Get to the Heart.
I'll take care of Lavan.
(roars)
Yay!
Yeah, yay!
Uh-oh!
(ice crackles)
Stop!
Quickly!
We must work together.
(laughs loudly)
No!
He's gone.
(tremoring)
(All gasp)
Yeah, and we will be too unless
we fix Ponyland's magic.
(tremoring continues)
Let's put our wands
together again.
(struggles)
Uhh! Uhh!
Wind Whistler, look!
What does it mean,
Wind Whistler?
It means everything
is all right now, Locket.
Oh, my, my, my!
Oh, this is powerful magic.
The most powerful
there is, Habbit.
Oh, well, Magic
can't fix everything.
Everything's back to normal.
I can sense it.
We could not have defeated Lavan
without your help, Bushwoolies.
(All)
Aww, shucks... It's nothing...
In return for your bravery,
we knight you.
Henceforth, you shall
guard these crowns
as we guard the magic wands.
- Wow! Yay!
- Bushwoolies like it.
- Watch 'em close!
- Yeah!
I will keep this last one,
in memory of the Bushwoolie who
was lost in the Jewel Desert.
Uh, does anyone have any idea
how we get out of here?
That's easy, Spike.
Goodbye, my friends.
Come back and visit
the new kingdom
of the Lava Demons
and the Ice Orgs.
(giddy laughter)
Well, the magic has been put
right in Ponyland again
and Lavan is no more.
Our quest is over.
We never did decide
who should be queen.
I know!
Let's all take turns.
- Good idea!
- Perfect!
(All giggle)
A terrific idea.
It's too bad
about that poor Bushwoolie.
It's also too bad that
I lost the Rainbow of Light.
We'll never find
it in the desert.
(gasps)
Hey, everybody, look!
(All gasp)
Oh!
Here, Megan, Rainbow of Light.
(sighs)
Bushwoolie bushed!
What for dinner?
(gobbling and murmering)
(burps)
(All laugh)