♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Honeysuckle,
are you okay?
Oh, she's gone.
Gone, but not forgotten.
She'll always be remembered
as the Flutter Pony
who tried to dump me,
but got dumped herself!
(laughs)
Oh my,
I'm so poetic sometimes.
All right, back to work,
Flutter Ponies.
We'll get a new claw
and fix the crane.
But we've got to get that
Sunstone out of the hole.
I'll talk to Bumble.
No, Megan.
Talking won't work.
The Furbob's right.
I am?
Bumble's too mean
to listen to reason.
But we have to
try to find the good in people.
That's right.
I have to try.
Wait for me.
I'm coming with you!
Morning Glory.
Megan.
Grab her!
Wait, I've come to talk.
Talk?
Who are you?
What are you?
I'm Megan,
a friend of the Flutter Ponies.
I'm asking you to let them go
and give them back
their Sunstone.
(laughs)
Surely you jest,
yes?
No, as a matter of fact,
you're surrounded!
Do as I ask,
and no harm will come to you.
Agh!
Megan!
Help!
Let's go.
Yikes!
Come on, Flutter Ponies.
Let's fly.
We can't. There's still honey
on our wings.
But we can try to run again.
Swarm them!
Don't let them get away!
I'll save you, Megan.
Grab hold!
Gotchya.
Whoaaaaa!
Ugh, thanks Furbob.
- Oh...
- I've got you now, Sting.
Ouch!
(buzz)
Sting, are you okay?
I think so...
Can...can you pull
this stinger out?
Thanks, Morning Glory.
I owe ya.
To the victor
goes the Sunstone.
(buzz)
Aww, cheer up, Draggle.
Not being able to do magic
isn't the end of the world.
It is if you're a witch.
Especially if Hydia's
your mother.
Why don't you let us go?
Yeah. That'll show Hydia
she shouldn't make fun of you.
Oh no, I couldn't do that.
She'd never forgive me.
She'd kick me out of the
Volcano of Gloom for good.
What's wrong with that?
(whispers)
We have an idea, Draggle.
We'll teach you some pony magic.
You will?
Sure! Then you can make
Hydia proud of you.
She'll think
you're the greatest.
What do I have to do?
Just watch and listen.
You might want to take notes.
I'm ready.
♪ Pony magic is
the very best of magic, ♪
♪ The kind of magic
used for doing good. ♪
♪ It really comes in handy
when there's trouble, ♪
♪ If you can do what
Fizzy does and bubble ♪
♪ Pony magic is our
favorite kind of magic, ♪
♪ We know you'd use our
magic if you could. ♪
♪ Imagine just how much
you could improve things, ♪
♪ If you could be like Buttons
who can move things ♪
♪ Imagine like Surprise,
you could fly, ♪
♪ Think how far you'd get. ♪
♪ Hey, Draggle!
Let us out, ♪
♪ and we'll really
show our stuff ♪
♪ You ain't seen
nothing yet ♪
Great, let me just...
♪ Pony magic is
the greatest kind of magic... ♪
♪ Gusty here can
cause the wind to blow. ♪
♪ With pony magic, ♪
♪ our kind of magic, ♪
♪ Who knows
how far you'll go, ♪
(laughs)
Gee, what a shame.
Bye, Draggle. See ya!
You tricked me,
you miserable little ponies.
Wait 'till I get out of here!
I'll get you.
It's almost sunset.
There's not much time
to find the Sunstone!
Or the Flutter Ponies.
We've got to
get to Bumbleland now!
I think it's that way.
Hop on, Spike.
I'll give you a ride!
Through there.
Hey, it's only a painting.
It's sticking to us.
It's fly paper.
It's a trap!
(groan)
(cackles)
That's a taste of real magic,
little ponies.
Take 'em away, Ahg!
Rooaaagghhhrr.
What you gonna do to Draggle?
Something bad, I hope.
Really punish her.
Is that any way to
talk about your sister?
Well, I, Uh...
I just thought that...
Shut up!
Let's go watch
Flutter Valley rot.
It's almost sunset.
Flutter Valley's going to
shrivel up to nothing...
I'm sorry, Morning Glory.
I wasn't much help.
Don't give up.
Remember, it's never over
'till the fat lady stings!
That really makes me feel
a lot better, Sting.
(slurps)
Another one!
Sorry, your Bumbleness.
There are no more.
No more?
No more beautiful
nectar-filled flowers?
We cleaned out the forest.
There aren't any more
for miles!
But if we had the Sunstone,
it would attract the sun,
and the flowers would grow
and I'd have my nectar.
Right?
But we can't reach the
Sunstone, your Bumbleness.
Psst...
Honeysuckle!
Shh.
Get the Flutter Ponies and
go down the hole.
Don't worry, it's safe.
What about Bumble and her bees?
They've got a surprise coming.
You ready?
Now, Stonebacks, NOW!
The Stonebacks?
(Stonebacks snort)
To the hole, Flutter Ponies.
Hurry!
Honeysuckle!
But we thought you were...
What happened?
Later, Rosedust.
Just get everybody
down the hole.
Follow me, Flutter Ponies.
Hi, Honeysuckle.
Hi, Peach Blossom.
Hi, Forget-Me-Not.
What's going on here?
Whoaaaah!
Your Bumbleness!
Whoooooaaah!
That's enough, Stonebacks.
Retreat!
(snorts)
Where's the Furbob?
I thought he was with you.
I'll get him.
You're next, Sting.
Sting?
Come on, Furbob.
We have to go!
I...I can't.
I'm afraid of the Stonebacks.
They'll hurt me.
No, they won't.
They're helping us.
It must be a trick.
They're our mortal enemies.
Nothing will happen to you,
I promise.
Please, Furbob. Come on.
Move out!
Hurry!
Go on, Furbob.
You first.
Okay!
Get 'em!