♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
"And so, the giant chased
after the little grundle.
"And as he chased
he went boom, boom, boom!
"The grundle ran fast,
but the giant took giant steps.
"Boom, boom, boom!
"Coming closer and closer
and closer,
"boom, boom, boom!
The tiny grundle"
Oh, hello, Cherries Jubilee.
What's the story?
Oh, it's about
the giant that goes, boom!
I thought you're gonna
be fixing things up.
See? Everything needs work.
Not everything.
Ouch!
- (giggles)
- Oh, my.
Yes, everything.
Okay.
Baby Cuddles, why don't you run
along for your nap?
Paradise and I will get to work.
(wall crumbles)
Don't you dare.
Gosh, Paradise, I'm sorry.
It's not you, Sweet Stuff.
It's Paradise Estate.
It's simply...falling apart.
Even our tools are a mess.
But we promised
we'd fix up the Estate,
And I just couldn't face
the other ponies if we failed.
Come help me oil this shade.
Oh, dear!
I don't understand it.
It's never
this hard in fairytales.
I heard a story
once about a wizard
who cleaned up a whole kingdom
just by snapping his fingers.
I wish it were as easy for us.
There. Solid as a rock slide...!
Ah!
Whoa!
I have had it!
Come on, Sweet Stuff.
Where are we going?
To get some decent tools.
I'm glad we did this.
We needed a break, Sweet Stuff.
House work is so--so boring.
Why can't life be more like
a storybook anyway?
A good question indeed!
But chores need not be dreary,
if you have the right equipment.
Why he's got just
what we've been looking for!
Yes, but we need some nails
and a new broom and--
(chuckles)
Oh, I could sell
you all those things,
but this can of magic paint
is all you really need.
Paint?
You're kidding, right?
It will solve
all your household problems.
I guarantee anything
this paint touches will be
transformed into something new
and wonderful.
You may even have this
can as a free sample.
All right, we'll take it.
But Paradise--
Haven't you ever heard
the one about,
never look a gift pony
in the mouth?
Thank you.
(evil laugh)
Magic paint?
When Paradise?
When are you going to stop
believing such crazy stories?
Well, it can't hurt
to try it out.
You've got to admit,
it looks a little better.
(All gasp)
What do you know? It is magic.
Well, come on.
♪ Isn't it amazing
what a fresh coat of paint ♪
♪ A fresh coat of paint
can do ♪
♪ Things frayed and worn ♪
♪ Are suddenly reborn ♪
♪ Everything looks
brand new ♪
♪ Half the world awakens
with a fresh coat of paint ♪
♪ A fresh coat of paint's
like spring ♪
♪ Spirits revive,
the whole world comes alive ♪
♪ And everything
starts to sing ♪
♪ Things that are drab
seem a lot less duller ♪
♪ When you add
a touch of color ♪
♪ (all humming) ♪
♪ Brush a coat of paint on and
then you'll get a surprise ♪
♪ You'll open your eyes ♪
♪ And faint ♪
♪ You won't believe
what wonders you'll achieve ♪
♪ With a fresh
coat of paint ♪
The magic paint!
It brought everything to life.
Well, don't just stand there
with your mouths a'gapin'.
Say something!
Uh, hi!
Uh, aren't you the sofa
I was s'posed ta fixed.
Well, the very same!
Only I fix myself.
Good as new, don't ya know?
Can I help? Can I help?
Huh?
Can I? Can I?
Oh, uh, certainly.
Don't step on the begonias!
Uh-oh...
I need more water.
(gasp)
I'll get it.
Fill 'er up, buddy!
(laughing)
That tickles!
(both giggle)
You're my favorite baby buggy.
You're my bestest friend ever.
And I always
will be Baby Cuddles.
Oh! I love you.
♪ La, la. La, la. ♪
♪ La, la. La, la, la.
La la, la, la. ♪
(water boiling)
Hey, turn me down already.
I am boiling over!
Okay, okay, don't have a fit.
Hey, hurry it up already!
You think I wanna be stuck
in this goop all day?
Oh!
Come on, Cherries Jubilee,
you can do it.
Just ten more reps, that's it.
Come on.
Go, Jubilee, go!
Hey, lighten up, huh?
Hey! Wipe yer' feet!
I was just polished.
Well, excuse me!
I've wanted to give
these wretched ponies
a piece of my mind
for some time now.
What's going on, Paradise?
The whole place
is getting so pushy.
(all arguing)
Oh, yeah. Come on. Watch it!
(humming)
Watch it.
Don't trample the petunias.
Sorry...
I-I'll be more careful...
Lay off.
The roses
don't need much water.
Okay, okay.
This nag doesn't know
what to do.
She only gets in the way.
I say get rid of her.
I'll--I'll--I'll do better.
I promise.
Scram!
(All shouting)
Beat it! Yes! That way!
My garden...
(All shouting)
Hey! Snap it up,
little slowpoke! C'Mon! Hurry!
I'm gonna have a
nervous breakdown.
Oh!
Back to work!
Cupcake!
Over here.
Am I glad to see you!
(All shouting)
Harder! C'mon! Harder!
Sweep me!
Polish me!
Dust me!
Harder, faster!
(panting)
Oh, I can't take it anymore.
You can't quit now.
You've still got 20 sets to go!
(wailing)
Oh, oh!
I can't take it!
And where do you think
you're goin'?
Let me out!
Cherries Jubilee... Run for it!
You ponies can't
keep nothing neat.
Why, we do a better job
ourselves, don't ya know?
(ponies shout)
(shouting)
Go, shoo!
(sneezing)
(shouting continues)
(shouting)
♪ La la, la la, la la, ♪
♪ la la, la laaa, ♪
♪ la la la la, la laaa. ♪
What's going on?
Baby Cuddles!
Paradise, what's the matter?
We've got to get out of here.
No! Don't wanna leave my buggy.
Baby Cuddles, don't leave me.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Is that everyone?
Almost.
You clods,
You're crushin' my fibers.
Ah! Oof!
Stay out!
(sobbing)
But that's our home.
Not anymore, Sweet Stuff.
(both sob)