♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
What's Pluma doing?
I found it!
But you destroyed
Paradise Estate.
I had to destroy the estate
to get to the amulet.
If I don't give this to Squirk,
I'll never see
my grandfather again - ever!
Oh yeah?
Well, what about us?
Please try to understand.
Perhaps I can restore
it with this.
Now, let's see...
I mean, it's a matter
of thinking about...
what you...
Uh, that is to say...
You mean the Flashstone will do
whatever he or she wills?
Oh, exactly!
Then do it.
Oh, sounds like
it's working!
Huh? Well,
that sure looks weird.
I'm sorry.
But it's the best I can do
without the other half
of the amulet.
(sobs)
Our home no good.
Still can't live there.
Shh, Baby Heart Throb.
We'll get it fixed somehow.
Do you know where the
other half of the amulet is?
No. But with this half,
the other half can be found.
Uh... I think that's
what grandfather said.
Then let's
look for it together.
No, no, no!
We don't have time.
I have to get this to
Squirk right away.
There must be something
we can do.
Buttons, Fizzy, come on!
I've got an idea.
So, how's your
ancient feathered friend?
Oh, so help me, Squirk.
If I ever get out of here,
by cracky,
I...I... Oh...Oh...
Give it up, grandpa!
Your powers are gone.
(Crank)
Oh look it, Squirk. He's trying
to change shape to escape.
Oh, relax!
He's so old
he can't even change his mind.
(laughs)
Hey-ho!
That's a good one, Squirk!
(laughs)
A real good one...
Shut up!
So where is this Squirk?
What if he doesn't
see Pluma's signal?
Oh, I'm sure he will!
All this water
makes me nervous.
Dragons don't swim
very well, you know.
But I've never tried to
make such big bubbles, Megan.
You can do it, Fizzy.
Go for it.
Wow!
Wow, this is neat!
Terrific, Fizzy!
Now make one for Danny.
Now we may need some help
getting down there.
What's that, Megan?
It's the signal shell
that I got from the sea ponies.
They said use it any time
I needed them.
♪ Shoop be doo
Shoop shoop be doo ♪
- Baby Sea Ponies!
- All right!
Too old, am I?
Huh!
I'll show you who's too old!
Quiet down.
I can hear your
feathers squeaking.
As long as I'm alive, Squirk,
you'll never rule
this land again.
I've got news for you, Ruff.
When I get the Flashstone back,
that's exactly what I'll do.
Why, I'm gonna flood the land
just like it was before!
(laughs)
Hey, where is Pluma anyway?
She should have signaled
by now.
There's the signal now.
(wheezes)
Well, what are you
lying around for?
Get going and follow it!
Yes... Yes Squirk!
Right away.
I'm on my way -
right now, right now!
Crank?
Where's Squirk?
He's busy.
Give it to me!
You want it?
Come get it.
Ready Buttons?
Now!
Oh no!
[All gasp]
What in tarnation...
Who are you?
Friends of Pluma. We're here
to help you escape.
Squirk's going to
be mad at you, Crank.
He already is!
Er...uh...um...hi, boss.
(gasp)
Yikes!
(growls)
Got ya!
(gasp)
Hey! Let go, before
I pull you under with it!
Give it back!
- Hold on, Crank!
- I am!
I've got you at last!
Wait for me.
Hurry, Fizzy, before
Squirk and Crank get back.
Going somewhere?
(growls)
We've got to do something before
all those plants are eaten away.
(gasps)
Pluma, can you change
shape and get us out of here?
I'll try...
Come on, Pluma!
You can do it.
Try harder, my dear!
Can't.
The ropes are too tight.
Then Ponyland's doomed.
Now all I've gotta do is
find the other half of this...
Heh, heh!
And I'll rule again!
♪ I am the meanest
meanie I ever met ♪
♪ But I'm just half as bad
as I'm gonna get ♪
♪ Why should
I be humble? ♪
♪ I'll make
the mountains crumble ♪
♪ You ain't
seen nothin' yet ♪
♪ When I'm in power watch
my enemies sweat ♪
♪ He'll zap them all
without a moment's regret ♪
♪ Let them
try attacking... ♪
♪ They'll get
a shellacking... ♪
♪ You ain't
seen nothin' yet ♪
(laughs)
♪ I make a promise,
no idle threat ♪
♪ I'll be a baddie
they won't ever forget ♪
♪ Better start praying
or soon you'll be paying... ♪
♪ Like the man
was saying... ♪
♪ As I was saying... ♪
♪ You ain't seen nothin'...
You ain't seen nothin'... ♪
♪ You ain't seen
nothin' yet ♪ ♪
(laughs)
Shut up!
Water coming.
I scared.
Don't worry, Baby Cuddles.
We'll stop it.