♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(cracking and tremoring)
Wha-What's that?
Come on! Let's find out.
(cracking and tremoring)
Well, how about that!
Aren't they the strangest
looking creatures?
(Whizzer)
They're strange all right,
strange as in ugly!
Never mind that, Whizzer.
We'd better do something...
before they rip up all
of Dream Valley.
(clears throat)
Ahem!
May I speak to you a moment?
I said I'd like to
speak to you for a...
Sorry ma'am, no time.
Gotta find the Flories.
Captain's right, ma'am.
Those Flories could
be hiding anywhere,
even in...here.
Now you stop that
right this instant.
You heard the Captain, ma'am.
Can't stop now.
(sighs)
But-but...this is no
way to find anything.
We gotta get help!
Yeah! We gotta find Megan.
(panting)
Feels like we've been
running for days.
Oh!
Ooh!
We have!
(both panting)
Come on! Hurry! Soil.
Gotta find some
rich fertile soil.
And water!
Can't go another
step...without water.
Look, we're saved!
Rich soil!
Oh! Yeah! We're saved.
Oh..oh boy, oh boy.
(laughs)
(continues panting)
Just hold it.
No!
There's some kind of
creature in there.
(bird chirps)
It...It seems nice,
whatever it is!
I think it likes flowers.
An-and it has water!
If that creature cared
for us like that,
we'd be-be-be-be back on our
roots in no time.
(giggles)
Wait! It doesn't know us.
We've got to be careful
not to frighten it.
Yeah!
Follow me!
Ya all look so beautiful today.
I'm so proud of each
and every one of you.
(bird chirps)
Yes, you too!
(chirping continues)
♪ How does my
garden grow ♪
♪ With lots of
tender care ♪
♪ When there is
care to spare ♪
♪ Flowers blossom
everywhere ♪
♪ It doesn't take
a magic wand ♪
♪ To make a
daffodil respond ♪
♪ Oh, anyone can make
a rosebud sprout ♪
♪ If you want a
healthy fern ♪
♪ Simply show it
some concern ♪
♪ Affection is what
it's all about ♪
♪ What makes my
garden bloom ♪
♪ My seedlings
have no fear ♪
♪ They know that
mother's near ♪
♪ If the fate
should interfere ♪
♪ They all depend on
me, their friend ♪
♪ To weed, and rake,
and hoe ♪
♪ I give my flowers love ♪
♪ And it's love that
makes my garden grow ♪
Hello!
(gasps)
Ah!
You, You gave me a start.
Umm...wh-who are you?
Can't talk.
Need water, fertile soil.
- Help! Need water.
- Fertile soil!
You poor things.
You're half-starved.
How can I help?
We need to be in
rich fertile soil!
Oh!
I have the perfect
place for you.
You'll love it.
I was saving it for
my prize roses,
but I'm sure they won't mind.
(All exhort)
Ooh! Aah! Ooh!
Posey, we heard voices in--
(bird chirps)
Posey, who're you talking to?
Megan, Cherries Jubilee, hi!
Oh, now I see.
You're planting
some new flowers.
They're pretty.
They look pretty sick to me.
Oh, yeah! You don't look
so hot yourself you...
You...you move! You talk!
What are you?
Flories, from far away.
Chased here.
They're trying to hurt us.
Who is?
Terrible creatures.
Crab Nasties.
Crab Nasties?
Ohh, they sound icky.
Shame on them, mistreating
such lovely flowers as you.
Why are these Crab Nasties
after you?
They're mean and nasty.
They've driven us from our home
on the other side
of the big lake.
They tried to capture us.
But we escaped.
And they've come after us.
to hunt us down and enslave us.
We've suffered so
at their hands.
You mean at their claws!
Claws?
So it's you those
creatures were after...
You've seen them?
Yes!
And we think they're
headed this way.
Woe is us!
Help us! Help us!
Don't worry, you
poor little things.
We'll protect you.
But those crab things
don't seem cruel.
(trees falling)
(trees extirpate)
(both gasp)
Look! There they are.
After them!
Get out of here!
Go on! Scat!
That's it.
Turn 'em over on their backs.
They're completely
helpless that way.
- Give it to 'em.
- Hip hip hurray!
Step on him.
Oh, this is too much!
(All chuckle)
You got 'em, yeah!
(claws snip)
(crab cackles)
I have you at last.
Puff!
(rock shatters)
Phew!
That's the last of 'em.
Now what we do with them?
(crab groans)
Lock them up in a cage of stone
till we're strong.
Then...we'll take care of them.
(chuckles)
But ma'am, you've
got to believe us.
We were after them
because we're police
and they are escaped convicts.
That's right, ma'am.
Ma'am, they ruin the soil.
(rock gate rumbles)
There'll be
nothing left but brown dirt.
I can't believe you.
The Flories haven't
done any damage,
but you, you went and
trampled my garden.
I don't know.
I'm getting a bad
feeling about this.
I think I'd better keep an
eye on those Flories.
(snore)
Are...are they gone?
Would you relax?
(chuckles)
What a sweetheart setup!
Thanks to those
four-legged suckers,
the long claws of
the law are trapped
where they can't give
us anymore grief.
All this land is ours!
Yeah, this garden is
only an appetizer.
(chuckles)
So what are we waiting for?
Come on! Dig in!
(gulping sound)
Yeah!
Hey! Whose hogging all
the magnesium?
Leave some for me.
Say, get your elbow
out of my face!
Spread out!
(Flories sprawl)
(twig snaps)
Well, well, well!
Looks like one of those
multi-colored dingbags
is smarter than we thought.
I guess this'll teach ya
who to root for, huh?
(laughs)