♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Ooh, don't-don't you think
that's enough, Bumble?
You don't want to
drown them?
I don't.
Oh well, of course I don't.
I just want
to GROUND them.
(laughs)
That's enough.
How about if I get
you some more nectar,
your...your...your...
Bumbleness?
Ugh, I'm afraid we're stuck,
Flutter Ponies.
I can hardly move.
I can!
Oh, I'm trying, Honeysuckle.
There's a tiny opening...If...
if I can only get up there,
maybe I can escape.
You can do it, Morning Glory.
Just a little more.
One more step to freedom.
(cheers)
Hey, you can't do that!
Oh no!
Buzz...ooh!
Hey, Stonebacks!
(giggles)
Up here.
Bet you can't catch me.
Na na na na na...
(snorts)
It's not working, Surprise.
I'd make a bubble,
but what good would it do?
What's Gusty doing?
Trying to blow them away.
It's not working.
Oh, they're too, too heavy.
I...I can't do it.
Wish them away, Wishful.
Oh, I wish I could.
- Try it, yeah.
- At least try.
I wish...I wish
the Stonebacks would go away.
(snorts)
Some wish.
Yeah,
we could do that.
Get ready to run.
I have an idea.
Run, everyone!
(grunt)
In here, Furbobs.
Hurry!
I knew we lived this way.
(snorts)
Welcome to Furbobia!
Ooh, it's beautiful!
And these are
the rest of the Furbobs...
- Hi!
- Hello!
- Goodbye.
- Glad to see you.
- No, we're not.
- What's up?
We need your help.
Baby Cuddles hurt her leg.
Prepare the steamer!
The steamer?
Me not want to get steamed.
(gasps)
I...I'm getting tired.
My wings are heavy
from the honey.
I'll never make it
to the little ponies.
I don't suhelp? you could
Well,
thanks anyway.
Flutter Pony!
Get her!
Oh dear!
Oh... Oh no!
My wings won't work.
Oh... It's hard to be a hero...
Back to Bumbleland!
No! Help!
Ugh,
I drank so much nectar,
I'm going to explode.
I told you to take it easy,
your Bumbleness.
Too much of a good thing
makes it bad.
Spare me the wisdom of your
philosophy, Sting,
and remove my slippers.
Ahh...that's better.
The escapee.
Well done, Pointer.
You may go now.
And just where did you think
you were going? Hmm?
Please don't hurt me.
I won't try to escape again.
I don't think you will either.
Sting,
place this sticky little
Flutter Pony in the cage.
And this time,
YOU guard her!
Oh, do I have to...
Do you wish to continue
being my right hand bee?
Well, to tell you the truth...
Just do it!
Oh, let's go. Let's go!
It's just you and me now.
Move it out!
Ooh!
Is it getting warm in here,
or is it just me?
(yawns)
I'm so sleepy...
(snores)
I scared, Spike.
Aww, don't worry.
I'm here.
I won't let anything
bad happen to you.
Are you sure
this is gonna work?
As sure as I'm a Furbob.
We do it all the time.
Besides, they are our cousins.
They wouldn't do anything bad.
No, never, uhuh.
Nothing bad.
Baby Cuddles will be
as good as new.
What's that?
Shh...
They're starting.
♪ Nature's in harmony -
doo-ah, doo-ah ♪
♪ Hear that sweet melody
- doo-ah, doo-ah ♪
♪ Nature's in harmony -
doo-ah, doo-ah ♪
♪ Nature's a symphony -
♪ Nature's in harmony -
doo-ah, doo-ah ♪
♪ Nature's music has powers
to restore us ♪
♪ It makes us feel,
It helps us heal ♪
♪ Come and join
the chorus ♪
♪ Nature's in harmony
- doo-ah, doo-ah ♪
♪ Singing a rhapsody,
All of us here agree ♪
♪ Nature's in harmony... ♪
♪ Doo-ah, doo-ah ♪
It worked!
Me all better.
Thanks for your help, Furbobs.
But I'm afraid we have to
leave now
and get back
to Paradise Estate.
Before you go,
do you think you could
help us with the Stonebacks?
Yeah, they destroy
every place we live.
They haven't found this one.
They will.
You helped us, Furbobs,
so we'll help you.
Let's get them!
Wait, Gusty!
There are too many Stonebacks.
Why don't we ask
the Flutter Ponies
to help us help the Furbobs?
Because we can do
it ourselves, that's why.
Fizzy's right.
We'll go back to Flutter
and get the Flutter Ponies.
It's too dangerous alone.
Hi.
Spike?
I thought you were staying
behind with the others.
Us dragons are brave and tough.
I thought you might need me.
Aaaah, what was that!
Oof!
(laughs)
What happened
to brave and tough?
Well, I'm pretty sure
we're tough.
Come on!
The way out of the orchard's
this way. I think...
(snorts)
Soon, my little girls,
Flutter Valley will be
wilted and ugly,
and we'll have a
new place to live.
(cackles)
Ow!
I'm not so sure I want to
the Volcano of Gloom, Hydia.
Me either.
It's hard to start over
in a new neighborhood.
You'll do
what I tell you to do!
Besides,
I've always wanted an
ugly old place in the country.
Some acreage,
a dried up stream...
The perfect setting to
raise a family.
I'm going to win, girls!
(Laughs)
It's my turn.
My turn.
Oh, I won, I won!
Rooaaaaggghhhr!
How much longer till
Flutter Valley turns rotten?
Just as soon as the sun sets.
Then it's goodbye sun,
goodbye Flutter Valley!