♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Never see
other ponies again.
(sniffles)
Maybe they
look for us right now?
Let us out of here!
(sniffles)
We've got
to find our babies!
Save your breath.
They won't let us go.
But we
didn't do anything.
Didn't do anything?
You've done plenty.
Or rather,
your friend Knight Shade did.
We don't know what's wrong,
but we're not gonna let you do
that to the rest of 'em.
But Knight Shade
is not our friend.
So you say...
Say.. I've got it.
Mr. Mayor, look at the
sick children.
They cast no shadows.
That's the reason
they're sick.
Knight Shade must have stolen
their shadows.
That makes sense.
No doubt they
feel empty and incomplete.
The loss of their shadows
being an outward sign
of some loss of substance.
Please, Mr. Mayor, you must
let us go.
What happened to your children
could be happening to
the Baby Ponies right now.
We must be free
to stop this Knight Shade.
Well, perhaps
I will let you go.
(cheer)
But, Sheriff Ricotta and I will
go with you.
You'll need our help to get past
our nasty cousins, the Roadies!
(crying)
Nobody comin' to save us..
Where grown-ups?
Can't give up!
Hey...let's sing!
(All crying)
I wonder where the
Baby Ponies could be?
(crying continues)
Our babies!
The coast is clear.
We're so glad
we've found you.
But you're so pale.
We're sick..
Knight Shade stole shadows..
Well, he's not gonna get
away with it.
We're going to make him
give those shadows back.
(Molly)
There he is.
Let's go after him.
Where?
He's on his way to his trailer.
Let's go get him!
What is that
in the mirror?
It looks as
if that looking-glass
could use a good cleaning to me.
You fiend!
You'd better give our babies'
back their shadows or else!
We're gonna make you pay
for what you did
to our children.
Yep!
(All)
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
We've gotta catch Knight Shade.
Or we'll never get
our babies' shadows.
Look at that!
Uh...oh...uh...
I didn't wanna do it.
Then why did you?
He made me do it.
Who?
Erebus.
He's a wizard.
He looks like a big,
gray storm cloud.
That must be the
thing we saw in the mirror.
Yes!
That's how
he gives me my orders.
What kind of orders?
To steal shadows for him.
Although Zeb is the one
who actually steals 'em.
He puts them
in his satchel.
You mean, the babies' shadows
were in the satchel
he was carrying?
Yeah,
that's right!
And we let him get away...
Was he taking them to Erebus?
Yeah!
So you see, I couldn't
give back your babies' shadows.
I haven't got 'em.
What does Erebus do
with the shadows?
I don't know exactly,
but they give him power.
Power which he uses to make me
do what he wants.
You see, I come from Grayvale,
a place that used
to be called Bright Valley.
I tried my best
as a singer there,
but nobody
came to see me.
I was ready to give up,
then Erebus came along.
He said he was a wizard
and promised to make me a star
All he said
he wanted in return..
was a little cooperation.
The first concert he promoted
in Bright Valley was a smash.
Everyone in town was there.
(cheering)
And while I was singing,
Erebus had Zeb steal
everyone's shadow -
including my own mother's.
When I saw what
Erebus had done,
I refused to work
for him anymore,
and I demanded that he give
everyone their shadows back!
But he threatened
to steal my shadow..
(evil laugh)
...and he laughed at me.
I didn't know then
that the shadows provided
Erebus with energy
that gave him his
magical powers.
And he used the energy
from the shadows
to make himself
into this huge cloud of energy.
I don't know how he does that-
it's a closely guarded secret.
I'm not even sure Zeb knows.
Then Erebus made me take my act
on the road,
and he sent Zeb along to
do the shadow stealing.
And as I became famous,
more fans came to see me.
Zeb stole more shadows
and Erebus became
even more powerful.
his hunger for power is
endless.
And I'm forced to help
Zeb supply him
with more and more shadows.
If I don't help him,
he'll steal my shadow,
which would end my career.
But worse, it would mean that
I'd never have any hope of
restoring Grayvale
and my mother,
to the way they used to be.
Please let him go,
he didn't really wanna hurt us.
What do you think?
Well, the poor creature
didn't have any choice, did he?
Thank you, Baby Heart Throb.
You know, you're so lucky
to have loved ones
who care about you so much.
I have a wonderful mother,
but she--
(sniffles)
she has to live with
the terrible shame of
what I've done,
to her and Grayvale.
(All crying)
I think we oughta
help Knight Shade.
You mean we should
fight Erebus ourselves?
Exactly!
That's the only way
we'll ever get
the babies' shadows back.
And our
children's shadows, too.
(sniffles)
Yup.
And my mother's,
and the rest of Grayvale's.
Well, what are we waiting for,
guys?
Knight Shade, show us
the way to Grayvale.
(All)
Alright! Yeah!
Where is everybody?
I think
they must be in hiding.
Knight Shade...
Knight Shade!
(gasp)
You've got a lot of nerve
coming back here, Knight Shade.
(menacingly)
And you'll be sorry you did...
♪ We're gonna
make you sorry ♪
kick up a fuss ♪
♪ We're gonna make you sorry
you tangled with us ♪
♪ We'll make you regret
the day ♪
♪ You stole
our shadows away ♪
♪ You chose
a nasty game to play ♪
♪ And now we're
gonna make you pa-a-a-a-y ♪
♪ We're gonna
make you sorry ♪
do it to you ♪
♪ We're gonna
make you sorry ♪
♪ And when
we are through ♪
♪ No one in this world will
be as gloomy and forlorn ♪
♪ We're gonna
make you sorry ♪
♪ You wanna know
how sorry ♪
♪ You're gonna
be real sorry ♪
♪ Sorry you
were ever born... ♪
♪ You'll be sorry
you were ever born ♪