♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(Stonebacks snorting)
Help! Help!
Somebody! Help us!
(snorts)
- Somebody!
- Anybody!
Stop, Stonebacks.
Don't do this.
(All scream)
Help!
I'll make a parachute.
Oh, Fizzy, thank you.
Oh, we're safe.
Oh, thank goodness we're safe.
(All)
Yeah! Yeah, safe! Safe!
(snorts)
Why don't
the Stonebacks like you?
(All)
Yeah, why? Why, why?
Why not? Why?
Because we wouldn't
play with them.
That's not why.
It's because they smell bad.
They don't smell bad.
We've been fighting so long,
I guess we don't remember
why we're fighting.
My leg hurts.
Oh, Baby Cuddles.
What happened?
Don't know.
Can't walk.
And it's a long way
back to Paradise Estate.
Come home
to Furbobia with us.
We'll fix you up.
- This way.
- That way.
This had better work, Reeka.
I desperately want
that Sunstone.
Oh, don't worry, Bumble.
Is your swarm ready?
They but await
my special signal.
A special signal?
Then get ready to give it.
Smirtlab, wilmot,
crock and zerb!
Look, a rainbow.
Isn't it beautiful?
But it didn't even rain.
Proceed after me, swarm.
That's the worst
special signal I ever heard.
Take it to Bumbleland.
They're stealing
our Sunstone.
I knew it.
This rainbow's a phony.
Hurry!
We have to get the Sunstone
back before sunset,
or Flutter Valley will die.
Farewell, Flutter Ponies.
The Valley's ours now.
(laughs)
We're gaining on them.
To the hives!
(gasp)
They've gone into Bumbleland.
Wait!
What if it's a trap?
We can't argue
about it now.
Let's go.
Sting,
prepare the honeycomb.
Where did you go?
Yes, your bumbleness.
Right away.
What are you doing?
I'm going.
I'll get the honeycomb ready.
Okay?
I'll get it.
Oh, how does anything
ever get done around here?
(gasp)
The Sunstone!
I don't think
it's a good idea.
Why doesn't anybody
listen to me?
Let's get it.
Wait!
Help!
We're trapped!
We can't get out!
(laughs)
You're mine now,
my little Flutter Ponies.
And I've got
some marvelous plans for you.
But first...
(slurps)
Sting, place the Sunstone
to reflect the sun.
Bring forth those golden rays
that will make Bumbleland
drip with rich,
nectar-bearing flowers!
♪ Dark and dirty,
Isn't it wonderful ♪
♪ Dank and dingy,
Isn't it grand ♪
♪ We love
watching flowers wilt ♪
♪ Hey, watch out!
The ketchup spilled ♪
♪ Dark and dirty,
Isn't it beautiful ♪
♪ Nice and shiny
we cannot stand ♪
♪ We prefer
when things look seedy ♪
♪ Shirts unlaundered,
gardens weedy ♪
♪ Why bother making
things look neat ♪
♪ Messy, scattered,
soiled and tattered ♪
♪ Simply can't be beat ♪
♪ Dark and dirty,
We think it's fabulous ♪
♪ Nothing can compare ♪
♪ How we wish
that dark and dirty ♪
♪ Flourished everywhere ♪
♪ Oh, dark and dirty!
Isn't it wonderful ♪
♪ Dark and dirty,
We think it's fabulous ♪
♪ Dark and dirty ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
By sunset,
Flutter Valley will be
just the way we like it.
(All)
Wilted!
(cackles)
Aww, are we getting
close to Furbobia?
- No!
- Yes!
I think we'd better
rest for a while.
Me too heavy?
Don't you worry about a thing,
Baby Cuddles.
Everything's going to be fine.
Cupcake is right.
That leg of yours
will be fixed up in no time.
Right, Furbobs?
- Definitely!
- Maybe!
Ahh, Gee, I wish we
could have some apples.
Yeah, an apple.
- Me too!
- I want one.
Gosh, Wishful.
That was terrific.
You mean all you have to do
is make a wish
and you get what you wish for?
(gasp)
Gosh!
Well, it doesn't
work all the time.
No, not all the time.
- Sometimes. Once in a while.
- Rarely.
I think we'd better be
moving on to Furbobia.
The sun is going to set soon.
Ready, little ponies?
Ready.
Let's do it.
Lift!
To Furbobia!
Ouch! Huh?
I think it's that way.
(snorts)
On second thought,
maybe it's that way?
(snorts)
(gasps)
I wonder
if they speak our language.
(snorts)
I don't think so.
What are we going to do?
- Yeah, what?
Maybe I could snort to them.
I heard my dad do it once
a long time ago.
(snorts)
What did you say, Spike?
I...I don't know...
Oh, goodie, goodie!
I can't wait.
(slurps)
More!
I want more!
Don't you think you ought
to wait a few minutes?
I've been waiting
a lifetime for this, Sting.
Get me some more.
Ah...yes, your Bumbleness.
Whatever you say.
Do you still want to turn
the other wing, Morning Glory?
There must be a
simple explanation
for this seemingly mean act.
There is.
Bumble got the Sunstone,
the witches got Flutter Valley,
and we got...
Honeysuckle, Morning Glory,
what's done is done.
What we have to do now
is get out of here.
We have one chance,
Flutter Ponies.
If we try very hard,
maybe we can blow down
these walls and escape.
We can do it, Rosedust.
We're with you!
We'll try anything!
Let's do it.
All right, Flutter Ponies.
Shift to Utter Flutter!
Release the honey!
There is no escape now,
Flutter Ponies.
You will be my slaves!
(slurps)
Yes, slaves!
(cackles)