♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Look out, Twilight.
Here I go!
Now it's my turn!
(sighs)
I could have made it.
I wish,
I wish, I wish!
I'm going for the
double inside-out loop!
But it's dangerous, Firefly.
Danger is my life, Medley!
Firefly! Look out!
(laugh)
Apple sauce, anyone?
♪ Sunny and pleasant
Here in the present ♪
♪ No sign of trouble
in sight ♪
♪ My Little Pony,
My Little Pony, ♪
♪ May all your days
be bright ♪
Twilight,
will I ever fly like
Firefly and Medley?
No, Ember.
Not all little ponies can fly.
Will I jump far like Bow Tie?
Or disappear like you can?
Ember, you'll grow up to
be your own special little pony.
Everybody, quick! Come on.
Oh no! No way...
Oh no...
(squeaking)
Ahh..
What's going on?
- It's the Stratadons!
- Stratadons?
Run!
Help! Help!
Seize them!
Whoaaaaaah, help!
You are all doomed.
Soon every pony
will belong to Tirrac,
the master of Midnight Castle.
Help! Aah!
Firefly,
no! Wait!
Where are you going?
To get help!
No, come back!
It's too dangerous!
Firefly, come back!
Come back!
Listen, Scorpan,
can I go with you next time?
Huh?
- Can I? Can I?
- No, Spike.
I can slither really fast,
Scorpan, really fast.
- Not now, Spike, not now.
- Aww...
(Tirrac )
Quiet, my friend.
Your time will come.
We have captured two
of the little ponies, Master.
Have you forgotten something,
Scorpan?
Yes, that is better.
Two ponies, you say?
Only two?
Yes, Master.
But I need four ponies
for my chariot.
Not two, not three, four.
Yeah, Yeah,
but he tried to get them,
Master Honest
I mean honestly,
he really
and truly tried and...
Silence!
You will prepare another raid,
Scorpan...NOW!
As you wish...Master.
That is precisely what I wish.
Look, TJ a shooting star!
Whoah! Whoooooah!
Whooooooaaaaaaaaaah!
Whatever it is,
it sure is heavy!
- Hello.
- Talking pony?!
Ugh. I can fly too.
At least I could before
my wings got soaked!
(whinnies)
Sorry.
What...who are you?
My name's Firefly.
What's yours?
Megan, and...and that's
my pony, TJ.
Hey! Firefly,
where are you going?
Slow down.
Yep, Yep, Yep,
looks high enough...
High enough...
high enough for what?
Hop on.
Uh...you do know how to ride,
I hope?
- Of Course I know how to ride.
- Great!
Hey! Where are we going?
To help my friends,
they need you.
Me? What can I do?
- You're strong.
- No, I'm not.
- You can fight.
- No, I can't.
And you can fly.
I said I could ride...not fly!
Oh, my friends are just
gonna love you!
No, they won't!
Ponyfeathers.
♪ They'll be dancing on air ♪
♪ When they meet you ♪
♪ Dancing on air with glee ♪
♪ I doubt they'll
be celebrating ♪
♪ When they see it's only me ♪
♪ They'll do cartwheels
in air ♪
♪ When they greet you ♪
♪ Their hopes will start
to rise ♪
♪ From what they're
anticipating ♪
♪ They're in for
a big surprise ♪
♪ They'll be floating ♪
♪ Lighter than a cloud.
They'll be floating ♪
♪ laughing right out loud ♪
♪ The sight of you ♪
♪ Will send spirits flying ♪
♪ One or two may
burst out crying ♪
Why can't you believe?
You're gonna be great.
- But Firefly...
- Trust me!
♪ Megan, you're a dream
come true ♪
♪ That my friends all
think so too ♪
♪ You're the answer to
our every prayer ♪
♪ Time will tell
if I come through ♪
♪ But just imagine if I do ♪
♪ They'll be dancing ♪
♪ Prancing ♪
♪ Dancing on air ♪
(All)
Firefly! Firefly! You're okay.
This is Megan, everybody.
She's here to help us!
(All)
Hooray!
(thundering)
Run, everybody!
Run!
(shrieks)
Help!
(screams)
Somebody do somethin'.
Agh! The double-inside-out loop.
It's the only way.
(screams)
Help!
MEGAN!
(screams)
Leave this land.
This battle is not yours.
What are you doing?
You...you...you beast!
You're a monster.
Do you hear me?
A monster!
See? Whoo, you are brave.
Am not, he just got me mad,
that's all.
Now come on.
We'll save our friends...
somehow.
(Ponies groan)
Help me! Help me! Help me!
No, please!
Help!
Let us go.
(Tirrac)
Silence!
That's better.
Guards, remove the small one.
Oh...You won't hurt Ember?
She is too small to pull
my Chariot of Midnight
as you should have known,
Scorpan.
Ow!
But you three will do...for now.
Behold the Power of Darkness!
(scream)
(growls)
What's happened to my friends?
They belong to me now.
And, Scorpan, if by midnight
I do not have a fourth pony,
a head will roll...HIS!
(evil laugh)
The Moochick has magic powers.
He'll help us.
He lives in the Mushromp,
over there.
This bridge doesn't feel
very safe.
Come on, it's fine!
Whooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
APPLEJACK!
I'll save her.