♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
(All gasp)
This isn't the way out.
Shhhh...
Be very quiet.
The best thing that bag of
flubber, Porcina,
ever did was to turn
Ponyland into glass.
Ponyland!
Into glass?
And now it's all ours!
Yeah! And, we ain't gonna
share our new home
with nobody.
Look!
(cheer)
Oh, I just can't wait!
There ain't no place like home.
(All)
There ain't no place like--
What can we do?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Let's go take
a look at our new home.
(laugh and cheer)
This is so great home.
My darlings!
What are you doing here?
Well, Molly and I followed
Megan and the others here
in hopes that we could help
rescue you.
I mean, I could help rescue you.
I mean, after all,
it was probably my fault
in the first place
that you were captured.
I should have stayed with you,
gotten help or something.
Oh, no!
It wasn't your fault.
You couldn't have saved us
from the Raptorians.
Anyway, I think I just might
be able to help after all.
Did you ever notice how much
hair the Bushwoolies shed?
(All)
Yeah, Yeah. Shed!
And how much it looks
like pony hair once it's cut.
(All)
Yeah! Yeah. Pony hair.
Yeah, pony hair.
If we use the Bushwoolie hair
to weave a fake magic cloak
and exchange it for the real one
maybe we can use the real one
to change the spell?
(All)
Yeah, yeah! Hair. Yeah, cloak.
To the weaving room.
(All)
- Hurray!
- Shhhh...
Okay, let's do it!
(snoring)
My beautiful cloak.
My beauty.
Beauty...
(snoring continues)
Shhhhh.
Ah...ah...ah.
Ah, thanks.
(Porcina mumbles)
Hmm... My lovely, lovely cloak.
(snoring)
What are they doing?
Shhhhh.
What do we do now?
Gusty, you stand on
that side of the bed,
Shady, on this side.
Molly, hold the torch up.
And I'll stand at the foot.
As soon as she moves, grab it!
Oh, oh, all these
wonderful mirrors!
Oh, I must be even
more magnificent than I thought.
(sneezes)
Sorry, I think
I'm allergic to pigs.
Oh, dear! Which one
is the real cloak?
Somebody is coming.
(indistinct conversation)
(All)
Hide, hide, yeah, hide.
Raptorians are coming.
Yeah, coming.
I hope this is it.
Porcina! Porcina!
Porcina!
The Ponies have escaped.
Oh, what is it, Shrock?
It's the Ponies!
Ah...Ah...Ah...
They've escaped.
Escaped?
You got to help us find them
and...and turn them into glass
before they ruin everything.
You're giving me orders now?
(sneezes)
Ponies!
Get'em!
Stop, before I turn
you into toads.
Oh, she's bluffing!
That's an obvious fake.
Porcina, turn 'em all into glass
before they ruin everything.
(magical incantation)
Kazeem! Kazaam...
Oh, oh!
Ah, I-I can't.
I can't.
The Ponies in my crystal orb
didn't seem real.
But these Ponies here,
these living, breathing,
trembling creatures of flesh
are alive,
just like you and me.
I don't have the right
to turn them into glass.
What!
Are you crazy?
They'll ruin everything.
Then give it to me.
All right, you little pests.
First I'm gonna turn you all
into glass
and then I'm gonna shatter
you one by one.
(magical incantation)
Kazeem! Kazaam!
Kazoom!
This cloak's a dud.
That must be the real one.
Get it boys!
(indistinct muttering)
Don't be afraid.
Huh?
(indistinct muttering)
(All scream)
Don't worry,
they never felt it.
In fact, they never
felt anything.
Not about you or me, not about
anything but themselves.
I guess I didn't see that.
I didn't see a lot of things
till now.
Well, there's still time
to put things right.
Let's get back to Ponyland
and help our friends.
Okay. In fact,
I'll lead the way.
(magical incantation)
Beem! Salaah! Sim!
(cheer and merriment)
Wait.
(magical incantation)
Kazoom! Kazaam! Kazeem!
(cheer and merriment)
You see, Shady, your bravery,
quick thinking came through
when we needed them most.
So don't you ever
underestimate yourself again.
(indistinct chattering)
Now well that cloak was probably
never a good thing for me
to have had anyway.
But what's to become of me now?
Bushwoolies think
Porcina not so bad.
Oh!
Why not stay with
Bushwoolies underground?
We need clever and
beautiful hair groomer.
(All)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Beautiful groomer.
Oh, why not?
(All)
Bye, bye! Bye! Bye!