♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
Get him.
Whoah!
Don't let the Stonebacks
get me, Megan.
They won't hurt you, Furbob.
Would you rather be up there?
Come on.
Let's fill up the hole.
I can't see a thing.
We know they're down there.
And so is the Sunstone.
Lead the way, Pointer.
Er...
Listen, your Bumbleness.
I'm not really good
at dark places...
Could somebody else go?
What?
Are you saying no to me?
Well, no. No, no, no, no, no!
It's just that you're the queen.
I wouldn't want anyone to think
that...that...that
you're not the bravest just
because you didn't go first.
Oh yes.
Bravest.
Very well, Pointer.
I shall deed
by my deeds,
not by my words.
Stand back!
Get me out of here!
If we hurry,
we can still get the Sunstone
back to Flutter Valley
before sunset.
You can't stay
there forever, Furbob!
Yes I can.
At least until
the Stonebacks leave!
But they don't want to leave.
They helped save us.
I still think it's a trick.
Stonebacks hate Furbobs!
(Blows raspberry)
(snorts)
Why did you do that?
We always do that.
Then they chase us,
and we run away,
and we have to
find a new home.
Did you ever think that
maybe
the Stonebacks
want to be your friends?
Are you serious?
All they do is snort,
dig up the ground and chase us.
It's not easy to get your point
across when you can't talk.
Try imagining what it would be
like if the Stonebacks
were your friends.
My imagination is not
that good.
Try, Furbob.
♪ Imagine you were friends ♪
♪ Think how it would be ♪
♪ You'd ask them for
a helping hand ♪
♪ They'd lend you one
for free ♪
♪ Imagine you were pals ♪
♪ You could be if you tried ♪
♪ Imagine being in a band ♪
♪ And marching side by side ♪
♪ Imagine playing games
together ♪
♪ Or being inside when
it's stormy weather ♪
♪ Imagine something you
have never known ♪
♪ Never ever feeling alone ♪
♪ How happy I would be ♪
♪ If you could make amends ♪
♪ The whole world would
be better off ♪
♪ Imagine you were friends ♪
♪ How happy I would be ♪
♪ If you could make amends ♪
♪ The whole world would
be better off ♪
♪ Imagine you were
friends... ♪ ♪
What do you think,
Furbob?
Well, it does sound
like a good idea.
(snorts)
But I do have to check
with the other Furbobs first.
Come on, Megan.
We have to get the Sunstone
back to Flutter Valley.
How are you going to
get it there, Rosedust?
It's too hot to handle.
All we have to do
is cool it off.
We can use utter flutter.
Right, let's do it.
That's fantastic.
I wonder if I can do that?
It's cold now.
We can move it.
I've got the Sunstone.
Which way to Flutter Valley?
(snorts)
They want us to follow them.
To Flutter Valley.
Hurry!
Buzz, buzz, buzz!
Er...
Don't be so upset,
your Bumbleness.
Upset?
WHO'S UPSET?
Buzz!
It's just a silly Sunstone.
We never had one before.
I know that.
But once you taste
the good life
it's very hard to give it up.
So I have an idea,
Pointer.
Er...
What is that,
your Bumbleness?
LET'S GO TO FLUTTER VALLEY
AND GET IT BACK!
(Stonebacks snorts)
It's almost sunset.
We'll never make it in time.
Oh, Flutter Valley
is going to wilt away.
Don't give up,
Flutter Ponies.
There's still time to get
the Sunstone in place.
Don't forget the witches.
What about them?
Oh,
I forgot to tell you,
the witches have
taken over Flutter Valley.
Oh no!
I'll go to Furbobia,
and get the rest of the Furbobs.
Maybe they can help.
Hop on, Furbob!
I'll get you there in no time.
Meet you all at Flutter Valley.
Not that way,
this way.
(buzz)
It's a race against the sun,
Flutter Ponies. Hurry!
(snorts)
(gasps)
Can I stop now, Hydia?
Please!
No, one more lap.
Because of you the little ponies
almost escaped.
Yeah, sister dear.
(crunches)
They almost got away.
She heard me.
She didn't mean to disobey you,
Hydia.
It was really our fault.
Yeah. Gee, we were only trying
to teach her some magic tricks.
I'll teach the tricks
in my family, okay?
Everybody is a magician.
The Flutter Ponies
are coming back.
What?
(gasps)
I said, the Flutter Ponies
are coming back.
Listen.
It is the Flutter Ponies.
(cheers)
There's still time
to save Flutter Valley.
Shut up! There's no time
to save anything.
It's almost sunset.
We've got to stop them,
Hydia.
What if they have the Sunstone?
Ahhg!
Roooooaaaaggghhrr!
Guard the entrance.
Don't let anyone in. Nobody.
Rooaaaagghhrr!
Oh no. Not Ahhg.
They'll never get past him.
But Hydia, don't you remember
what happened the last time?
Of course I remember.
And Ahhg won't be tickled again.
Come here, Ahhgy.
I've got something for you.
Roooaaaaggghhrr!
Drink this,
my little Ahhgy.
And we won't have anything
to fear from Megan
and the Flutter Ponies.
We're going to make it.
It's Ahhg!
He's blocking the way.
Rooooaaagghr!
Not you again?
Rooooaaaaghr!
We can fly over him, Megan,
but we can't carry the Sunstone.
It's too heavy.
We'll never make it
in time now.
Not to worry. I know just
how to handle Ahhg.
We found out he's ticklish.
All you have to do is tickle him
and he'll fold up
like an accordion.
Coochy coochy coo!
Maybe if we all do it...
I don't understand.
It worked last time.
Rooooaaaaghr!
We'll never get past him.
And it's almost sunset.
What are we going to do?
Roooaaaaghhr!