♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ What will
today's adventure be? ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ Will there be
exciting sights to see? ♪
♪ Where will you wander?
Hither and yonder ♪
♪ Letting your heart
be your guide ♪
♪ My Little Pony...
My Little Pony ♪
♪ I'll be there
right by your side ♪
♪ I'll be there...
It will all be over soon!
What the...
This is incredible!
We coulda told you that.
You know,
we'll probably
never let you leave now.
(laughs)
Oh, darlings!
We're trapped down here forever
unless Megan and the others
manage to find us.
But does anybody
even know that we are missing?
Well, I did drop
my sweatband
at the entrance to the cave.
You did?
Good thinking, Gusty.
Yeah. But who's
ever gonna find it up
here in the Black Mountains?
Oh...
This way.
(All gasp)
Oh, my dears!
You will complete the work
of replacing my magical cloak,
so my world will be filled
with my radiance,
my own extraordinary,
indescribable beauty.
(sneezes)
(mirror breaks)
(All laugh)
Okay, start spinning.
Of course,
if you stop cooperating,
you will be the first to feel
the glassy wrath of the great
and beautiful Porcina.
Whereupon
all of your little friends
back in Ponyland
will be happy to do our bidding.
Yeah,
'cause they will be
turned into glass.
So get to work.
Faster, faster!
This way.
(All)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This way.
Oh, ooh, oh.
Maybe that way?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
that way, that way.
Could this be the way in?
Bushwoolies remember now,
this is it!
(All)
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
this is it, this is it!
Well, of course,
you probably do know the way,
but, well,
it could be more dangerous
down there than you think.
D-Dangerous?
Oh! no!
Bushwoolies don't like danger,
n-n-no sir.
Don't like danger?
Uh-huh-uh, no sir, no sir.
Okay. The Ponies and I will
lead the way. Let's go.
Uh!
What's the matter?
Let's keep out of sight.
Why?
I thought once we
caught up with them.
Yeah, I know. But I thought
if we keep an eye on them,
we'd be the back-ups.
Something extra
in an emergency.
Besides, maybe I'll get a chance
to do something special.
- What's that?
- I don't know.
Which way do we go?
This way.
This way exactly, this way.
Wait a minute!
Follow me.
♪ Oh, what a tangled
web we weave ♪
♪ A tangled web
we weave ♪
♪ Our legs all ache ♪
♪ Our backs may break ♪
♪ Oh, how we wish
we could leave ♪
Come on get to work,
move it.
♪ Oh, what a nasty
fate's in store ♪
♪ A nasty
♪ A world of glass
will come to pass ♪
♪ We'll see Ponyland
no more ♪
♪ oh, yeah.
We are all in stitches. ♪
♪ Isn't it a joke? ♪
♪ Soon we'll
swim in riches ♪
♪ Thanks to Porcina's cloak
(laughs) ♪
♪ Oh, what a tangled web
we weave ♪
♪ It makes
our poor hearts grieve ♪
♪ Wait till Porcina learns ♪
♪ what's up our sleeves ♪
♪ Oh. what a tangled web ♪
♪
Oh, what a tangled web ♪
♪ Oh, what a tangled web
we weave ♪
It's finished.
The cloak is finished!
Now we'll have everything
we waited for.
No more puttin' up
with this bowing and scraping.
Yeah!
Oh!
Come on,
let's go.
It's the Ponies!
Let me see.
Don't push.
Bushwoolies want to see too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah!
You found my headband!
Oh! Hurry
before they come back!
Are you guys okay?
Yes, but, please hurry,
so we can get out of here.
Don't forget
Porcina's threat.
What threat?
And who's Porcina?
She's the princess that all
this belongs to.
And she threatened to turn
Ponyland into glass!
I thought the Raptorians
kidnapped you.
They did.
But they work for Porcina.
How can she turn Ponyland
into glass?
She's a magic princess.
There's no way
we could stop her.
No!
We'll find a way to stop her.
I've gotta think of a way
to stop the princess.
Her magic is all
in her cloak,
and I must say it looks
much better
since they used
all our hair to re-weave it.
Oh!
The cloak is beautiful!
Oh,
and I'm beautiful too,
don't you agree?
A sight for sore eyes.
Yeah, very sore.
(sarcastic coughing)
Don't you wanna test out
the power of your new cloak?
Of course,
but what should I test it on?
Ponyland!
Ooh, uh-uh,
yes.
That could do
with some improving.
(magical incantation)
Kazeem! Kazaam!
Kazoom!
(All)
Oh! Noo...
Your work is truly
magnificent,
oh, omnipotent mistress.
Oh, most fair one!
But, would your mirrored world
not take on an added beauty?
If all the creatures in it
also reflected your loveliness?
Uh, why...
Uh--my feeling exactly.
Oh, dear me,
I know it's here somewhere.
Ah, ha! Here it is!
(magical incantation)
Beenasim Salaah!
There, it's done.
(yawning)
Oh, my... This is exhausting.
Go lie down
my beautiful porkiness.
Uh...uh...I-I mean my
beautiful princess.
You don't want to spoil
your good looks
on hard work like this.
Thank you, Shrock.
You're so kind.
So thoughtful.
Oh, boy,
she's gone.
Hey! I got here first.
Yeah,
but you sat there last time.
Ahem!
Uh, would you care to sit down?
It's nice and comfy.
We did it, boss,
we did it!
Ponyland is ours!
At last,
a kingdom to call home.
(wicked laughter)